I've got three boxes here. One of them
我这里有三个箱子。其中之一
contains $1,000. One of them contains
内含1000美元。其中之一包含
$10,000. And one of them contains
10,000美元。其中之一包含
$100,000. And you three are the avengers
10万美元。你们三个就是复仇者联盟。
of entrepreneurship on the internet. So,
互联网创业。所以，
you're going to tell me what you would
你要告诉我你会怎么做
do with that amount of money to build a
用这笔钱来建造一个
scalable business.
可扩展的业务。
&gt;&gt; So, do I get to give the money? Is that
那么，我可以给这笔钱吗？是吗？
how this works?
这是怎么回事？
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, I would three highly
好的。所以，我会强烈推荐三家。
successful entrepreneurs with three very
拥有三个非常成功的企业家
different perspectives. This is the
不同的视角。这是
ultimate master class in creating and
创作和创作的终极大师班
scaling your businesses to make
扩大业务规模以实现
millions. There's two paths to making
百万。通往成功之路有两条。
money quickly if you don't have any. And
如果你没钱，可以快速筹钱。和
the first path is go find the best
第一条路是去寻找最好的
entrepreneur and go work for them. Learn
创业并为他们工作。学习
as much as you can.
尽你所能。
&gt;&gt; Totally agree. Like Kim Kardashian was
完全同意。就像金·卡戴珊那样
Harris Hilton's assistant and she
哈里斯·希尔顿的助理和她
learned the playbook for being famous.
学会了如何成名。
And then she took it to a new level.
然后她又把这件事提升到了一个新的高度。
&gt;&gt; And then the second way is high risk but
第二种方法风险很高，但
highest reward. Go do it yourself.
最高奖励。自己去做吧。
&gt;&gt; And the first business that you start,
你创办的第一家企业，
you're going to be learning the game of
你即将学习的游戏是
business even more than you're learning
商业方面的内容甚至比你学到的还要多
the business that you're doing. Things
你正在从事的业务。事物
like if you wait 8 seconds after you ask
比如，你问完问题后等8秒钟。
someone to buy, you close 30% more
如果有人买，成交价会高出30%。
sales. And there are actual studies now
销售量。现在确实有相关的研究。
that show that if I'm a woman, you make
这表明，如果我是女性，你就会……
more money if you do one thing. You wear
做一件事就能赚更多钱。你穿着
makeup, which is wild.
化妆，真是太棒了。
&gt;&gt; And what about making content?
那么，内容创作方面呢？
&gt;&gt; Building a content empire that builds
打造一个能够不断发展壮大的内容帝国
your business. This is brand new to a
您的企业。这对于一个……来说是全新的。
lot of people. And so a lot of creators
很多人。所以很多创作者
online don't think about how do I
在线上别想我该怎么做
monetize on top of this,
在此基础上实现盈利，
&gt;&gt; right? And I can name some Tik Tokers
正确的？我还能说出一些TikTok网红的名字。
with 50 plus million followers that have
拥有超过5000万粉丝
had failed launches because they have
发射失败是因为他们有
views but they have zero influence. And
他们持有观点，但没有任何影响力。和
in order to create influence, there's
为了产生影响力，需要……
four things. So number one is
四件事。所以第一点是
&gt;&gt; okay so let's go on to simple actionable
好的，接下来我们来看一些简单易行的步骤。
frameworks.
框架。
&gt;&gt; So I have a framework in order to raise
所以我有一个框架来提高
money.
钱。
&gt;&gt; I have a framework for pitching
我有一个推销框架
&gt;&gt; and I have one that can increase sales
我有一个可以提高销售额的工具。
by 20 to 40%.
增长20%至40%。
&gt;&gt; And then if you want to know if your
然后，如果你想知道你的
business is going to make you money or
做生意会让你赚钱，或者
not we use the moat strategy
我们不采用护城河策略
&gt;&gt; and there's a lot more. So let's go
还有更多。那么，我们走吧
through all of this.
经历了这一切。
[Music]
[音乐]
Daniel, Cody, Alex, I feel like I have
丹尼尔、科迪、亚历克斯，我觉得我好像有
waited a long time to have this
等了很久才拥有这个
conversation with you three because in
和你们三个聊天是因为在
my mind, you three are the avengers of
在我看来，你们三个就是复仇者联盟。
entrepreneurship on the internet. And
互联网创业。和
for very different reasons, you do very
出于截然不同的原因，你非常
different things. You have very
不同的事情。你非常
different perspectives. You run very
不同的视角。你跑得很快
different businesses. But for those
不同的企业。但对于那些
people that are sat at home and they
那些待在家里的人
have an idea and they're mulling whether
他们有了个想法，正在考虑是否
that is the idea worth pursuing, is
那才是值得追求的想法，是
there a framework for knowing if it's a
是否存在一个框架来判断它是否是
good idea or a bad idea? What we use
好主意还是坏主意？我们使用
that comes from private equity. If you
这主要来自私募股权。如果你
want to know if your business is going
想知道你的企业是否正在发展
to make you money or not or investable
能不能赚钱，或者是否值得投资。
or not, we use the MOAT strategy which
或者，我们采用MOAT策略，
is basically M stands for margin. So you
M 基本上代表边际。所以你
want a business that actually makes you
想要一家真正能让你赚钱的公司
money, doesn't just generate revenue.
金钱不仅仅能创造收入。
And so a good business typically has at
因此，一家好的企业通常具备……
least 15% net margin. So that's the
至少15%的净利润率。就是这样。
money you put in your your pocket,
你放在口袋里的钱，
right?
正确的？
&gt;&gt; So that's profit.
这就是利润。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Yeah.
是的。是的。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. And then uh the O stands for
确切地。然后，呃，O代表……
operations. So operations being can this
运营。所以操作可以这样进行。
thing actually scale over time or will I
事物真的会随着时间推移而变化吗？还是不会？
really have a job, not a business? And
你是真的有份工作，而不是自己创业？和
what's the difference there?
有什么区别？
&gt;&gt; The difference between the two is if you
两者的区别在于，如果你
have a job, not a business, that might
拥有一份工作，而不是一家公司，这可能会
be for instance without AI, if my entire
例如，如果没有人工智能，如果我的整个
business was just me talking
生意上的事，我只是在说话而已。
continuously to camera and I'm an actor,
我一直对着镜头，我是一名演员。
it's really hard to turn acting to a
将表演转变为……真的很难
business, right?
生意，对吧？
&gt;&gt; You're trading time,
你是在用时间换取时间。
&gt;&gt; right? You're still an employee. You're
正确的？你仍然是公司员工。你是
just self-employed as opposed to a
只是自雇人士，而不是
business owner. And there's a real
业主。而且确实存在这种情况
difference between a CEO and a
CEO和A的区别
self-employed person. And then the A
自雇人士。然后是A
stands for advantage, which is, do I
代表优势，也就是，我是否……
have an unfair advantage in my business?
我的业务中是否存在不公平的优势？
I think over time all arbitrage windows
我认为随着时间的推移，所有套利窗口都会消失。
close. So, if you don't have some sort
关闭。所以，如果你没有任何
of advantage, it's hard to stay in
拥有优势，就很难保持优势。
business over a long time. An advantage
长期经营的业务。优势
might be I have distribution because I
或许我有分销渠道，因为我
have social media, so I can get more
我有社交媒体账号，这样我就可以获得更多
eyeballs. I can figure out how to talk
眼球。我可以想办法开口说话。
to 2,000 people quickly because I can do
因为我能做到，所以很快就能向 2000 人传达信息。
it via video as opposed to knocking on
通过视频而不是敲门的方式进行。
20 doors. H or it could be logistics or
20扇门。或者可能是物流或其他方面。
it could be uh 10 years of experience in
可能需要10年的经验
an industry. And then the T stands for
一个行业。然后，T 代表
TAM, total addressable market, which
TAM，即总潜在市场，指的是
goes back to the doggy teeth issue,
又回到了狗狗牙齿的问题上来，
which is, you know, is this a real
也就是说，你知道，这是真的吗？
market that enough people are interested
市场需要有足够多的人感兴趣
in that I can build a business that is
因为我可以建立一个这样的企业
big enough for me? And, you know, to
够大吗？而且，你知道，
Alex's point, I don't think everybody
亚历克斯的观点是，我认为并非所有人都如此。
should try to play the trillion or
应该尝试玩万亿或
billion dollar uh game. In fact, I think
价值十亿美元的游戏。事实上，我认为
it can be quite miserable to to strive
努力奋斗可能会相当痛苦。
for billions. And so the the total
数十亿人。因此，总数
addressable market for your local fruit
本地水果的目标市场
stand in your community may be a perfect
在你的社区里站稳脚跟或许是个完美的选择。
amount of income for you, but let's
你的收入是多少，但我们……
actually know what amount of income is
实际上知道收入是多少
reasonable for you. And the cool thing
对你来说合理。还有一件很酷的事
about entrepreneurship in like today's
关于当今的创业精神
age, the data is available everywhere.
年龄方面，数据随处可得。
&gt;&gt; And so in private equity, you would take
因此，在私募股权投资中，你会采取
this model like that. So you'd go moat,
这个模型就是这样。所以你会挖护城河，
you would I take them and for each one,
你会让我把它们拿走，对于每一个，
I rank them one to 10 and businesses. So
我将它们和企业按 1 到 10 的分数进行排名。所以
margin, operations, advantage, total
利润率、运营、优势、总计
addressable market. each one of them. A
目标市场。他们每一个人。一个
10 is perfect. A one is the worst you
10分完美。一是最差的。
could have. And businesses that are
本来可以的。以及那些企业
better than 30 across all four, well,
四项指标均优于 30，嗯。
that's a fund it. That's a fundable
那是为了筹集资金。这是一个可融资的项目。
business model. Businesses that are less
商业模式。较少的企业
than 30 but more than 20, that's a fix
大于30但大于20，这算是一种解决办法。
it. You've got some problems in the
它。你遇到了一些问题
model. And businesses that are less than
模型。以及那些低于
20, that's a flee it. This is probably
20，那就赶紧逃吧。这大概是
not right for you and a hard business to
不适合你，而且生意很难做
do.
做。
&gt;&gt; I think it's not just the people who are
我认为不仅仅是那些人
looking for a new opportunity or people
寻找新的机会或人
who don't currently have a business. I
目前没有自己企业的人士。我
personally think at the moment every
就我个人而言，目前每个
single person on the planet who has a
地球上唯一拥有
business should assume that their
企业应该假定他们的
business is on borrowed time because AI
由于人工智能，企业正处于苟延残喘的状态。
is going to disrupt everything and in
将会扰乱一切，而且
that disruption everyone has the
每个人都会经历的那种干扰。
opportunity to rethink whether they want
有机会重新考虑他们是否想要
a different opportunity or whether they
不同的机会，或者他们是否
want to pivot. It's the perfect time. I
想转型。现在正是时候。我
look at simple things when I'm thinking
思考的时候，我会关注一些简单的事情。
about is it a good opportunity. I think
这是一个好机会吗？我认为
every good business is built upon
所有成功的企业都是建立在……之上的。
somebody's case study. So when I look at
某人的案例研究。所以当我看到
not just businesses as a thing on their
不仅仅是企业本身
own, I think businesses as a thing on
我认为，就我个人而言，企业本身就是一件事情。
their own have to be taken in
他们自己的人必须被带走。
consideration with who's the
考虑谁是
entrepreneur. So your entre like
企业家。所以你的入口就像
something that's a great opportunity for
这对……来说是个绝佳的机会
Cody may be just a disaster for me and
科迪对我来说可能就是个灾难。
like and likewise.
类似，也一样。
&gt;&gt; So I'm looking at the background of the
所以我现在正在查看背景信息
entrepreneur. Do you have a case study
企业家。您有案例研究吗？
to leverage? Do you have knowledge? Do
利用什么？你了解相关知识吗？做
you have a network? Do you have
你有网络吗？你有
resources? Have you got a reputation in
资源？你在哪方面有声誉？
something? Because those are the things
某物？因为那些就是这些事。
that we can then leverage. And then I'm
然后我们可以利用这一点。然后我
just going to have a look at three
我打算看一下这三个。
little things. I'm going to say this
小事。我要说的是……
idea that you've got going forward.
你对未来发展的想法。
Does this address someone's pain? Right?
这能缓解某人的痛苦吗？正确的？
Is there some sort of problem that this
这是否存在某种问题？
solves? And that to we could measure
解决了吗？而我们也可以衡量这一点
that, right? Because people pay to move
是吗？因为人们需要付费搬家。
a metric. They love to move some sort of
一个指标。他们喜欢移动某种东西
a number. So, is there a pain that we
一个数字。所以，我们是否感到痛苦？
can measure and can I take people out of
可以测量，我可以把人带出去吗？
that pain based on my story?
我的经历让你感到痛苦吗？
&gt;&gt; The next thing is does that type of
接下来要说的是，那种类型的
person who I'm going to solve that for,
我要帮他解决这个问题的人，
do they have money to spend? Because
他们有钱花吗？因为
ultimately 60% of all the money is in
最终，60%的资金都流入了这些资金池。
the top 10%. So the top 10% have about
前10%。因此，排名前 10% 的人大约拥有
60% of the available disposable income.
可支配收入的 60%。
So groups that t tend to have money is
所以那些往往有钱的群体是
business owners, executives, people
企业主、高管、人员
who've got accumulated wealth. Um you
那些积累了财富的人。嗯，你
know, so you're looking at like some
知道了，所以你现在看到的就像是一些
sort of indication that you're selling
这似乎表明你在卖东西
to a group of people who have money.
对一群有钱人来说。
Underneath that top 10%, Amazon's
在排名前 10% 的市场之外，亚马逊的
already got them, McDonald's has already
麦当劳已经拿到了，他们已经
got them. Like that's a saturated part
收到了。就像那部分饱和了一样
of the market. You looking for that top
市场。你在找那件上衣吗？
10% who've got disposable income. And
10%的人有可支配收入。和
then the final part is passion. Like are
最后一部分是激情。就像
you passionate about this? And my
你对此充满热情吗？而我的
definition of passion is a willingness
激情的定义是意愿
to suffer. So it's not do you get joy
遭受痛苦。所以问题不在于你是否获得快乐。
from it, not are you super happy from
从中，你不是超级开心吗？
it. It's are you willing to suffer for
它。你是否愿意为此受苦
this? Are you willing to have delayed
这？你愿意延迟吗？
gratification um would an objective
满足感嗯，会是一个目标
third party who looks at your behavior,
第三方会观察你的行为，
who looks at the way that you show up in
谁会关注你的外表呢？
the world, would they agree that you
全世界的人都会同意你的观点。
seem to be willing to push through
似乎愿意继续推进
difficult times in order to have this?
经历如此艰难的时期才能拥有这一切？
So those are some of the conversations
以上就是部分对话内容。
I'd have with anyone. And not just
我会和任何人发生关系。而且不仅仅是
people who are starting out, people who
刚入行的人，那些
have already got a hundred million
已经拥有1亿
dollar business.
美元生意。
&gt;&gt; It's like the adult marshmallow test
这就像成人版的棉花糖实验
basically.
基本上。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I think Cody had a had a great
是的。我认为科迪过得很棒
framework in terms of thinking about
从思考的角度看框架
this from an investing perspective for
从投资角度来看，这是因为
the people who are considering starting
那些正在考虑创业的人
their first business. I like the pain
他们的第一份事业。我喜欢这种痛苦
passion profession angle of like
热情职业角度
typically it'll be something that comes
通常情况下，它会是某种来袭的东西。
from a personal pain that you overcame
从你克服的个人痛苦中走出来
whether it's you had an eating disorder
无论你是否患有饮食失调症
or you have kids who have allergies and
或者你的孩子有过敏症，
you figured out how to pack lunches or
你学会了如何打包午餐或
you figured out how to store stuff for
你已经找到了储存物品的方法
twice as long because of some unique
由于某些特殊原因，时间延长了一倍。
thing that that you retrofitted a cooler
你改装的那个冷却器
with. whatever some passion which is
和。无论某种激情是什么
just like a hobby that's that's you're
就像你的爱好一样
deeply interested in or it's a
对……非常感兴趣，或者说，这是一个……
profession so something that you already
职业，所以你已经拥有的东西
currently do like in a way this is I
目前我确实喜欢这种方式，我
think one of the easiest self-
想想最简单的自我提升方法之一
entrepreneur you know self-employment
企业家，你知道的，自雇人士
path is just going from employed to
这条路就是从就业到……
self-employed doing the same thing that
自雇人士做着同样的事情
somebody already pays you for
已经有人付钱给你了。
&gt;&gt; so like you don't need to worry about
所以你不用担心
like market risk of like I wonder if if
就像市场风险一样，我想知道如果
accounting is still going to be desired
会计仍然会受到人们的青睐。
by other people like right now because
像现在这样，其他人也一样。
everyone's so interconnected like remote
每个人都像远程办公一样紧密相连。
work and being able to be fractional
工作和能够兼职
like many people can start kind of mini
就像很多人一样，可以开始某种迷你项目
consulting businesses doing, you know,
咨询公司从事，你知道的，
because a lot of businesses and
因为很多企业和
entrepreneurs are very um bad at
创业者非常不擅长……
allocating resources. And so they have a
资源分配。所以他们有
lot of quote full-time employees that
很多全职员工都这么说。
are working 20% of their effort and
他们只投入了20%的精力，
still keep, you know, keeping their
仍然保留着，你知道，保留着他们的
paycheck and at the end of the day like
工资单，以及一天结束时的感受
they do enough to keep their job, but
他们做得足够好，足以保住工作，但是
not so much that they are nearly at
还不至于他们几乎已经到了
their full discretionary effort. And so
他们竭尽全力。所以
all of a sudden you think, okay, well, I
突然间你想，好吧，我
could probably do the same work for half
或许花一半的钱就能完成同样的工作。
the price and the entrepreneur be
价格和企业家
willing to pay it, but I could do that
我愿意支付，但我可以做到。
same work for half the price for five
同样的工作，五人份的价格减半。
times the people and make three times as
人数翻倍，数量翻三倍
much and do it on my own time. And so
很多都是我自己做的，而且都是利用自己的时间。所以
that becomes I think a great like foray
我认为这就像一次伟大的突袭
into entrepreneurship. Now what do you
投身创业。现在你打算怎么办？
have to learn there? It's like well you
必须在那里学习吗？就像你一样
already have delivery down because you
因为你已经把交付搞定了
already do the job. You just have to
已经完成了这项工作。你只需要
learn how to promote. It's just like how
学习如何进行推广。就像这样
do you reach out to people and ask them
你会主动联系别人并询问他们吗？
if they want what you have and then get
如果他们想要你拥有的东西，那就去拿。
them to trade you money for it. Um but
他们会让你用钱来换它。嗯，但是
that like at least takes half of it out
那至少能去掉一半。
of the equation. And almost all three of
方程。几乎这三个人
those pain, passion, profession, you
那些痛苦、激情、职业，你
already have kind of the back end. Like
后端已经有了雏形。喜欢
you have the pain, you figured out the
你感受到了痛苦，你找到了解决办法
thing. Uh the passion, you've already
事物。呃，热情，你已经有了
spent all this time loving this thing.
一直以来都喜欢这个东西。
So you've already done a lot of the the
所以你已经做了很多……
work and research. And so really you
工作和研究。所以，真的，你
just need to learn the front end which
只需要学习前端，
is like how do I promote and how do I
就像我该如何推广以及如何……
sell, right? how to get someone to give
卖掉，对吧？如何让别人给予
me money for it. And then in terms of um
给我钱。然后就……而言
how much money you make, I think Dana
我想，达娜，你挣多少钱？
had a great perspective of like, you
对你来说，你有着很棒的视角
know, sell the rich, like they're the
知道，把富人卖掉，就像他们是……
ones who have the money. And if you uh
有钱人。如果你呃
sell rich people, you get to sell at
向有钱人推销，你就能以……的价格卖出去。
rich people prices, which is more fun.
有钱人的价格，这更有趣。
Uh and so I mean, I'll give you a simple
嗯，所以我的意思是，我会给你一个简单的
example. Um I have a CRO company that
例子。嗯，我有一家CRO公司，
that we do a conversion rate
我们计算转化率
optimization across our sites and our
优化我们网站和我们的
portfolio. And so if that company go
文件夹。所以如果那家公司
works with an e-commerce business and
与一家电子商务企业合作，
they, you know, add 10% to, you know,
你知道，他们会在……的基础上加10%，
topline and goes from 1 million to 1.1
总销售额从100万增至110万。
million, they make $100,000 of value. If
一百万美元，他们创造了10万美元的价值。如果
they work with an e-commerce business
他们与一家电子商务公司合作。
that's doing $100 million a year and
那家公司每年营业额达1亿美元。
they do the same exact work and they add
他们做着完全相同的工作，并且还增加了
10%, they add $10 million a year. So
10%，他们每年增加1000万美元。所以
it's a hundred hundred times more in
比这多一百倍
terms of value that's being created. And
就所创造的价值而言。和
so fundamentally, you have the value
所以从根本上讲，你拥有价值
they create, your ability to negotiate a
它们创造，你的谈判能力
slice of that pie, how unique that is.
能分到一块这样的蛋糕，真是太独特了。
As in, for example, I could have plenty
例如，我可能有很多
of sales guys are like, "Hey, Alex, I
销售人员会说：“嘿，亚历克斯，我
could sell millions of dollars of stuff
可以卖出价值数百万美元的东西
for I'm like, "Yeah, but so could every
因为我会想，“是啊，但每个人都可以这么做。”
other salesperson." So, you have
其他销售员。”所以，你有
significantly less uh you know,
明显减少，你知道的，
negotiating power even if you have the
即使你拥有谈判能力
negotiating skill just because many
谈判技巧仅仅是因为许多
other people can do it, right? And then
其他人也能做到，对吧？进而
the third the the final component is
第三个，也是最后一个组成部分是
risk. And that's the one that I would
风险。而那正是我要说的。
multiply everything by, which is how
将所有数字乘以，就是这样
much risk you take on.
你承担了多少风险。
&gt;&gt; People often say this idea of selling to
人们经常说这种向……销售的想法
the rich, but as you explained it there,
富人，但正如你刚才解释的那样，
what what it actually sounded more like
它实际听起来更像什么呢？
is sell to the person who's going to
是卖给即将……的人
yield the most returns from your skill.
最大限度地发挥你的技能。
&gt;&gt; And I I reflect on this because I spent
我反思这件事是因为我花了
the first half of my career doing social
我职业生涯的前半段从事社交活动
media marketing. Yeah. I think I said
媒体营销。是的。我想我说过
this when we sat down that I used to
当我们坐下来的时候，我过去常常……
work with fast fashion companies or
与快时尚公司合作或
fashion and the net return
时尚与净回报
&gt;&gt; of me selling them all dresses was tens
我把所有裙子都卖了，一共花了数十万英镑。
of thousands. I then left that business
成千上万。然后我就离开了那家公司。
and spent two years working in
并在那里工作了两年。
psychedelics in the biotech industry
生物技术行业的迷幻剂
where if this was around the g the meme
如果这是关于梗图的
stock thing where if they could
股票交易，如果他们可以
galvanize people on social media to care
动员社交媒体上的人们关心
about their stock the upside the swing
关于他们的股票上涨潜力
was billions of dollars. I was the only
高达数十亿美元。我是唯一
employee in this biotech firm that ended
这家生物技术公司的员工已经离职
up listing on the NASDAQ for $3.2
在纳斯达克上市，价格为3.2美元。
billion. And so their remuneration to me
十亿。所以他们给我的报酬就是如此。
for the six months contract was many
六个月的合同有很多
many many many many millions.
数以百万计。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Because they they made billions.
因为他们赚了数十亿美元。
&gt;&gt; So for me they they thought they were
所以对我来说，他们认为他们是
ripping me off.
坑我。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And and I think about funnily enough
而且，我觉得很有意思的是
when you put the same company on
当你把同一家公司放在
different stock markets
不同的股票市场
&gt;&gt; the the company is worth wildly
这家公司价值连城。
different. And I think the same about
不同的。我也这么认为。
our skills where think about the stock
我们的技能在于思考股票
market where you're trading your skills.
你用技能进行交易的市场。
&gt;&gt; I've got a I got a small example of that
我有一个很小的例子。
really small example. There was a guy
一个很小的例子。有个家伙
who we worked with who was an
我们曾与一位名叫……的人共事。
occupational health and safety uh
职业健康与安全
consultant and inside the workplace in a
顾问，并在工作场所内部
typical office he would charge a couple
通常情况下，他会在办公室收取几美元的费用。
of grand a day
盛大的一天
&gt;&gt; uh to go in and it was about 10 days so
呃，进去之后大概过了10天。
about 20 grand to do an occupational
做职业培训大约需要2万美元。
health and safety. And I asked him the
健康与安全。我问他
question, "What is the most dangerous
问题：“最危险的是什么？”
workplace you've ever worked in?" And he
你曾经工作过的工作场所是什么样的？”他
says, "Well, there's this type of
他说：“嗯，有这种类型的……”
manufacturing that has lasers, freezing
具有激光、冷冻等制造工艺
stuff, boiling stuff, lava, you know,
东西，沸腾的东西，熔岩，你知道的。
the sharks, you know, the whole thing,
你知道，鲨鱼，所有的一切。
right? Whatever it is, and not actual
正确的？无论它是什么，都不是实际的
sharks, but you get the idea." And I
鲨鱼，但你明白我的意思。”而我
said, "Do you know how to solve the
他说：“你知道如何解决……”
problems of that workplace?" And he
“那个工作场所存在什么问题吗？”他
says, "Yeah, I absolutely know how to
他说：“是的，我完全知道怎么做。”
fix those problems." I said, "Why don't
解决这些问题。”我说：“为什么不呢？”
you position yourself and why don't you
你如何定位自己，以及你为什么不……
run a campaign that you're one of the
发起一场竞选活动，表明你是其中一员
best in the world for that and that
在这方面，它是世界上最好的。
you're actually going to just run a
你实际上只是要运行一个
campaign around that?" Um, within a year
围绕这个开展竞选活动？嗯，一年之内
his day rate had gone to 20,000 a day
他的日薪涨到了每天2万美元。
from 2,000 a day and a typical
每天2000美元起，典型值
engagement had gone up to 400 grand.
订婚费用已高达40万美元。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Mainly because he went from, you know,
主要原因是他从，你知道，
the same skill set, but he applied it to
他拥有同样的技能，但他将其运用到了
a a much, you know, more valuable
你知道，更有价值
environment. Podcasting is somewhat
环境。播客在某种程度上
similar, you know, because if I podcast
类似，你知道，因为如果我做播客的话。
in the UK, the amount of money I get per
在英国，我每……能拿到多少钱
view from YouTube is half versus if I do
YouTube 的观看量只有我的一半，如果我这样做的话……
the same activity, the same amount of
同样的活动，相同数量的
effort, the same amount of hours in the
付出同样的努力，花费同样的时间
United States, the platforms pay me
美国，这些平台付钱给我
double for the same amount of views. And
浏览量相同的情况下翻倍。和
I think many of us are like trying to
我认为我们很多人都像是在尝试……
get a pay rise from our boss or
从老板那里获得加薪
whatever, but actually thinking about
随便吧，但其实我在想……
are you trading your skills on the
你是在用你的技能进行交易吗？
highest return market is a great way. We
高回报市场是一个很好的途径。我们
I used to hire writers at my old company
我以前的公司经常招聘撰稿人。
and those writers would be paid you know
你知道，那些作家会得到报酬的。
30 $40 $50,000 whatever it was in the UK
30美元、40美元、50000美元，或者不管在英国是多少。
when when I was working in biotech and
当我还在生物技术行业工作的时候
we were looking for someone that could
我们一直在寻找能够
write about biotech it was a quarter of
写一篇关于生物技术的文章，这是四分之一
a million the salary it was five times
一百万的薪水是原来的五倍
more for the same fundamental skill of
对于同样的基本技能，需要投入更多。
writing.
写作。
&gt;&gt; I think that I think that a lot of times
我觉得很多时候
when you're starting out as a brand new
当你刚开始做一名新人时
entrepreneur it's scarier to sell to
向企业家推销产品更可怕
rich people. You're like I don't know
有钱人。你就像我不知道一样
rich people. I'm not a rich person. I'm
有钱人。我不是个有钱人。我是
going to sell to my friends. That is
准备卖给我的朋友们。那是
very normal. That's the people that you
非常正常。那就是你认识的那些人。
have the closest proximity to. But the
离得最近。但是
problem is is that means you have to
问题是，那是否意味着你必须
play the volume game. And the volume
玩转音量游戏。音量
game is actually really hard. It's hard
这游戏其实很难。这很难
to get a lot of people to buy your
让很多人购买你的产品
thing. Incredibly difficult. It's
事物。极其困难。它是
actually much easier to get a few rich
实际上，让少数人致富要容易得多。
people to buy your thing. And so, you
人们会购买你的产品。所以，你
know, we had this home inspection
我们之前做过房屋检查。
company and I didn't know it at the
公司和我当时都不知道。
time, but
时间，但是
&gt;&gt; he was telling me they were having like
他告诉我他们当时正在……
major cash issues in their business. And
他们的企业面临严重的现金流问题。和
uh and I could kind of tell because when
嗯，我大概能看出来，因为当
an entrepreneur is under stress, like
创业者承受着压力，就像
you can sort of see it, you know, it's a
你大概能看出来，你知道，那是一个
it's a a visual thing, too. and he was
这也是一种视觉体验。他当时
about 45 days away from uh running out
还有大约45天就用完了
of cash. And when I was sitting down and
现金。当我坐下时，
talking to him, I was trying to
我当时正试图和他交谈。
understand his business. Home inspection
了解他的业务。房屋检查
has been around forever. It's a
它一直都存在。这是一个
normalized business. This business
商业活动恢复正常。这家企业
works. It functions. It has good
作品。它能用。它有优点
margins. It's a rollup for private
边距。这是私人领域的汇总。
equity. The business model is not the
公平。商业模式并非
issue. So, what was the issue? The issue
问题。所以，问题到底是什么？这个问题
was their clients and their pricing. So,
关键在于他们的客户和定价策略。所以，
he was trying to be the home inspector
他当时想当房屋检查员。
for everyone at a lower price point. And
价格更低，人人都能负担得起。和
what does that mean? It means it was
这意味着什么？这意味着它是
actually really hard for him to
对他来说这真的很难
advertise because he wasn't niching
因为他没有做小众市场推广，所以才做广告。
down. He was competing with all of the
向下。他当时正在与所有……竞争
major players and he had very little
主要参与者，但他却很少。
margin because he was competing for
因为他当时正在竞争，所以有优势。
people who couldn't afford very much in
那些经济条件不太好的人
their home inspection costs. We made one
他们的房屋检查费用。我们做了一个
change which is we just said in front of
我们刚才提到的变化是在……前面
his business name and in all of his ads
他的公司名称以及他所有的广告名称都出现在他的广告中。
luxury home inspections instead of just
豪华住宅检查，而不仅仅是
San, you know, San Diego home
你知道，圣地亚哥的家
inspections or whatever city he was in
不管他当时在哪个城市，不管是检查还是其他什么活动。
previously. And that one change
之前。而那一次改变
increased his margins by 45% and they
他的利润率提高了45%，而且
saved his business. He didn't do more
挽救了他的生意。他没做更多。
volume. He didn't hire more people. He
体积。他没有雇佣更多人。他
didn't get smarter. He didn't get
并没有变得更聪明。他没得到
better. He just sold to rich people
更好的。他只是把东西卖给了有钱人。
instead. And because that increased the
反而。因为这增加了
surface area that he was covering, so
他所覆盖的表面积，所以
each house was like, I don't know,
每栋房子都感觉……我不知道该怎么形容，
thousands of dollars instead of a couple
几千美元，而不是几美元
hundred bucks to inspect, his business
检查费一百美元，他的生意
was saved forever. And so I I think
永远地保存了下来。所以我觉得
protecting your profit is so crucial
保护利润至关重要。
when you start a business. And nobody
当你开始创业时。而且没有人
tells you that because it feels safer to
告诉你，因为这样感觉更安全
sell things cheaply to people who don't
低价卖东西给那些不买东西的人
have very much money. But there's that
很有钱。但还有这一点。
old adage which is, you know, try to
俗话说，要尽量……
work with a $50 client and they will
与一位收费 50 美元的客户合作，他们将
say, "I need everything under the sun
我说：“我需要阳光下的一切。”
for this $50 I'm going to give you." And
为此，我将给你50美元。”
then go to a $50,000 client and they'll
然后去找一个价值 5 万美元的客户，他们会
say, "Why are scent?" And so, you know,
例如，“为什么会有气味？”所以，你知道，
so
所以
&gt;&gt; in the beginning, go for the $50,000.
一开始，先争取5万美元。
And the last thing I'll say on that is
最后我想说的是……
also when you're a young gun
当你年轻气盛的时候也是如此
entrepreneur, a lot of times people who
企业家，很多时候是那些
have money, they got there through
他们有钱，他们就是靠这个到达那里的。
business nine times out of 10. They see
十有八九都是生意。他们看到了
themselves in you as a young hard
他们自己就像你年轻时那样坚强。
worker. You can often get away with
工人。你通常可以侥幸逃脱惩罚
things when you are young working for
年轻时为……工作时会遇到的事情
somebody who is rich and sees themselves
一个富有且自视甚高的人
in you, especially in service businesses
在你身上，尤其是在服务行业
that you just can't at volume when
当你音量开到最大时，你根本做不到。
you're selling to people that really
你卖东西的对象是真正……的人
need that last dollar. And so I think
我需要最后一美元。所以我认为
that's why most businesses go
这就是为什么大多数企业会这样做。
servicebased business. You trade your
服务型企业。你用你的
time for money in some sort of way. Then
以某种方式用时间换取金钱。然后
you productize the service. So now you
你将服务产品化。所以现在你
make the service so other people can run
让其他人也能运行这项服务
it too. And then finally you turn it in
也是。最后，你把它交上去。
technology software as a service. you
技术软件即服务。你
increase your margin at every single one
提高每一笔交易的利润率
or your profit at every single one, but
或者说，你每次都能获得利润，但是
they're the same business. You're just
它们是同一家公司。你只是
smarter. You're you're a higher level
更聪明。你比我高一个级别
entrepreneur when you're able to create
当你能够创造时，你就是一名企业家。
tech around it. And but really all tech
相关的技术。但实际上所有科技
is is process at scale. And so it sounds
这是大规模处理的过程。听起来确实如此。
scary when you're just starting out, but
刚开始的时候会很害怕，但是
it it's it's really just the difference
这其实只是区别而已。
between 10 years in entrepreneurship and
在创业领域拥有 10 年以上经验
learning and not
学习而不是
&gt;&gt; I think when you um when you're starting
我觉得当你……当你开始的时候
out, you a lot of times you sell out of
出去，你很多时候都会卖光
your own wallet to to Cody's point. So,
用你自己的钱包来反驳科迪的观点。所以，
it's like you have no dollars in your
就好像你一分钱都没有一样
wallet, so you assume everyone else has
钱包，所以你假设其他人都有。
no dollars in their wallets either.
他们的钱包里也没有美元。
&gt;&gt; And you're so afraid of getting
你如此害怕得到
rejection that you continue to lower the
你不断降低的拒绝
price until you get here. You hear
价格直到你到达这里为止。你听到
people say yes. But just as like a
人们都说“是”。但就像……
benchmark for people who are starting
对于刚入行的人来说，这是一个基准。
out is that like usually you're
出局的情况就像通常那样，你是
appropriately priced when seven out of
价格合理，七分之七
10 people are saying no. Um that's like
10个人投了反对票。嗯，那就像
about the appropriate price. So if you
关于合适的价格。所以如果你
have like if I you know see a business
就像我看到一家企业一样
and they're doing 80% close rates as in
他们的成交率达到了80%，就像……
like 80% of uh the people they talk to
就像他们交谈过的80%的人一样
say yes, they usually have a double or
答应下来，他们通常会有双份或
triple in pricing just sitting there. If
价格就这么翻了三倍，就这么摆在那里。如果
they're at like 60% close rates, they
他们的成交率大概有60%，他们
usually have a one and a half to 2x
通常是 1.5 到 2 倍
price increase that's sitting there. If
价格上涨的问题就这么定了。如果
they're at, you know, 40 to 50, they've
他们现在大概40到50岁，你知道的，他们已经
got a 50% price raise in there. And if
价格上涨了50%。如果
they're right at that, you know, 30-ish
他们差不多就那个年纪了，你知道，30岁左右。
35%, then they're usually appropriately
35%，那么他们通常是合适的。
priced. And if they're at 20, they just
定价。如果他们只有20岁，他们就……
need to learn how to sell better. But
需要学习如何更好地销售。但
and so, but fundamentally, I say this
所以，但从根本上讲，我想说的是……
because usually, you know, in the
因为通常情况下，你知道，在
beginning of entrepreneurship, you're so
创业之初，你真是太棒了！
afraid of hearing no. Um, but the
害怕听到“不”。嗯，但是
reality of it is that you need to be
现实情况是，你需要……
hearing no more than you hear yes to
你听到的只有“是”。
know that you're being appropriately
要知道你的做法是恰当的。
priced
定价
&gt;&gt; because you like I way back in the day I
因为你就像我以前那样
had a gym. Um, and I had I can't
曾有健身房。嗯，我……我不能
remember how many members it was, but uh
还记得有多少成员吗？呃……
I I said that's it. And I decided to
我说过，就这样吧。于是我决定
triple my prices, which is a pretty big
价格翻三倍，这可不是个小数目。
move. Uh, we have a recurring membership
移动。呃，我们有定期会员资格。
base. And so I gave everyone a trial of
根据。所以我给每个人都试用了一下
the new level of service I wanted to
我想要的新服务水平
give. I wanted to go from large group to
给。我想从大团体到
semi-private. And um, I tripled the
半私密。嗯，我把……增加了三倍
price alongside that. and I lost
价格也包含在内。我输了
one-third of my customers. Um, but I had
我的三分之一客户。嗯，但我有
twothirds of the people at three times
三分之二的人在三倍
the price. And so I made um two times
价格。所以我做了两次
the revenue and I cut my costs by
我通过以下方式提高了收入并削减了成本：
twothirds.
三分之二。
&gt;&gt; And so I made a lot more money.
于是我赚了更多的钱。
&gt;&gt; And it was probably better for your
而且这可能对你更有利
clients as well. More exclusive
客户也是如此。更独家
experience.
经验。
&gt;&gt; 100%. And it was like right as I was
100%。就在我……的时候
beginning to learn how like pricing uh
开始学习如何定价之类的
worked with profit in a business. And so
在一家盈利性企业工作。所以
it and by doing that tripling in price,
它的价格因此翻了三倍，
it didn't like triple my profit. It did
它并没有让我的利润翻三倍。确实如此。
way more than that. And so like when you
远不止这些。所以就像当你
have a 10% or 15% margin business, like
拥有10%或15%利润率的业务，例如
Cody saying, if you actually can pull
科迪说，如果你真的能拉动
off a double in your pricing, it'd be a
价格翻倍，那就……
6x or 7x increase in profits.
利润增长6到7倍。
&gt;&gt; So there's a lot more sensitivity to
所以人们对……更加敏感
that price number. What's interesting is
那个价格数字。有趣的是……
that it's really just like, you know, a
其实就像，你知道，一个
lot of like, how do I raise my price?
很多人会问：我该如何提高价格？
It's like you do the exact same thing
就好像你做了完全一样的事
you normally do and then right when
你通常会这样做，然后就在这时
you're about to say the number, you just
你正要说出那个数字，你刚刚
add a zero and then and then you just
加个零，然后，然后你就……
act the same. Dan Kenny had this great
行为相同。丹·肯尼曾有过一段精彩的经历
quote. He said, um, go as high as you
引用。他说，嗯，尽可能高。
can without cracking a smile. Uh, and I
可以面不改色地做到。呃，还有我
think that's usually a pretty a pretty
我认为这通常相当不错
decent place to start. Yeah. And if
不错的起点。是的。如果
nobody is giving you push back on
没人反对你
pricing, that means you're too cheap
定价过低意味着你太抠门了。
immediately. Like I mean value metrics I
立即地。我的意思是，价值指标
think are so un listen the thing is like
觉得他们根本不听，事情是这样的
if you're a serious business person, you
如果你是一位认真的商人，你
want to make more money, pricing is
想赚更多钱，定价是
going to be really interesting to you.
你会觉得这很有意思。
If you're not a serious person wanting
如果你不是一个认真的人，
to make a lot of money, pricing seems
为了赚很多钱，定价似乎
like such a boring conversation. This
真是无聊透顶的对话。这
will never go viral on the internet
永远不会在互联网上爆红
except for people who actually are in
除了那些真正身处其中的人之外。
the game of business and they understand
他们了解商业游戏的规则。
that pricing save saves businesses. And
这种定价策略可以为企业节省成本。和
the the thing that I learned that I
我学到的那件事是……
thought was like wrong at first, and I'd
一开始我觉得错了，而且我
be curious if you guys were the same. I
我很好奇你们是不是也一样。我
thought it was wrong to charge different
认为收取不同的费用是错误的。
people different prices. I was like,
不同人群的定价不同。我当时就想，
"No, no, everybody gets the same price.
“不，不，大家的价格都一样。”
That's the right way to do business."
这才是正确的经商之道。
And then I realized there's something
然后我意识到有些事情……
called value metrics, which is basically
称为价值指标，它基本上是
your prices should be a representative
您的价格应该具有代表性。
of three things. Usage, so does somebody
三件事。用法，所以有人
use this service a ton? Then you should
你经常使用这项服务吗？那么你应该
charge them more. Do they have a lot of
向他们收取更高的费用。他们有很多吗？
users? Do lots of people use it on their
用户？很多人用它来做什么？
behalf. Or then finally, uh, value. How
代表。或者最后，呃，价值。如何
much value do they derive from it? Do
他们从中能获得多少价值？做
they make a ton of money? Um, you know,
他们赚了很多钱吗？嗯，你知道，
can they have some sort of quantifiable
它们能否具有某种可量化的指标？
return? And if you're charging everybody
返回？如果你要向所有人收费的话。
90 bucks a month for whatever your
每月90美元，无论你
service is, you are wasting a ton of
服务方面，你浪费了大量时间。
money from a segment of your clients
来自部分客户的资金
that would pay you way more.
那样你会赚到更多钱。
&gt;&gt; Like Typeform is a good example. I I
Typeform 就是一个很好的例子。我 我
started using Type Form, started using
开始使用 Type Form，开始使用
it myself. They charge me $50 a month.
我自己做的。他们每月向我收取50美元。
Then I started running tens of thousands
然后我开始跑数万公里
of surveys through there and I put my
我通过那里提交了一些调查问卷，我的
whole team on there. Now I'm paying
整个团队都在里面。现在我要付钱了。
$1,000 a month. It's the same [__]
每月1000美元。真是他妈的一样
tool.
工具。
&gt;&gt; Yes, it is. But I'm using it way more
是的。但我现在用得更多了。
and I've got more of my team using my
我的团队里有更多人在使用我的
account as well. So they're charging me
也记账。所以他们要向我收费。
a thousand just over $1,000 a month
一千美元，每月略高于1000美元。
&gt;&gt; and they only had to acquire you which
他们只需要得到你，
is amazing. So from acquiring one person
太棒了。所以从收购一个人开始
and you're like you know your cost of
你会想，你知道你的成本是多少
good or their cost of goods don't
商品或其商品成本并不高。
escalate at the same rate at all. So
以相同的速度升级。所以
that's how these SAS companies get this
这就是这些SAS公司获得这些产品的方式。
80% margins.
80%的利润率。
&gt;&gt; That's it. When you look at uh this this
就是这样。当你看着这个的时候
little pyramid of customer segmentation,
客户细分的小金字塔
you get 1% of people who have 15% of the
1% 的人拥有 15% 的
budget, 9% of people have 45% of the
预算方面，9%的人拥有45%的
budget. 90% of people combined 40%.
预算。 90%的人合计40%。
Right? So when you actually break that
正确的？所以当你真正打破那个
down, you have one person willing to pay
好吧，现在只有一个人愿意付费。
15 grand, you have nine people willing
15000美元，有九个人愿意
to pay 5 grand each, and you have 90
每人支付 5000 美元，你就有 90 个
people willing to pay 445 each. So you
愿意每人支付 445 的人。所以你
are almost always better off going I
几乎总是去I会更好。
think the best place for most small
认为对大多数小人来说，最好的地方是
businesses to go is that 9%. And the
企业发展前景看好，占比9%。以及
reason is the top 1% typically shop on
原因是，排名前 1% 的人通常会在……购物。
pedigree. They want to work with the
谱系。他们想与……合作
best businesses out there. They want to
最好的企业。他们想要
win work with the ones who have won
与那些已经获胜的人一起赢得工作
awards and the ones that have been
奖项以及已经获得的奖项
around for a long time.
存在了很长时间。
&gt;&gt; Relationships
人际关系
&gt;&gt; and and through trusted relationships.
并通过信任关系建立起来。
&gt;&gt; The 90% they shop on price. They have a
90%的人购物都以价格为导向。他们有一个
fixed price and they only want to shop
价格固定，他们只想购物。
on that price. The 9% shop on passion.
这个价格。 9% 的商店，充满激情。
They want to follow someone who's an
他们想追随一个……
interesting uh who has an interesting
有趣的是，谁有有趣的
new take on things who's putting
谁对事物有了新的见解
together a group who's done some
一群做过一些事情的人聚在一起
education or entertainment around it. So
围绕它进行教育或娱乐。所以
the this 9% I would call that the
我把这9%称为
affluent niche. And that affluent niche
富裕的小众群体。以及那个富裕的小众群体
is really good place to start. And that
这是一个非常好的起点。而那
9% are the ones that are closest to
9%是最接近的
moving into the 1%. So you can grow with
跻身前1%。所以你可以和……一起成长
a client over time, which we saw a lot.
随着时间的推移，我们经常遇到这样的客户。
&gt;&gt; You could help get them up to the 1% and
你可以帮助他们达到那1%的水平，
then then they'll take you and introduce
然后他们会带你去介绍你
you to all the others.
你也对其他人说。
&gt;&gt; This was one of the really fascinating
这是其中最引人入胜的事件之一。
things for me when I was running a
当我经营一家公司时，对我来说有些事情……
marketing business, which is I think you
营销业务，我认为这就是你
you referenced this Cody, which is when
你提到了科迪，就是在那时
I started the company, I was working
我创办了这家公司，我一直在工作。
with founders who had a 10K budget and
创始人当时只有 1 万美元的预算，
the amount of times they would call me
他们会给我打电话的次数
because of that 10k budget because that
因为那1万美元的预算，因为
was do or die for them. And then when we
对他们来说，这是生死攸关的时刻。然后当我们
signed Uber and Coca-Cola and Samsung,
Uber、可口可乐和三星签署了协议。
the budgets are massive and they they
预算规模庞大，而且他们
call me less.
少给我打电话。
&gt;&gt; They sign things off quicker.
他们签字速度更快。
&gt;&gt; The meetings are easier, life is easier.
会议更轻松了，生活也更轻松了。
And that's just one of these sort of
这只是这类事情中的一个例子。
interesting phenomenons with um with
有趣的现象，嗯，
client services, I guess, and service
我想，还有客户服务和服务
businesses generally is the bigger the
企业规模通常越大
budget, it typically it requires the
预算，通常需要
same or less units of effort to keep
保持相同或更少的努力
them happy than someone whose life is on
他们比那些生活困顿的人更快乐
the line because it's their five grand
因为他们有五千美元，所以才排队。
out of their own pocket.
自掏腰包。
I think part of that you earn too as an
我认为其中一部分也是你作为……所获得的。
entrepreneur. I think I mean I'll speak
企业家。我想我的意思就是我会发言。
for myself. I uh you start out selling
为自己。我呃，你一开始是卖东西的
way too cheap.
太便宜了。
&gt;&gt; Um because you also need the money
嗯，因为你也需要钱。
because as much as it's like a nice it's
因为尽管它很美好，但它
very comfortable for me to say like yeah
对我来说，说“是的”感觉很自在。
you need to add a zero to your price
你需要在价格后面加个零。
tag. If I don't get paid for the rest of
标签。如果我剩下的时间都拿不到工资
my life it doesn't matter.
我的生命无关紧要。
&gt;&gt; And so I have a lot of leverage and
因此，我拥有很大的筹码，
people can feel that. That's really
人们能感受到这一点。那真是
interesting,
有趣的，
&gt;&gt; right? Whereas I mean this is also like
正确的？我的意思是，这也类似于
if you behave as if, right? If I behave
如果你表现得像那样，对吧？如果我表现
as if I have a significant amount of
就好像我拥有大量
money, then I tend to attract people who
如果我有钱，我往往会吸引那些
are going or basically somebody else who
是要去的，或者基本上是其他人要去的
also has a lot of money will recognize
也有很多钱，会得到认可
that behavior and say, "Okay, this guy's
那种行为，然后说：“好吧，这家伙……”
a player." And so then they'll be more
一名球员。” 这样他们就会更多
willing to do business with me. Now,
愿意与我做生意。现在，
it's tougher when you don't have that
如果没有那些东西，那就更难了。
and you present that way, right? Which
你就是这样表现的，对吧？哪个
is so I think that a lot of this kind of
所以我觉得很多这类事情
does become earned because like either
之所以会获得，是因为就像……
you're faking it, which is not my not my
你在装模作样，这跟我没关系。
recommendation, or you just do a decent
建议，或者你只要做得不错就行了。
amount of volume and you realize you're
音量很大，你意识到你是
like, "You know what? can't charge $99 a
比如，“你知道吗？不能收99美元。”
month for this. It doesn't make sense
一个月的时间。这说不通。
for me. And then you have a different
为我。然后你就会有另一种情况
level of confidence going into this
对此的信心程度
where you just look at someone, you're
当你只是看着某人时，你
like, I just can't do it for that price.
这个价格我实在接受不了。
&gt;&gt; That's the word confidence, isn't it?
这就是自信的体现，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, that's how I how
是的。嗯，这就是我的方法
&gt;&gt; does one build that confidence or
一个人如何建立这种自信？
portray that confidence when really they
他们表面上表现出自信，但实际上
don't believe it themselves.
他们自己都不相信。
&gt;&gt; You outwork yourself, right? You do you
你比自己更努力，对吧？你做你自己
do so much volume that um you get bored
做太多事情，以至于你会感到无聊。
of it. Like when you can basically train
它的。比如当你基本上可以训练的时候
out your your affective response or your
表达你的情感反应或你的
emotional response to a given activity,
对特定活动的情绪反应
then at that point I would say like you
那么在那时，我会说就像你一样。
are ready. And so whenever I hear
准备就绪。所以每当我听到
someone, he's like, "How do you get rid
有人会问：“怎么才能摆脱他？”
of nerves?" I was like, "You're just not
紧张吗？我当时就想，“你只是不紧张而已。”
you haven't done it enough times like
你做得还不够多次，比如
until you're bored and you hate it."
直到你感到厌倦，然后开始讨厌它。
&gt;&gt; At that point, I'm like, "Okay, now
那时我就​​想，“好吧，现在……”
you're ready."
你准备好了。
&gt;&gt; Is that what like self-belief is to you?
这就是你眼中的自信吗？
&gt;&gt; To me, yeah.
对我来说，是的。
&gt;&gt; There's two two types of confidence.
自信有两种类型。
There's a confidence that comes from
这是一种源自……的自信
repetition. And I think it takes courage
重复。我认为这需要勇气。
the first 30 times and then you get a
前30次，然后你会得到一个
little bit of confidence and then it
稍微有点自信，然后……
takes courage and then you get
需要勇气，然后你就能
confidence. But I think it's like 30
信心。但我认为大概是30
block little blocks of 30 repetitions
将重复次数分成若干小块，每块30次。
and then you get rewarded with a little
然后你会得到一些奖励
bit of confidence upgrade. That's one
信心略有提升。那是一个
type of confidence. There's another type
自信的类型。还有另一种类型
of confidence which is an abundance of
自信，这是一种充沛的自信
options. So, let's say you run a lead
选项。假设你正在追踪一条线索
generation campaign and you want to get
发起营销活动，你想获得
10 clients and you're hoping to sign up
10位客户，你希望他们签约。
10 clients and a thousand people
10个客户和一千人
respond. You end up with this with or
回应。最后你会得到这样的结果，或者
without you energy. And the with or
没有你的能量。以及与或
without you energy is I'm going to be
没有你，我将失去活力。
fine with or without you. I'm going to
有没有你都无所谓。我要
definitely make my 10 sales. I've got a
肯定能完成10笔销售。我有一个
thousand leads. I've got 10 sales I can
上千条线索。我有10笔销售可以完成。
make. So, therefore, it's out of
制作。所以，因此，它已经出局了。
balance. Mhm.
平衡。嗯。
&gt;&gt; I I go back and forth on this because
我在这件事上犹豫不决，因为
the good thing about today actually is I
今天的好处其实是……
think people do less than ever but think
认为人们比以往任何时候都做得更少，但认为
that they do more than ever in
他们比以往任何时候都做得更多
entrepreneurship. And so we have a lot
创业精神。所以，我们有很多
of mental masturbation that goes on.
持续不断的精神自慰。
I've thought about this a lot. I've
我仔细考虑过这个问题。我已经
really pondered it. I've wondered about
我真的认真考虑过了。我一直很疑惑……
this. I've worried about it, etc. Right?
这。我一直很担心这件事，等等。对吧？
I've watched all these videos. I've
这些视频我都看过了。我已经
consumed all this stuff, but I've
这些东西我都吃光了，但我
actually done nothing.
实际上什么也没做。
&gt;&gt; Keep watching the videos.
请继续观看视频。
&gt;&gt; Like and subscribe.
点赞并订阅。
But you know I if if if I if you take
但你知道，如果如果如果如果我如果你接受
the quantity advice then what you do
数量建议，然后你做什么
when you try to go get a job let's say
当你尝试去找工作的时候，比如说
whether it's it's a job uh that that you
不管这是一份工作，呃，就是你
have in your business or you're trying
你的企业里有吗？或者你正在尝试
to get an actual job then you just go
要想找到一份真正的工作，你就得这么做。
and you apply to 15,000 of them. I
你向其中 15,000 家公司投递了简历。我
actually think you'd be much better off
实际上，我认为你会过得更好。
by applying to five and doing as much
通过申请五个职位并尽可能多地完成
work as it would take to reach out to
像需要联系对方那样努力
15,000 to obsess on those five. And so
15000 美元，用来痴迷于那五个人。所以
even if you haven't done 10,000 hours of
即使你还没有完成 10,000 小时的……
painting uh somebody's house, if you go
给别人家粉刷房子，如果你去的话
and sit down and you sit down with uh
然后坐下，你和呃一起坐下
AI, get in front of Perplexity and you
AI，领先于Perplexity，你
write down, okay, what is the average
写下来，好的，平均值是多少
painting job cost? What are the problems
油漆工程费用是多少？存在哪些问题
that come up with painting jobs? Uh who
那些提供油漆工作的人？呃，谁
are who is the most expensive? Um how do
谁的身价最高？嗯，怎么做？
I upsell them? And you put together a
我向他们推销升级产品吗？然后你把……
package that is like here is everything
包裹里的东西都在这里。
that you think you need to know
你认为你需要知道
data-wise on this job that I want. Like
从数据上看，我非常希望得到这份工作。喜欢
you will be the 1%. Nobody preps for
你将成为那1%。没有人为此做准备
anything anymore to the degree that you
再也没有其他任何事了，以至于你
need to execute. And so I don't think
需要执行。所以我觉得……
you always have to do the job if you do
如果你这么做，你就必须完成这项工作。
the preparation to show that you care
做好准备，以表达你的关心
about the job. And just think about it
关于这份工作。仔细想想。
like how many times have we all had
比如，我们都经历过多少次这样的情况？
people reach out to us and they're like,
人们联系我们，他们会说：
I want to come work for you or I want to
我想来为你工作，或者我想
come get this job and they're like, hey,
来应聘这份工作，他们会说，嘿，
can I send you a video of XYZ and if I
我可以给你发一段XYZ的视频吗？如果我
do it then then you'll hire me or can I
那就这么做，然后你就会雇用我，或者我可以吗？
do a sales pitch for you? You know what
帮你做个销售推介？你知道吗
you should actually do? Make the video.
你真的应该这样做吗？制作视频。
Make the video. Put together an entire
制作视频。把整个
prep document. Put together a strategy
准备文件。制定策略
document on why I should hire you. And
一份说明我为什么应该聘用你的文件。和
make it so that it is almost impossible
使其几乎不可能实现
for somebody to say no to you because it
有人因为这个原因对你说不
shows how obsessed you are in a world of
这显示了你对这个世界的痴迷程度
super curious, uninterested, not that
超级好奇，没兴趣，不是那种
deep obsession. And I've hired God, I
深深的痴迷。我已经聘请了上帝，我
probably hired 15, 20 people solely
可能只雇佣了15到20人。
because obsession is rare and competence
因为痴迷是罕见的，而能力是罕见的。
is rare. And if you can show those two
很少见。如果你能展示那两个……
things, you can be people who have been
事情，你可以成为曾经是的人
doing it for 20 years. Because I know
做了20年。因为我知道
many painters. We we own one of the
许多画家。我们拥有其中之一
bigger painting franchises in the
规模更大的绘画特许经营权
country and I know very many painters
国家，我认识很多画家
that have all the experience but they
他们拥有所有经验，但他们
don't know how to properly communicate
不知道如何正确沟通
it and show the preparation that they've
它展现了他们所做的准备。
already done.
已经完成了。
&gt;&gt; Let's talk about that because that's a a
我们来谈谈这件事，因为那是一个……
function of really sales. I guess that's
真正实现销售的功能。我想那就是
sales that's marketing. Um, I was
销售就是营销。嗯，我当时
mulling the other day because I've I've
前几天一直在想这件事，因为我一直……
just hired someone called Harry who's
刚雇了个叫哈里的人，他
our new head of happiness in our in
我们新任幸福主管
Flight Story. And she and she didn't
飞行故事。她没有
just make a seven-minute video. She also
只需制作一个七分钟的视频。她也
sent the video via unsaturated, less
通过不饱和度较低的方式发送视频
noisy channels. And it made me think
嘈杂的频道。这让我想到
about this framework of the resonance of
关于这种共振框架
the message and the high signalness of
信息及其高信号强度
the medium
媒介
&gt;&gt; because as you all know, you're getting
因为你们都知道，你们正在得到
DMs from people that say, "Any jobs
收到一些私信，对方说：“有工作机会吗？”
going?" that's like low emotional
“去吗？”这就像情绪低落一样。
resonance and a terrible medium. So I
共鸣和糟糕的媒介。所以，我
think of it as like this four sort of um
你可以把它想象成这四种……嗯
square quadrant where in the top right
正方形象限，其中右上角
of the quadrant you have message the
您在象限中已发送消息
7-inute video but then figuring out how
7分钟视频，但后来弄清楚如何
to get it round back past the PAS not
绕回PAS那里，而不是
into the saturated inboxes maybe into
或许会进入饱和的收件箱
the post. I think post is so like
帖子。我觉得帖子就像
unbelievably unappreciated as a medium
作为一种媒介，它竟然没有得到应有的重视，真是令人难以置信。
in a world of like laziness where nobody
在一个充斥着懒惰的世界里，没有人
wants to like go to the post box. you
想去邮筒取信。你
you're all on the receiving ends of
你们都是受害者
thousands of DMs and messages a month
每月数千条私信和消息
and sometimes some of them get through.
有时其中一些会成功。
Sometimes some of them result in someone
有时候，其中一些会导致某人
being offered a job or you investing in
获得工作机会或进行投资
their company. So if I'm listening at
他们的公司。所以如果我正在听……
home and I'm thinking, okay, I've got
回到家，我在想，好吧，我拥有
four people here who get thousands of
这里有四个人，他们获得了数千美元
DMs. What is the secret that penetrates
私信。究竟是什么秘密能够渗透人心？
your your fortresses?
你的堡垒？
&gt;&gt; I would be careful reaching out to
我联系对方时会很谨慎。
people who get who have millions of
那些拥有数百万美元的人
followers because it's hard for you if
关注者，因为这对你来说很难
you've never had millions of followers
你从来没有过数百万粉丝。
um or even hundreds of thousands of
嗯，甚至成千上万的
followers. It's it would blow most
粉丝。这会彻底摧毁大多数人
people's minds just how much traffic is
人们都在想，到底有多少人开车？
moving on in the background on any given
在任何给定情况下，后台都在继续推进
day. There are plenty of people who have
天。有很多人拥有
10,000 followers or 20,000 followers or
10,000 个粉丝或 20,000 个粉丝或
they've got a very successful business.
他们的生意非常成功。
They don't get a,000 emails a day. They
他们一天不会收到一千封电子邮件。他们
get maybe a thousand emails a year. So
一年大概会收到一千封邮件。所以
there's a there's something that you can
有件事你可以……
reach out with which is called a proof
用一种叫做证明的方式进行沟通
story which you mentioned. And the
你提到的那个故事。以及
format that I like to use is I did
我喜欢使用的格式是“我做了”。
something special. I recently worked
特别的东西。我最近工作过
with a extremely famous uh YouTuber
与一位极其著名的YouTube用户
&gt;&gt; um who has over 22 million followers
嗯，他拥有超过2200万粉丝
&gt;&gt; and we were able to spin out a new
我们得以衍生出一家新公司
business
商业
&gt;&gt; um which became very very successful and
嗯，结果非常非常成功，
exitable
可退出
&gt;&gt; um and that business uh got you know 10
嗯，那家公司……你知道，有10家。
million worth of revenue in the first
第一年收入达数百万美元
six months uh and I project managed the
六个月，我负责项目管理。
whole thing and I can explain exactly
整件事，我可以详细解释。
how we did that step by step. So that
我们是一步一步做到的。以便
the format is I did something special
格式是：我做了一件特别的事
with a certain type of person. We got a
与某种类型的人相处。我们得到了一个
great result. Here's what the result was
结果非常好。结果如下：
and here's how I can explain it step by
以下是我逐步解释的方法
step.
步。
&gt;&gt; And what's in that for me or am I making
那对我来说有什么好处？或者说，我到底在做什么？
the the link?
链接是什么？
&gt;&gt; So I'm reaching out to you with my proof
所以我联系你，并附上我的证据。
story. Yeah.
故事。是的。
&gt;&gt; So I'm telling you this is this is what
所以我告诉你，这就是……
I've done
我已经做过了
&gt;&gt; and are you asking me for something?
你这是要我帮你什么忙吗？
&gt;&gt; I'm saying would you like to know how we
我是说，你想知道我们如何
did it step by step? Now the other way
是按步骤做的吗？现在反过来
we can do this that works pretty well is
我们可以这样做，效果相当不错。
to do this in the public domain. So, for
在公共领域进行这项工作。所以，对于
example, you could reach out by actually
例如，你可以通过实际方式联系。
posting a video or a or a post on
发布视频或帖子
LinkedIn or on Instagram or um or on uh
LinkedIn 或 Instagram 或 嗯 或 呃
X. And what you can do is have five,
X. 你可以做的就是拥有五个，
six, seven, eight friends who then jump
六个、七个、八个朋友然后跳起来
in and start commenting on it. Now, for
登录并开始评论。现在，为了
me personally, if you've tagged me in
就我个人而言，如果你在帖子中标记了我
something in the public domain and
公共领域的事物
people are now commenting it, so that
现在有人在评论这件事，所以
the the the the thing might be I've got
事情可能是我有
a little bit of advice for Daniel
给丹尼尔一点建议
Priestley
普里斯特利
&gt;&gt; and I go, oo, what's going on here?
我心想，哦，这是怎么回事？
Right? And then I see that there's a
正确的？然后我看到那里有一个
public video and I see several people
公开视频，我看到好几个人
commenting on it. And then I look at the
评论一下。然后我看了看
video and it's a proof story and it's
视频就是一个证据，而且这是一个证明故事，它是
really complimentary. I really like your
真是赞美。我真的很喜欢你
stuff and here's what here's going and
东西，还有接下来要发生的事……
here's the here's my proof story. And by
这就是我的证据。并且通过
the way, Daniel, I'd love to get in
丹尼尔，我真想进去。
touch. Drop me a DM. I'm I'm going to
触碰。给我发私信。我打算
check that out because it's in the
查一下，因为它在……
public domain
公共领域
&gt;&gt; because
因为
&gt;&gt; well because it could be negative. It
因为结果可能是负面的。它
could be
可能是
&gt;&gt; like I don't know.
我不知道。
&gt;&gt; I want to know what the heck's what
我想知道这到底是怎么回事。
what's being said there, right? I I
那里面在说什么呢？我 我
think the real thing is don't confuse
认为真正重要的是不要混淆
famous with rich. Like you guys
因富有而闻名。就像你们一样
shouldn't care about us and reaching out
不应该在意我们，也不应该主动联系我们
to us. There are people that are richer
对我们来说。有些人比我富有。
than all of us even though we all have
比我们所有人都要多，尽管我们都有
some means as far as I understand. There
据我所知，这有一些方法。那里
are people that are way richer than us
他们是比我们富有得多的人。
that nobody knows that nobody's reaching
没人知道，也没人能触及到
out to that want to give you their
那些想给你他们的
money. And so I think a lot of people
钱。所以我觉得很多人都
spend time focusing on fame as opposed
把时间花在追求名利上，而不是
to rich. And when you're young, who
富有。当你年轻的时候，谁
cares? Like you can't eat fame. Fame is
关心吗？名气又不能当饭吃。名声是
not lasting. We will all be totally
不持久。我们都会完全
irrelevant probably sooner than we even
无关紧要的事情可能比我们想象的还要早。
want to
想要
&gt;&gt; speak for some
代表某些人发言
&gt;&gt; like and subscribe.
点赞并订阅。
&gt;&gt; Alex will be remembered in 500.
500年后，人们会记住亚历克斯。
&gt;&gt; So like it, you know, for young people,
所以，你知道，年轻人会喜欢它。
I do think sometimes uh because we get
我确实觉得有时候会这样，因为我们会……
DMs, we think that it's important, but
我们认为私信很重要，但是
if you're watching this, you should
如果你正在看这个视频，你应该
really be obsessed with just making
真的痴迷于制作
money and then you can be sitting at a
有了钱，你就可以坐在……
table like this and not worry about, you
像这样的表格就不用担心了，你
know, slipping into our DMs. I mean, the
我知道，他们会偷偷给我们发私信。我的意思是，
richest guy that you know probably
你认识的最富有的人可能是
started a sprinkler head company, lives
创办了一家洒水喷头公司，现居
down your street in a big house, and if
你家街对面有一栋大房子，如果
you went and asked knocked on his door
你去敲了他的门，问他怎么回事。
and asked him how he made it, and if you
然后问他是怎么做到的，以及如果你
could do a service for him, he would
如果他能为他做点什么，他会
probably let you.
或许会允许你这么做。
&gt;&gt; So true.
如此真实。
&gt;&gt; I wouldn't mess around with famous
我不会招惹名人。
people.
人们。
&gt;&gt; The people that gave me my first leg up
那些帮助我迈出第一步的人
in the world of business were no one.
在商界，没有人。
They didn't have followers.
他们没有追随者。
&gt;&gt; They were some guy who had built a
他们是某个建造了……的人
business similar in the city and was now
城市里也有类似的企业，现在也是如此。
living out in Monaco, living an isolated
住在摩纳哥，过着与世隔绝的生活
life. It was someone who'd sold some
生活。是有人卖掉了一些东西
kind of company was running uh you know
你知道，那家公司当时在运营某种类型的业务。
some kind of marketing business but and
某种营销业务，但是
they were at that level. They were
他们当时的水平就是那样。他们是
probably at the $50 million level in
可能在 5000 万美元的水平
terms of net worth and they were
就净资产而言，他们是
delighted to have an email from me
很高兴收到我的邮件
tickling their ego
满足他们的虚荣心
&gt;&gt; of course
当然
&gt;&gt; and saying that I was reading their blog
并说我在阅读他们的博客
etc.
ETC。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; It's very exhausting to do the very deep
做非常深入的工作非常累人。
level of work that you do in order to
你为了达到以下目的而付出的工作量
get a high level client and then have no
获得一个高级客户，然后就没有了
response. Right. That can be that can be
回复。正确的。那可能是，那可能是
really you know extinguishing from a
真的，你知道，熄灭……
behavior perspective. But if you do that
行为视角。但如果你那样做的话
work for, you know, Steven Bartlett and
为史蒂文·巴特利特工作，你知道的
then you make the post and you say,
然后你发帖说：
"Hey, this is this like I'm a XYZ, you
“嘿，这就像我是XYZ，你
know, whatever designer and I've worked
我知道，无论哪个设计师，我都和他合作过。
with these types of clients and let me
与这类客户打交道，让我
just show you my breakdown of what I
我只需向你展示一下我的分解图即可。
would do. I think his stuff's awesome.
可以。我觉得他的作品很棒。
This is just some stuff I would do." And
这只是我会做的一些事情。
then I tag you, then I'll probably like
然后我标记你，然后我可能就会点赞。
things is enough people will see that
事情已经足够了，人们会明白的。
that you'll get it sent to you from
你会收到它。
somebody else who you will answer the
你会回答其他人的问题
response from messenger messaging type
来自即时通讯软件的回复
perspective. like somebody whose DMs you
看法。就像有人给你发私信一样
will open will be like, "Hey, I don't
打开后会像这样：“嘿，我没有
know if you saw this
知道你是否看过这个
&gt;&gt; team member."
队员。”
&gt;&gt; Right. Exactly. Um and you do respond to
正确的。确切地。嗯，你确实会回应
them.
他们。
&gt;&gt; I do. Yeah.
我愿意。是的。
&gt;&gt; And so all of a sudden it's like that's
所以突然之间，就好像……
actually how you can get in, but you
实际上，你可以通过某种方式进入，但是你
also get all the free exposure of the
同时还能获得所有免费的曝光机会
work that you're doing. And then another
你正在做的工作。然后又一个
person who might not be you and it might
这个人可能不是你，而且可能
be me and saying, "Hey, I like Stephen
让我说：“嘿，我喜欢斯蒂芬。”
stuff too and I thought this was a
还有其他东西，我以为这是
pretty good breakdown. Um hey, do you
分析得相当不错。嗯，嘿，你
have services?" Uh you know, in exchange
提供服务吗？呃，你知道，作为交换
for money.
为了钱。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I'm I'm nab that [__] Um, and so
是的。我一定要搞到手。嗯，所以
and so yeah, I actually actually really
所以，是的，我其实真的很
like that perspective because it doubles
喜欢这种视角，因为它能带来双重体验。
it allows the work that you do for your
它允许你为你所做的工作
lead magnets to basically double as
引流工具基本上可以兼作
content and so doubles as promotion. And
内容兼具宣传作用。和
so you get you kind of get multiple
所以你会得到多个
bites of the app, which I think is
应用的部分功能，我认为这是
really uh good.
真的很好。
&gt;&gt; And I think if you do do it though, be
而且我觉得，如果你真的要这么做，那就……
sure you're good because
你肯定没问题，因为
&gt;&gt; because you know the truth of this
因为你知道这件事的真相。
happens all the time with you and I. I
这种情况在你我之间经常发生。
mean there we go back and forth because
这意味着我们要来回折腾，因为
people will say online like, I built
人们会在网上说，我建造了
everything that Alex Formoszi owns. Can
Alex Formoszi 的所有财产。能
I come work for you, Cody? Yeah, you
科迪，我来为你工作吗？是的，你
know, I received those emails, too. I
我知道，我也收到了那些邮件。我
built
建造
&gt;&gt; He'll have this. He has the same people.
他会得到这个。他的人脉还是那些人。
You know, I built everything Cody has.
你知道吗，科迪拥有的一切都是我一手打造的。
How? And then, you know, kind of
如何？然后，你知道，有点像
funnily, I'll be like, "God, I don't
有趣的是，我会想，“天哪，我没有
remember that person ever working for
还记得那个曾经为……工作过的人吗？
me." Like, did
我。” 就像，真的吗？
&gt;&gt; did this actually happen? And so, I do
这事真的发生过吗？所以，我这么做了。
think this is just a little listen, you
听着，你觉得这只是个小小的听听而已吗？
got to hustle when you're young. You got
年轻的时候就得拼命努力。你得到了
to do things you're going to cringe
去做那些让你感到尴尬的事情
about later. I am so on board for all of
稍后再说。我完全赞同所有这些观点。
that. But also remember that the world
那。但也要记住，世界
is small, especially with people. pause
小，尤其是有人的时候。暂停
on that cuz I think this is an important
之所以这么说，是因为我认为这很重要。
point is all the people that have had
重点是所有曾经拥有过的人
the biggest net impact on my success, my
对我的成功影响最大的净因素，是我的
career in my team, they don't they don't
在我的团队里，他们不会，他们不会。
seem to have time to be telling the
似乎有时间讲述
world that they did everything.
世界认为他们做了一切。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; I mean, Jack is a good example. Jack is
我的意思是，杰克就是一个很好的例子。杰克是
Jack was here from episode one of the
杰克从第一集就在这里了。
podcast, but Jack in my view is doing
播客，但在我看来，杰克正在做
the like least personal branding,
最不擅长个人品牌建设
milking the cow, and he's in my view
他正在挤牛奶，在我看来，他就在那儿。
arguably the most responsible
可以说是最负责任的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; for all of this stuff. And there's
所有这些事情。还有……
almost this inverse correlation between
几乎这种反相关性
someone that works for you for three
为你工作了三年的人
months and then builds a personal brand
几个月后，再打造个人品牌
off the back of that
在此基础上
&gt;&gt; and is on stage claiming, you know, the
他在台上声称，你知道，
success versus the people in the in the
成功与身处其中的人们之间的对比
trenches
战壕
&gt;&gt; in the circle. Yeah,
在圆圈里。是的，
&gt;&gt; it's a it's a bit of a side point, but
这有点跑题了，但是……
um one of the things people are so
嗯，人们如此关注的事情之一
fascinated by is this idea of passive
被动的这种想法令人着迷。
income.
收入。
&gt;&gt; And I think I think they're fascinated
我觉得他们很着迷。
by it because it's a promise of big
之所以选择它，是因为它预示着巨大的未来。
returns for no work. And that's you talk
无所事事的退货。那就是你的谈话了。
about offers a lot. That's like the
关于提供很多服务。那就像……
perfect offer.
完美报价。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
What what's your what's your thoughts on
你对……有什么看法？
passive income, Alex, and is it
被动收入，亚历克斯，是这样吗？
something we should be aspiring for?
这是我们应该追求的目标吗？
&gt;&gt; So, um, first I think it'd be helpful
所以，嗯，首先我认为这会有帮助。
for everyone to even define in terms of
让每个人都能从这个角度来定义
how to think about passive income versus
如何看待被动收入与被动收入的比较
active income. So, one is that people
主动收入。所以，第一点是人们
often discuss it in binary terms,
通常用二元论的方式来讨论它，
passive versus actum, when it's really
被动语态与主动语态，当它真正
more of a continuum of how passive is it
更像是一个被动程度的连续体。
versus how active is it? And that way it
与它的活跃程度相比如何？那样的话……
becomes way less black and white. When I
变得不再那么黑白分明。当我
think about passive versus active, um,
想想被动和主动的区别，嗯，
when people are starting out, I
当人们刚开始的时候，我
generally just discard it entirely
通常直接丢弃。
because they typically don't have
因为他们通常没有
sufficient capital in order to actually
足够的资金才能真正
make meaningful passive income and they
创造有意义的被动收入，而且他们
would get significantly higher returns
将会获得更高的回报
on increasing their active income. And
提高他们的主动收入。和
virtually every extremely rich person
几乎所有超级富豪
who self-made as my asterisk generally
我自力更生，就像我的星号一样
has gigantic active income and only
拥有巨额活跃收入，而且只有
begins to look at passive when they have
当他们开始关注被动行为时，他们拥有
so much money from reinvesting in their
他们将大量资金再投资于此。
higher return things, which is what got
高回报的东西，这就是我们得到的
them this very large active income that
他们获得了非常可观的主动收入。
they're like, where else should I put
他们会想，我还能放在哪里呢？
it? And then at that point it's really a
它？然后到了那个时候，它就真的变成了
question of diversification which is
多元化问题，即
like how much more do I not want to
我到底还有多少不想再经历一次？
double down on the main thing and that's
把精力集中在最重要的事情上，那就是
a completely personal question and I
这是一个完全私人的问题，我
don't there is no in my opinion there's
不，在我看来，没有。
no right answer to that um of because
这个问题没有正确答案，因为……
that's a fundamental like how much risk
这是个基本问题，比如风险有多大。
do I want to take um which I see is
我要不要拿一下？我看到的是
entirely personal but I'll give you a
这完全是个人私事，但我会告诉你
very a real example of like an
一个非常真实的例子，就像……
investment I made you know 5 years ago
你知道，我五年前做的一笔投资
which was um we did ex exited the
那就是，嗯，我们确实退出了。
business um and I had more time on my
生意嘛，嗯，我有更多的时间在我的……
hands and I was like okay well why don't
我双手合十，心想好吧，为什么不呢？
I just start spending you a couple
我刚开始花你几个
million bucks a year on making content.
每年花一百万美元制作内容。
Now, that had basically zero return in
现在，这样做基本上没有任何回报。
that time period, but if I were to look
那段时期，但如果我去看……
at the return on capital for that, you
就资本回报率而言，你
know, $2 million a year I did for the
我知道，我每年为……赚了200万美元。
first few years compared to today was
与今天相比，最初几年是
probably the highest return capital that
可能是回报率最高的资本。
I made. But is that was that a passive?
我做的。但那是被动语态吗？
No, it's definitely not passive. It was
不，它绝对不是被动的。那是
100% active in from an investing
100% 积极参与投资
perspective. And so, this is when people
看法。所以，这就是人们
are like, what do you mean by investing
就像，你说的投资是什么意思？
yourself? I mean that right like you're
你自己？我的意思是，就像你一样
investing in either the skills that
投资于以下技能：
you're acquiring the businesses that
您正在收购以下企业：
that you have and a very simple
你所拥有的，以及一个非常简单的
investment a lot of times uh can get you
投资很多时候可以让你……
ideally leverage on your time and so I
理想情况下，要充分利用你的时间，所以我
would rather think for the person who's
宁愿替那个人想事情
starting out not like how do I make this
一开始并不是像这样：我该怎么做？
passive I would say how do I get more
被动地，我会说我如何获得更多
leverage on my active and so like I
利用我的活跃度，就像我
could start by shoveling snow in the
可以从铲雪开始
beginning and then once I save up enough
先开始，然后等我攒够钱之后再开始。
of my shekels then I'll buy a snow
然后我用我的谢克尔买一箱雪
blower and all of a sudden I can go from
鼓风机突然间，我就可以……
doing you know one driveway an hour to
你知道吗，一个车道一小时
doing three driveways an hour and then
每小时修三个车道，然后
boom I tripled my income. Now, for that
哇！我的收入翻了三倍。现在，为了这个
one week that my cash flow is down
有一周我的现金流下降了
because I had to buy the equipment, I'll
因为我必须购买设备，所以我将
I'll have made less money, but then I'll
我挣的钱会少一些，但是之后我会
very quickly recoup it. Now, to the same
很快就能恢复过来。现在，到同样的地方
degree, that's in a capital expense from
学位，这属于资本支出
an equipment perspective, but you can do
从设备角度来看，但你可以这样做
the same thing from a skills perspective
从技能角度来看也是如此。
of I give a classic example of a
我举一个经典的例子
phabotamist as somebody who draws blood.
抽血师是指抽血的人。
Um, in the US, I think they make
嗯，在美国，我想他们会生产
somewhere in the neighbor of like $25 an
大概在25美元左右
hour or something like that. It doesn't
大约一个小时左右。它不
take very long in order to become a
需要很长时间才能成为一名
phabotamist and it doesn't take a lot of
phabotamist，而且不需要很多
money. And so, you know, a couple weeks
钱。所以，你知道，大概两周吧。
you do the studies, you get your cert,
你完成学习，就能拿到证书。
and then all of a sudden you take
然后突然之间，你就……
minimum wage and as long as you're not
最低工资，只要你不是
in San Francisco, you will have double
在旧金山，你将拥有双倍的
or tripled your earning capacity in just
或者在短短时间内将你的收入能力提高三倍
a very short period of time. And so,
很短的一段时间。所以，
that's a very good return on capital.
这是非常可观的资本回报率。
And so, that's where I think about the
所以，这就是我思考这个问题的地方。
best investments for people who are
最适合以下人群的投资
starting out who have call it sub
一开始，他们称之为子版块
$10,000, sub maybe $25,000. It's like I
10,000美元，可能要25,000美元。就像我
put all my money into how I get more
我把所有的钱都投入到如何获得更多收益的研究中。
leverage on my active, which is either
利用我的主动资产，即
going to be more skills or or more
会有更多的技能或其他方面
actual physical equipment in order to
实际的物理设备
get returns on the skills I already
利用我已有的技能获得回报
have.
有。
&gt;&gt; Interesting. more leverage on my time.
有趣的。更好地掌控我的时间。
&gt;&gt; I I personally like the idea of asset
我个人很喜欢资产这个概念。
income versus passive income. So if you
收入与被动收入。所以如果你
actually look at what's really going on
真正看看发生了什么
with passive income, it's that there is
被动收入的特点在于……
a an asset and that asset is in some way
一项资产，并且该资产在某种程度上是
generating income. So for example, you
创造收入。例如，你
own a house and you get rental income or
拥有一套房子，然后获得租金收入
you write a book and you've got
你写了一本书，然后你就有了
intellectual property and that
知识产权以及
intellectual property generates a
知识产权产生
royalty income. So first there's an
版税收入。首先，有一个
asset. Income follows assets. So the
资产。收入与资产成正比。所以
first thing you need is an asset and
你首先需要的是一项资产，
then you get the yield from the asset.
然后你就能获得该资产的收益。
And there's traditional assets which are
还有一些传统资产，它们是
very very good if you've already made
如果你已经做过的话，那就非常好了。
money or you already have money and you
有钱，或者你已经有钱了，而且你
want to park it somewhere and you want
你想把它停在某个地方，而且你想
to stay ahead of inflation.
为了抵御通货膨胀。
&gt;&gt; Traditional assets are terrible for
传统资产对……来说很糟糕
trying to make money.
想赚钱。
&gt;&gt; Give me an example of a traditional
请举一个传统的例子
asset in this definition.
本定义中的资产。
&gt;&gt; Um I think of something like art, wine
嗯，我想到了艺术、葡萄酒之类的东西。
and watches as more like a speculation
更像是在进行某种推测。
but or or perhaps a store of value. But
但是，或者，也许是一种价值储存手段。但
then there's something else which is
然后还有另一件事，那就是
called a performance asset. And a
被称为绩效资产。以及
performance asset is typically
绩效资产通常是
intellectual property, media, code, or
知识产权、媒体、代码或
data. And when you have these
数据。当你拥有这些的时候
performance assets, if you can build
如果你能构建性能资产，就能建立
these, these are ones you don't have to
这些，这些是你不必……
buy, you build them. So, for example,
买下来，自己建造。例如，
you could write a book, and now you've
你可以写一本书，而现在你已经
got intellectual property. You could
拥有知识产权。你可以
build a system like a a SAS platform.
构建类似 SAS 平台的系统。
Uh, and now that SAS platform is in some
呃，现在SAS平台已经在某些方面有所改进。
way an asset, and you can rent that out
这是一种资产，你可以把它出租。
to to more people. uh you could build a
让更多人受益。呃，你可以建造一个
database of a thousand people and build
包含一千人的数据库并构建
a relationship with those thousand
与那一千人的关系
people and then every time you write one
人们，然后每次你写一个
email it goes out to a thousand people
邮件会发送给一千人。
and they've got a little newsletter. So
他们还有一份简短的电子报。所以
that's a performance asset. So typically
这是一项绩效资产。所以通常
when you look at um the people around
当你观察周围的人时
this table we're actually got we we're
这张桌子我们实际上有
very lucky to have a lot of performance
非常幸运能有这么多演出机会
assets big followings uh lots of media
资产、大量粉丝、大量媒体
and content um books that we've written.
以及我们撰写的书籍的内容。
So these are kind of like the
所以这些有点像……
performance assets that anyone can
任何人都能获得的绩效资产
create. It used to be until very very
创造。过去一直如此，直到非常非常
recently that you just couldn't build
最近你就是建不起来。
assets like you couldn't. It was very
你无法拥有这样的资产。非常
very difficult. But we live in this
非常困难。但我们生活在这样的世界里。
magical moment where almost anyone with
神奇的时刻，几乎每个人都能感受到
a phone and a laptop can start creating
一部手机和一台笔记本电脑就可以开始创作
performance assets with intellectual
具有知识产权的绩效资产
property, media, data, and code. And uh
属性、媒体、数据和代码。呃
and then you can basically start the
然后你基本上就可以开始了
process of building those assets and and
构建这些资产的过程以及
then those assets produce more income.
那么这些资产就能产生更多收入。
&gt;&gt; Here's my conspiracy theory about
这是我对这件事的阴谋论。
passive income. And uh I think that
被动收入。嗯，我觉得
passive income, it's a tax code, right?
被动收入，这是税法里的一种说法，对吧？
It is a real thing. It exists. You pay
这是真的。它存在。你付钱
less money to the government if you have
如果你有……，政府收到的钱就会少一些。
passive income than active income. Like
被动收入比主动收入更重要。喜欢
that's where the word comes from. But I
这个词就是从那里来的。但我
think the reason that it's been so
我认为造成这种情况的原因在于……
idealized is because there's an entire
理想化是因为存在一个完整的
industry where people have told all of
在这个行业里，人们已经倾诉了一切
us for decades that they are better at
几十年来，我们一直认为他们更擅长……
managing our money than we are. That's
我们比现在更懂得如何管理金钱。那是
the mutual fund industry, that's the
共同基金行业，那就是
investment industry, that's the real
投资行业，那才是真正的投资行业。
estate industry, that's the private
房地产行业，也就是私人房地产行业
equity industry. and they have said we
股权行业。他们说我们
are uh professionals and thus we will
我们是专业人士，因此我们将
charge you 2 and 20. We'll charge you uh
我们会收你2块20块钱。我们会收你……呃
an investment fee on top of your assets
除了您的资产之外，还要支付一笔投资费用。
for you to give us the professionals
请您给我们提供专业人员
your money to beat inflation over time.
让你的钱随着时间的推移跑赢通货膨胀。
The problem is is that to your point
问题就在于，正如你所说。
they will never make you wealthy.
它们永远不会让你变得富有。
Investing overtime in those assets are
长期投资这些资产是
are great for beating inflation or
非常适合对抗通货膨胀或
making sure you have downside protection
确保您有下行保护
for your cash over time in order to
随着时间的推移，你的现金会越来越多，以便……
allow it to grow and have
让它生长并拥有
diversification. But they're very bad if
多样化。但如果
you want to get rich. If you want to get
你想致富。如果你想得到
rich, you're not going to get rich in
富有，你不会通过这种方式致富。
mutual funds and sitting it in somebody
共同基金，然后把它放在某人那里。
else's private equity fund. The people
其他人的私募股权基金。人民
who get rich off those things, they do
那些靠这些东西发财的人，他们确实如此。
the active income. They're the ones who
主动收入。他们是那些
are running the private equity fund.
负责管理私募股权基金。
They're the ones that are running the
他们才是真正掌权的人。
private equity companies and they're the
私募股权公司，它们是
ones that are running the real estate.
那些经营房地产的人。
And so there's this fascinating world we
所以，我们生活在一个如此迷人的世界里。
live in actually where people think that
实际上，人们认为生活在这样的地方
it is better and more sophisticated to
它更好、更先进
not teach you how to become capable of
不教你如何变得有能力
running your own business and creating
经营自己的企业并创造
active income, but that instead uh
主动收入，但却是……
you're more sophisticated if you're on
如果你在……，你就更老练。
Wall Street. And and so I think that
华尔街。所以我认为
passive income was actually in a lot of
被动收入实际上存在于很多方面
ways a way for the wealthy class to gain
富裕阶层获取利益的途径
a lot of our assets.
我们的很多资产。
&gt;&gt; But people click it. And this is why
但人们还是会点击它。这就是原因
there's a generation of younger people
有一代年轻一代
as well that are obsessed with trying to
以及那些痴迷于尝试……的人
figure out how to make passive income.
想办法创造被动收入。
It's it's it's clickbait, isn't it?
这是标题党，对吧？
&gt;&gt; I think it's forex trading,
我认为这是外汇交易。
&gt;&gt; but I think it's almost deeper than
但我认为它几乎比这更深。
that. I think it is actually that um it
那。我觉得实际上是……
sounds, you know, if Alex says this, I
听起来，你知道，如果亚历克斯这么说，我
say it too, but like invest in yourself.
也要这样说，但要像投资自己一样。
People are like, "What does that mean?
人们会问：“那是什么意思？”
What do of course I'm trying to but how
我当然想这么做，但是该怎么做呢？
do I invest in myself? That's hard. I
我是否应该投资自己？那很难。我
don't know exactly how to do it. What
不知道具体该怎么做。什么
are you trying to sell me courses or
你是不是想向我推销课程？
tell me to buy your books or whatever?"
“告诉我该买你的书还是别的什么？”
And that's the the reaction. But the
这就是反应。但是
truth of the matter is is that you will
事实是，你会
never be able to have the return on
永远无法获得回报
investment in somebody else's asset that
投资于他人的资产
you will in yourself. You just won't.
你会在自己身上看到这一点。你就是不会。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, let's go on to that then.
好的。那么，我们就继续讨论这个问题吧。
Investing in yourself.
投资自己。
If you were starting out in your career
如果你刚开始职业生涯
today without the skills that you have,
今天，如果没有你拥有的技能，
without the audience that you have, and
如果没有你现在拥有的观众，而且
you had to choose how to invest in
你必须选择如何投资
yourself, what is that investment you
你自己，你那项投资是什么？
would make in yourself today in 2025?
你会如何规划2025年的自己？
&gt;&gt; I'm going to give two answers. So um so
我将给出两个答案。所以，嗯，所以
I started at zero once and then I've
我曾经从零开始，然后我……
lost everything twice. And so I have the
两次失去一切。所以我有了
I have done that three times now. Um
我已经这样做了三次了。嗯
starting from zero without a reputation
从零开始，没有声誉
um or money. And so um what I did in all
嗯，或者钱。所以，嗯，我所做的一切
three times was the same thing which was
三次都是一样的，那就是
the first thing I did was I learned how
我做的第一件事就是学习如何
to advertise which is how to let people
做广告，也就是让人们知道该怎么做。
know about the stuff I have. The second
了解我拥有的东西。第二
thing I did was that I went to people
我做的就是去找人。
who had an existing business and I said,
他已经有了自己的生意，我说，
"Hey, for as little as little money as
“嘿，只要花很少的钱……”
possible, what would you do to fulfill
如果可能，你会怎么做来实现这个目标
your existing services
您现有的服务
and then when someone uh I would then
然后当有人……呃，我会……
use the advertising that I had, so at
利用我已有的广告资源，所以
the time it was Facebook ads. Um, I
当时是Facebook广告。嗯，我
would run ads and then I would sell
我会投放广告，然后出售
those leads into that business based on
这些线索最终促成了该业务的开展。
the pre-determined price. And so let's
预先确定的价格。那么，我们开始吧
say it's a a chiropractor or for me it
比如说，他是脊椎按摩师，或者对我来说是……
was a gym. So I went to a gym owner. I
曾是一家健身房。于是我去找了一位健身房老板。我
said, "What would you, you know, take
他说：“你知道，你会拿什么？”
for a member?" And they said, you know,
“对会员来说？”他们说，你知道，
we would actually take them for if you
我们其实会接受它们，如果你
can just bring them, you can keep the
你可以直接带过来，你可以保留它们。
money. We just want the customer for
钱。我们只是想要客户
free. And so I said, okay, well, the
自由的。所以我说，好吧，那么
first six weeks of the time that they
前六周
spend money with you is mine, and then
和你一起花钱就是我的钱，然后
after that, they're all yours. And they
之后，它们就都是你的了。他们
said, "That's fair." And so then I just
他说：“这很公平。”然后我就……
spent money and I sold into someone
我花了钱，然后把钱卖给了别人。
else's business, and I kept everything
那是别人的事，我把一切都藏在心里。
above the spread, which since the basis
高于价差，因为基差
was zero, I kept all of the money, and I
结果是零，我把所有的钱都留下了，而且
had zero cost of delivery. So literally,
运费为零。字面上来说，
it was just cash collected minus CAC,
这只是收取的现金减去客户手续费后的金额。
all of that was profit. And so when I
所有这些都是利润。所以当我
started over from zero the third time,
第三次从零开始。
um I was able to make $100,000 in the
嗯，我赚了10万美元。
first month when I needed it
第一个月，我需要它的时候
&gt;&gt; because you had that skill of
因为你具备那种技能
advertising.
广告。
&gt;&gt; And so when we say like invest in
所以当我们说投资时，
yourself, it's just a it's a it's a very
你自己，这只是一个，这是一个，这是一个非常
uh amorphous term, but fundamentally you
呃，这个术语很模糊，但从根本上来说，你
have to learn the the the skills of
必须学习这些技能
generating money. And so you're going to
创造收入。所以你要……
have to have some level of promotion.
必须有一定的晋升空间。
You have to let people know about your
你必须让人们知道你的
stuff, which is either be through
东西，要么是通过
content, through paid ads, through
通过付费广告等方式提供内容
outreach, right? Or it's going to be
对外宣传，对吧？或者它将是
through affiliates. So somebody already
通过附属公司。所以已经有人这么做了
has an audience you negotiate some sort
你需要与观众进行某种形式的协商。
of thing with. Honestly, so many
和……的东西。说实话，太多了。
businesses, like you can go to a
像你可以去的那种商家
chiropractor and say, "Hey, you know,
脊椎按摩师说：“嘿，你知道，
how little will you do 10 sessions for?"
“你愿意以最低价格做10次疗程吗？”
And you'd be amazed if I say, "Hey, I
如果我说“嘿，我”，你一定会感到惊讶。
can bring you a hundred people. How
可以带一百人来。如何
little can you do 10 sessions for?" They
“你能做10次疗程吗？”
might say 20 bucks a session. Now, I
可能会说每次20美元。现在，我
might sell it for 200, but that's on me.
或许能卖200，但这得看我自己的意愿。
&gt;&gt; And I make my 90% spread. I don't have
我实现了90%的收益目标。我没有
to do anything. I just have to promote
做任何事。我只需要宣传
and sell. And so, that is an example of
然后出售。所以，这就是一个例子
something that like I have done and did
就像我做过的事情一样
do each of the times when I needed to
每次需要的时候我都这样做
make money in the beginning when I had
一开始我赚了很多钱。
nothing.
没有什么。
&gt;&gt; What skill that you currently have?
你目前拥有哪些技能？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. would get you back to being a
是的。会让你重新成为
hund00 million entrepreneur.
亿万企业家。
&gt;&gt; So, it's a really good question. I think
所以，这确实是个好问题。我认为
it's actually stacking skills. So, a lot
实际上这是技能的叠加。所以，很多
of a lot of times like when this
很多时候就像这样
question gets asked um basically the
问题基本上是这样的：
assumption is that you have to stay in
假设你必须待在……
the same vehicle. And so, like the
同一辆车。所以，就像
fastest way to make $100,000 is not the
赚到10万美元最快的方法并非
fastest way to make $10 million, but I
最快的赚到1000万美元的方法，但是
might make $10 million faster if I
如果我……我可能更快赚到1000万美元。
started with $100,000. And so, if I have
最初投入了10万美元。所以，如果我有
zero, then I'm going to do something
如果是零，那我就要做点什么了。
that costs zero capital and is pure
它无需任何资本成本，而且是纯粹的
skill, which is exactly what what that
技能，也就是……
was. right now to make let's say to
曾是。现在要做，比如说……
actually start running those ads I might
我真的可能会开始投放这些广告。
need $1,000. And so it's like I might
需要1000美元。所以，就好像我可能会
drive Uber for a,000 bucks, get my
开 Uber 赚 1000 美元，拿走我的
thousand, then spend the,000 on ads to
然后把一千块钱花在广告上
make my 30,000 and during that process I
赚到3万美元，在这个过程中我
can reinvest that to get the hundred.
可以把这笔钱再投资，得到一百块。
Okay, great. Now I've got the hundred.
好的，太好了。现在我已经拿到一百了。
Now with the hundred I can flip that
现在有了这100块钱，我可以把它翻过来。
into and the key of each of those is
进入其中，而每个关键点是
that none of those are really businesses
那些都不是真正的企业。
per se and that like I can just walk
就其本身而言，就像我可以走一样
away from them whenever. I don't have
尽可能远离他们。我没有
ongoing delivery or ongoing commitments
持续交付或持续承诺
and so that gives you a lot of
因此，这给了你很多
flexibility. And I mean, I think there
灵活性。我的意思是，我认为有
are a lot of entrepreneurs, at least the
有很多企业家，至少……
ones that I know, um, have have had
我认识的那些人，嗯，都曾有过
these moments where they needed to
他们需要的这些时刻
generate a lot of capital in a short
在短时间内创造大量资本
period of time and have a few kind of
一段时间，并且有几种类型的
like fast money skills that they don't
他们喜欢那些快速赚钱的技能，但他们并不具备这些技能。
flex normally because there's there's
正常弯曲，因为有……
caps to them, right? What
向他们致敬，对吧？什么
&gt;&gt; I think is cool about entrepreneurship,
我觉得创业精神很酷。
too, is we can all do it. You have to
而且，我们所有人都能做到。你必须
find your unfair advantage. One of your
找到你的绝对优势。你的其中之一
unfair advantages is you're very good at
不公平优势在于你非常擅长
paid promotion and getting to the
付费推广及如何获得
masses, right? That was never really my
大众，对吧？那从来都不是我的
unfair advantage. I think there's two
不公平优势。我认为有两个。
different ways you could do this. One
你可以用其他方法来实现这一点。一
would be promotion. So, are you an
这将是一次晋升。所以，你是……
incredible salesperson to go direct to a
一位非常优秀的销售员，可以直接联系
ton of people? The other way is
很多人？另一种方法是
partnerships. And I think you can think
合作关系。我想你可以想想
of these different ways. Promotion could
这些不同的方法之一。晋升可能
be BTOC often, which is like going
经常进行 BTOC，就像去
direct to consumer. Um, often
直接面向消费者。嗯，通常
partnerships is B2B, going to a few big
合作伙伴关系是B2B，面向几家大型企业。
people. Um, I think of partnerships as
人们。嗯，我认为伙伴关系是
employment, which is a very fast way
就业，这是一种非常快捷的方式
often to make money, too. Like Jack
通常也是为了赚钱。像杰克
might make way more millions with you
或许跟你一起能赚到更多钱。
than he does individually. And so, my
比他单独行动时的表现要好。所以，我的
background when I didn't have any cash,
在我身无分文时的背景
I didn't know how to go to people
我不知道该如何与人相处。
directly. I didn't know how to do paid
直接地。我不知道如何付费。
ads. I wasn't sure how to do promotion,
广告。我不太确定该如何做推广，
which is a volume game that you have to
这是一个音量游戏，你必须
be good at. So, I went towards
善于。于是，我朝那个方向走去。
partnerships. I said, I can get to
合作关系。我说，我可以到达
fewer, bigger, faster. I can't get to
更少、更大、更快。我无法到达
many fast. And so, I think there's like
许多速度很快。所以，我觉得就像……
two paths to making money quickly if you
如果你有两条快速赚钱的途径，
don't have any. And and the first path
一个也没有。而且，第一条路
has less risk, but perhaps midsize
风险较小，但或许属于中等规模。
returns. And that is go find the best
返回。那就是去寻找最好的
entrepreneur, founder, business builder
企业家、创始人、企业建设者
you can find who you can still get to on
你可以找到你仍然可以联系到的人
a daily basis in some way and go work
每天都以某种方式去上班
for them. Learn as much as you can, earn
对他们来说。尽可能多地学习，赚取收入
as much as you can. As you learn more,
尽你所能。随着你了解的越多，
ask for more continuously over time.
随着时间的推移，不断提出更高的要求。
This is how I mean Cheryl Sandberg is
这就是我的意思，谢丽尔·桑德伯格是
one of the richest people in the world
世界上最富有的人之一
and she's never had her own business,
她从来没有拥有过自己的事业。
right? She's only worked for other
正确的？她只为其他人工作过。
people and she's doing just fine. So I
她现在一切都很好，大家都很关心她。所以，我
think that's the first way and that
我认为这是第一种方法，而且
would be what I would call partnerships
我称之为伙伴关系。
or employment. And then the second way
或就业。然后是第二种方法
is to go do it yourself, right? which is
就是自己动手做，对吧？即
high risk but probably highest reward.
风险高，但回报也可能最高。
And in that instance, you have to go and
在这种情况下，你必须去……
figure out how to get people to buy your
想办法让人们购买你的产品
things continuously over over time. But
事物会随着时间的推移而持续发展。但
like when I didn't have money in the
比如我当时没钱的时候
beginning, um you know, I had just I had
开始的时候，嗯，你知道，我刚刚，我曾经
gotten out of finance. I didn't want to
退出了金融行业。我不想
work for somebody else again. I was
再次为别人工作。我当时
pretty miserable. I had worked for a
相当糟糕。我曾为一家公司工作过
billion hours for people in investment
投资人员投入的数十亿小时
banking and asset management. And uh I
银行和资产管理。呃，我
had massive gold in handcuffs. Like I
手铐里装着大量黄金。就像我
made a lot of money. And um I had no
赚了很多钱。嗯，我没有
brilliant idea. I didn't have a business
卓见。我没有生意。
idea. I had no idea what to do next and
主意。我完全不知道接下来该怎么办，
I'm pretty riskaverse actually. I was
其实我挺厌恶风险的。我当时
like way too scared to go do do what you
太害怕了，不敢去做你想做的事
guys all did which is start businesses
大家都这么做了，那就是创业。
from scratch. And so instead I partnered
从零开始。所以，我转而选择了合作。
up. I went to another company that
向上。我去了另一家公司。
needed to raise capital and get a few
需要筹集资金并获得一些
investments in it. And I went to them
对此进行投资。我去了他们那里。
and said, "I can raise money from a few
他说：“我可以从几个方面筹集资金。”
of these people that I know. If I do
我认识的这些人中，就这些。如果我这样做
that, can I negotiate a little bit of
那，我可以稍微协商一下吗？
equity in the company? Can I negotiate
公司股权？我可以协商吗？
upside return for the money and dollars
资金和美元的上涨回报
that I bring in? And I want to I want to
我带来的？我也想，我也想
be a partner in the company." And so you
成为公司的合伙人。”所以你
don't always have to start your own
不一定非要自己创业。
thing. If you can negotiate with
事物。如果你能和……谈判
partnerships, I think sometimes you can
我认为，在合作关系中，有时候你可以
skip to the front of the line if you're
如果你是，就插队到队伍前面。
not a great natural salesperson, you
你并不是一个天生的销售员。
know, or marketer. And so you really
认识，或者营销人员。所以你真的
just need to decide which one. And
只需要决定选哪一个。和
neither of them are better than any
它们俩谁也不比谁强。
others. They're just better for you.
其他的。它们对你更有益。
&gt;&gt; The amount of resources you have access
你所拥有的资源量
to is a factor of knowledge, network,
是知识、人脉等因素造成的。
and reputation. So you're at all times
以及声誉。所以你始终
you're trying to build your knowledge.
你正在努力积累知识。
You're trying to build your network.
你正在努力建立人脉网络。
You're trying to build your reputation.
你正在努力建立自己的声誉。
A lot of people are worried about the
很多人都担心……
knowledge, but they've probably done
他们可能知道，但他们可能已经这么做了。
interesting things already in their
他们身上已经有一些有趣的东西了。
history. They probably if they looked
历史。他们可能看起来像
over the last 3, four, five years, they
在过去的3、4、5年里，他们
could say, "Actually, I've done all
可以说：“实际上，我已经完成了所有……”
sorts of things, but I've never told
诸如此类的事情，但我从未说过。
anyone about that, right? I've never
有人知道这件事吗？我从未
actually explain to I've never posted on
实际上，我从未在……上发过帖子。
LinkedIn. I've never posted an update
领英。我从未发布过更新。
telling people what I've done. So
告诉别人我做了什么。所以
therefore, I've actually got things that
因此，我实际上有一些东西
could build a reputation, but I've never
或许可以建立声誉，但我从未
leveraged that reputation." If you're a
利用了这种声誉。”如果你是
young person, especially, network is
对于年轻人来说，尤其是网络，
actually you've got a superpower with
实际上，你拥有超能力。
network. And I'll tell you why. Because
网络。我会告诉你为什么。因为
if you go to a private bank that
如果你去一家私人银行，
normally banks people with 3 million,
通常情况下，银行会给拥有300万存款的人提供服务。
but you say, "I want to be an
但你说，“我想成为一个……”
entrepreneur. I want to come to some of
企业家。我想去参加一些活动
your entrepreneur events that you host,
你举办的创业活动，
they'll bring you along cuz you're
他们会带上你，因为你
you're an ambitious young person." If
你是一个很有抱负的年轻人。
you go to a large accounting firm and
你去了一家大型会计事务所，
say, "Do you ever host big events? Could
比如说，“你们举办过大型活动吗？”
I attend some? Can I jump on a
我参加过一些吗？我可以跳上去吗？
newsletter that lets people know about
让人们了解以下内容的简讯
the events?" They'll invite you along.
他们会邀请你参加这些活动。
And I'm talking about like Ernston Young
我指的是像恩斯顿·杨那样的人。
and KPMG. Every single week, they've got
以及毕马威会计师事务所。每周，他们都有
some thing that they're doing in their
他们正在做的事情
offices. They've got experts, they've
办公室。他们有专家，他们有
got rich people, they got all that sort
有钱人，他们拥有那种东西。
of stuff happening there and they'll
那里正在发生一些事情，他们会……
invite you along. So, you've got this
邀请你一起来。所以，你现在有了这个
ability to build your network, you got
你具备建立人脉的能力。
this ability to leverage uh your
这种利用你的能力
reputation. I actually don't think that
名声。我其实并不这么认为。
you can make good decisions about the
你可以就以下方面做出明智的决定：
knowledge on your own. I think you need
自学知识。我认为你需要
someone who's at the higher level to
一个级别更高的人
tell you this is the skills you should
告诉你这些是你应该掌握的技能
go for. These are the things you should
去吧。这些是你应该做的。
do. So, for example, at the time that
做。例如，当时
Alex did ads, it was a great time for
亚历克斯做过广告，那段时间对他来说非常棒。
doing ads. But now fast forward to
做广告。但现在快进到
today, it's probably better to study AI
如今，研究人工智能或许更为明智。
and and to bring that to the table. So
并把这一点摆到桌面上来讨论。所以
sometimes those rep sometimes those
有时那些代表，有时那些
things change. So let's say you figure
世事变迁。假设你觉得
out what is your reputation? What can
你的声誉如何？什么可以
you talk about when you're in front of
当你在前面的时候，你会谈到
people, you go networking, you go to a
人们，你去拓展人脉，你去参加一个
few of these events, you outreach, you
这些活动中，你们的外联活动很少，你们
get yourself in front of some people,
让自己出现在一些人面前，
and you actually ask the question, what
你实际上会问，什么
kind of skills do I need? What what sort
我需要哪些技能？什么类型的
of um I need to build my skills? I need
嗯……我需要提升自己的技能吗？我需要
to build my knowledge. What do you think
为了增长知识。你怎么认为
would be a valuable thing uh to do?
这样做会很有意义吗？
because people who are at that next
因为接下来要面对的人
level up, they're they're noticing what
升级了，他们注意到了什么
they what they need. Uh they're noticing
他们得到了他们需要的东西。呃，他们注意到了。
what's hot, what's not. Um so they're
什么流行，什么过时。嗯，所以他们是
going to be able to teach you or or
能够教你或者
guide you. And and um to Cody's point,
引导你。嗯，就像科迪说的那样，
you know, you you want to have a mentor
你知道，你想找个导师。
in your life. You want to have someone
在你的生活中。你想找个人
who's who's been there, done it. You
谁是那些亲身经历过的人。你
want to, you know, partner with a bigger
想和更大的公司合作。
organization and get some of those.
组织起来，弄到一些。
Before Kim Kardashian was Kim
在成为金·卡戴珊之前
Kardashian, she was Paris Hilton's uh
卡戴珊，她是帕丽斯·希尔顿的……
assistant and she learned the playbook
助理，她学会了这套流程。
for being famous for being famous. and
因为出名而出名。和
then she took it to a new level. Took it
然后她又把这件事提升到了一个新的高度。拿走了
to a new level. So she she uh she did an
提升到一个新的水平。所以她，呃，她做了一个
apprenticeship and then she applied the
她先参加了学徒计划，然后申请了……
apprenticeship.
学徒制。
&gt;&gt; One of the things that all of us have in
我们所有人都有的其中一件事是
common is we make content and it's
共同点是我们制作内容，而且是
almost a bit of an elephant in the room
几乎就像房间里的大象一样显而易见
that no one's no one's really doubled
没有人真正翻倍
down on when I asked what what you guys
当我问你们怎么回事时，你们都低下了头。
think is the most sort of like
认为最像
undervalued skill or the best place to
被低估的技能或最佳去处
invest in yourself. I was actually
投资自己。我当时其实
expecting you all to say start making
期待你们都说开始制作
content for a variety of reasons. Not
出于各种原因需要内容。不是
just because you want to build an
仅仅因为你想建造一个
audience so you have more customers, but
这样可以吸引更多客户，但是
actually
实际上
&gt;&gt; and I can see it on all of you. It's
我在你们每个人身上都能看出来。它是
helped you to think better.
帮助你更好地思考。
&gt;&gt; It's helped you to communicate better.
它帮助你更好地沟通。
It's helped you to sell better. When you
它帮助你更好地销售产品。当你
get that chance to sit down with that
有机会坐下来好好谈谈。
investor or that rich person, you said a
你说的是投资者还是那个有钱人？
second ago, you said earlier that if I'd
刚才你说过，如果我
sat old Alex here, one of the big
老亚历克斯坐在这里，他是大人物之一。
differences is this one's much more
区别在于，这个要多得多。
focused, concise, articulate. So, I'm
专注、简洁、表达清晰。所以，我是
wondering what you guys think of that
想知道你们对此有何看法。
content as a undervalued,
内容被低估了，
underappreciated skill in the world
世界上被低估的技能
we're heading in.
我们正往里走。
&gt;&gt; If I'm starting to today rather than
如果我今天就开始，而不是
when I had, you know, zero, there's
当我一无所有的时候，你知道，就是那样。
still a huge amount of attention that
仍然引起了极大的关注
sits on social media, if not more. And
活跃在社交媒体上，甚至更多。和
there's even more demand for content now
现在对内容的需求更大了。
than there was. And so you can supply
比以前多了。所以你可以提供
that and get compensated for it. And
这样做就能获得补偿。和
you'll have to do repetitions for a
你需要重复练习一段时间。
period of time until eventually you get
一段时间后，你最终会得到
good. And then you can develop an
好的。然后你可以开发一个
audience and then you obviously can sell
然后你就可以向受众推销产品了。
things to them.
对他们来说。
&gt;&gt; I think um content content's a little
我觉得内容有点……
bit of an interesting one because
这有点意思，因为
content works when you've got
当你拥有……时，内容就能发挥作用。
intellectual property to leverage. So I
可利用的知识产权。所以，我
remember Alex popped onto my screen the
记得吗？Alex突然出现在我的屏幕上。
first time and he says, "I've sold my
第一次，他说：“我已经卖掉了我的
company for $40 million and I've got
公司价值 4000 万美元，我还有
nothing to sell you. I'm just going to
我没有东西要卖给你。我这就去
tell you how I did it." Cody's the same.
告诉你我是怎么做的。”科迪也一样。
She's like, uh, you know, I, uh, I was
她就像，呃，你知道，我，呃，我曾经
working at Goldman Sachs, but then I
我在高盛工作，但后来
left Goldman Sachs to earn more money
离开高盛是为了赚更多钱
through laundromats. I'm like, that's
通过自助洗衣店。我当时就想，这……
interesting. That's fascinating. Right.
有趣的。真令人着迷。正确的。
So, I'm going to watch that content
所以我打算看看那些内容。
because there's some interesting
因为有一些有趣的事情
intellectual property there. Um, my
那里的知识产权。嗯，我的
channel took off when I started talking
我开始说话后，频道就火了。
about I've done seven startups that went
我大概创办过七家初创公司，它们都成功了。
zero to a million in the first 12
从零到一百万，前12个月
months. So, it's that ability to have
几个月。所以，关键在于拥有这种能力。
some intellectual property that people
一些人的知识产权
are going to want to get to. I can think
他们会想要到达那里。我能想到
of a bunch of examples of creators that
一系列创作者的例子
hadn't done anything but their ideas
除了他们的想法，他们什么也没做。
were the value. So if you think of
就是价值所在。所以如果你想到
someone like George Mack or even James
像乔治·麦克或者詹姆斯这样的人
CLA or lots of other of these sort of
CLA 或许多其他类似的物质
like J Shetty online writers who
像 J Shetty 这样的网络作家
&gt;&gt; J Shetty had a great one which was uh
J Shetty 有一首很棒的歌，呃……
I've got monk wisdom for the modern
我拥有现代僧侣的智慧
world
世界
&gt;&gt; and we've got Ali Abdal I left the I
我们有阿里·阿卜杜勒，我离开了我
quit being a doctor to be a YouTuber. M
放弃医生职业，转行做油管博主。 M
&gt;&gt; so there's these little hooks that work
所以这里有一些可以工作的小钩子。
and
和
&gt;&gt; does everyone have a you don't have to
每个人都有吗？你不必有
have sold a business for tens of
以数十万美元的价格出售了一家企业
millions or made millions
赚了数百万美元或赚取了数百万美元
&gt;&gt; from I think there's some intellectual
我认为这其中存在一些知识分子的因素。
property that you've got but bear in
你所拥有的财产，但请记住
mind that there was a different time
请注意，时代已经不同了。
where you could just burst onto the
你可以突然闯入
scene and we now have AI generated
场景，现在我们有了人工智能生成的
content so if you imagine like airplanes
内容就像飞机一样
and they're at the airport and the fog
他们在机场，雾气弥漫。
rolls in and if you're on the ground
滚进来，如果你在地面上
it's very hard to take off but if you're
很难脱身，但如果你是
already up in the air it's very easy to
既然已经悬而未决，就很容易……
stay up in the air and it's kind of like
待在空中，感觉就像……
the AI content that's coming in is is
正在输入的AI内容是
that fog Right? There's just going to be
那雾，对吧？只会有
thousands of AI generated content pieces
数千个人工智能生成的内容
just flooding onto everyone's feed. And
铺天盖地地涌入每个人的动态。和
if you don't have a really good hook,
如果你没有一个非常好的钩子，
you're just not going to drown out that
你不可能盖过那个声音。
noise.
噪音。
&gt;&gt; You guys must all be thinking about
你们肯定都在想……
this.
这。
&gt;&gt; I have I have so much I'm all right. All
我有很多东西，我没事的。全部
right. So So
正确的。所以还行
one thing I think everyone has to decide
我认为每个人都必须决定一件事。
on if they're going to start making
关于他们是否会开始制作
content is am I an entertainer or am I
内容是我究竟是娱乐者还是我
an educator? Right. Right off the bat.
一位教育工作者？正确的。开门见山。
And so I think AI content for sure will
所以我认为人工智能内容肯定会……
have tremendous leverage on
在以下方面拥有巨大的影响力
entertainment more so than education
娱乐比教育更重要
because the big underlying thing that
因为根本原因在于……
Daniel's hitting at is that you have to
丹尼尔想表达的是，你必须
have proof, right? Like like an AI
你有证据吗？就像人工智能一样
avatar cannot come in and say I sold my
化身不能进来就说我卖掉了我的
company for free. They can't. They
免费公司。他们做不到。他们
didn't do anything because they don't
他们什么也没做，因为他们不做。
exist in the real world. Which is why in
存在于现实世界中。这就是为什么在
my opinion like the absolute foolproof
我的意见就像绝对万无一失的办法
method for making educational content is
制作教育内容的方法是
dop Epic [__] and then talk about the
嗑药嗑到史诗级，然后谈谈这个
epic [__] you did. Period. And so like I
你干了件了不起的事。时期。所以就像我
um so yes I'm in you know I'm in LA.
嗯，是的，我在洛杉矶。
Yesterday we also um we had the school
昨天我们还有学校。
games winners come out schools platform
游戏获胜者将亮相学校平台
that hosts online communities and the
托管在线社区和
winner of the last school games. So 90
上届校际运动会的冠军。所以是90
days he got to like 300 and something
有几天他达到了300多岁。
thousand a month from a YouTube uh
每月从 YouTube 赚一千美元
channel that he started 16 months ago.
这是他16个月前创建的频道。
So he started 16 months ago making
所以他从16个月前开始制作
videos about AI. Now what was his
关于人工智能的视频。现在，他的又是什么呢？
interesting thing? So he was just always
有趣的事？所以他一直都是这样。
into AI learned about the tools and then
进入人工智能领域后，我学习了相关工具，然后……
he started helping small businesses for
他开始帮助小型企业
like $1,500 $2,500 a month where he
比如他每月能挣1500到2500美元。
would just help them implement these
这会帮助他们实施这些措施。
automations that would save them money
自动化可以帮他们省钱
and time. And then people were like well
还有时间。然后人们就说，嗯
how did you do that? And so he just
你是怎么做到的？所以他就
basically would just explain each of the
基本上就是解释每一项
automations that he made for each of
他为每个项目制作的自动化程序
these businesses on his channel. And he
他频道上的这些商家。而他
made one video a day explaining one of
每天制作一个视频，解释其中一个内容。
the automations. And then he said, "If
自动化。然后他说：“如果
you want I have a group that's whatever
你想要什么？我有个小组，随便什么都行。
$300, $400 a month that shows you how to
每月300美元、400美元，教你如何……
build the same automations." To your
构建相同的自动化流程。” 致您
point about the education is like you
关于教育的观点就像你
just need some proof. And it doesn't
只需要一些证据。但事实并非如此。
like you don't have to like the bigger
比如，你不必喜欢更大的那个。
the proof you have the wider basically
你所掌握的证据越广泛，基本上就是
the wider TAM you'll be able to reach
你能够触及的潜在市场范围越广
because more people be I'll just put the
因为更多的人会……我就直接放上来吧。
words impressed. if you just are in your
令人印象深刻。如果你只是在你的
20s and to be fair, you just quit
二十多岁，说实话，你就辞职了。
Goldman Sachs. It's like that is enough
高盛。这就足够了。
of a thing that because that's it's a 1%
因为那是1%的事情
type deal, right? But you can also you
这类交易，对吧？但你也可以
can 1% through achievement. But the
可以通过成就获得 1% 的收益。但是
other side that I think people widely
另一方面，我认为人们普遍认为……
underestimate is you can 1% through
低估的可能是你通过 1% 的概率。
volume of work. So if I said I read 200
工作量。所以如果我说我读了200本书
books last year,
去年出版的书籍
&gt;&gt; let me show you the 200. They're all
让我给你看看这200个。它们都是
dog, you know, dogeared. Let me tell you
你知道，就是那种耳朵卷起来的狗。让我告诉你
what I learned. Like I'd be like, well
我学到了什么。就像我会说，嗯
shoot. Because I think everybody wants a
射击。因为我觉得每个人都想要一个
bargain on time, right? Like I went on a
把握时机，讨价还价，对吧？就像我去了……
100 speed dates. this is what I learned.
100次快速约会。这是我学到的。
It's like, well, I don't want to go on
感觉就像，嗯，我不想继续下去了。
100 dates, but like anyone can do that.
100次约会，但谁都能做到。
So, it's either 1% achievement or 1%
所以，要么是1%的成就，要么是1%
effort, but this one you can do. And
需要花点功夫，但这件事你肯定能做到。和
even if you have zero outcome, there's
即使没有任何结果，也还有……
still stuff that you'll learn. And then
还有一些东西你会学到。进而
that will people find interesting that
人们会觉得这很有趣。
you can build an audience around. And if
你可以围绕它建立一个受众群体。如果
you do that enough times, eventually you
你这样做次数多了，最终你会
do achieve something that is
确实取得了一些成就
interesting. And then that kind of
有趣的。然后就是那种
becomes permanent. But at the end of the
成为永久性的。但在最后
day, like proof always beats promise. I
就像事实证明总比空头支票强一样。我
&gt;&gt; I also think anybody can go viral online
我也认为任何人都有可能在网上爆红。
with one of two things. We've talked a
有两种情况之一。我们已经谈过了
lot about experience. So if you do have
很多关于经验的内容。所以如果你确实有
experience, if you built a billion
经验，如果你建造了十亿
dollar and assets under management
美元及资产管理规模
business, gone to Goldman, built seven
生意上，去了高盛，建了七家公司。
startups, that's incredible. That's not
创业公司，真是太棒了。那不是
normal. That's totally fine. But that
普通的。完全没问题。但是……
means that you could just have the
这意味着你可能只需要
everyday other e of starting the
每天其他 e 开始
experience. I think we we obsess on
经验。我认为我们过于执着于
expertise. Expertise is the way to make
专业知识。专业技能是成功的途径。
content online and make millions. But
在线内容创作，赚取数百万美元。但
what about just the experience? You
如果仅仅是体验本身呢？你
could say, "Actually, I've done nothing.
可以说：“实际上，我什么也没做。”
I'm a college dropout. I've [__]
我大学辍学了。我操过
around a lot. I don't have much figured
周围很多地方。我还没想好太多。
out, but over the next year, I'm gonna
退出，但在接下来的一年里，我将
try to make a million dollars. And you
尝试赚一百万美元。你呢
can go just as viral, if not more. I
传播速度可能更快，甚至更快。我
mean, a good example would be like Ryan
比如说，瑞恩就是个很好的例子。
Tran, who who I love, who's in Austin,
Tran，我爱的人，她在奥斯汀，
Texas, too. And Ryan is just like, I'm
德克萨斯州也是。瑞恩就说，我是
trying stuff, and this might fail and I
尝试一些方法，但这可能会失败，而且我
have no idea, and you guys can come
完全不知道，你们可以来。
along. The proof could actually be you
沿着。证据可能就是你。
just trying a thing and it not working
我只是尝试了一下，但是没成功。
one way or the other. And so I think the
不管怎样。所以我认为
only problem with this type which is
这种类型唯一的问题是
experience as opposed to expertise is
经验而非专业知识是
that with expertise you have attention
凭借专业知识，你就能获得关注。
and intention aka intent to buy whereas
以及购买意图，即购买意向
if you're just experiencing thing you
如果你只是在经历某件事，你
might have attention but what are you
或许会受到关注，但你究竟是什么？
going to sell because you don't have
打算卖掉是因为你没有
like a value derived from it where's
就像从中衍生出的一个值，它在哪里？
your intent I mean if you think about
我的意思是，如果你仔细想想你的意图……
who are the biggest creators online
谁是网络上最大的内容创作者？
only fans the Kardashians you know what
OnlyFans 只关注卡戴珊家族，你知道的
are the biggest websites online porn
最大的在线色情网站是
sites that's a lot of attention but the
这些网站获得了大量关注，但是
intent to buy is going to be low for any
购买意愿在任何情况下都会很低。
of those over time at large. And so I
随着时间的推移，这些人逐渐增多。所以，我
think you have to ask yourself, okay, if
你应该问问自己，好吧，如果
I get a ton of attention, let's make
我受到了很多关注，我们来做这件事吧
sure I'm really thoughtful on what I get
当然，我会认真考虑我收到的东西。
attention for. And then let's think
引起关注。然后我们来思考一下
about once I have that attention, where
大约一旦我获得了那种关注，
do I actually have some sort of
我真的有某种……
expertise or value that I can trade in
我可以交换的专业技能或价值
order for people to have an intent to
要求人们有此意图
buy? And I think about it like this.
买？我是这样想的。
Rihanna, huge star, right? Big
蕾哈娜，超级巨星，对吧？大的
celebrity, billionaire now because of
名人，如今的亿万富翁，都是因为
Fenty Beauty. Drake, giant celebrity,
Fenty Beauty。德雷克，超级巨星
arguably more views, more hits than
可以说，浏览量和点击量都比……更多。
Rihanna, worth one, one six, 1/8 what
蕾哈娜，价值一，一六，八分之一什么
Rihanna is worth. Why? Because he has
蕾哈娜值这个价。为什么？因为他有
ton of sub attention, but he hasn't
他获得了大量的关注，但他并没有。
actually done much to get intent to buy
实际上做了很多工作来激发购买意愿。
from him. And so Rihanna's just
来自他。所以蕾哈娜就只是
categorically better, if we define
如果我们定义，那么它肯定更好。
better as bank account and scoreboard on
比银行账户和记分牌更好
uh net worth, than Drake is at
呃，净资产，比德雷克的要多。
monetizing their intention. And so, um,
将他们的意图变现。所以，嗯，
I think that a lot of creators online
我认为很多网络创作者
think too much about views, likes,
过多考虑浏览量、点赞数、
subscribes, and don't think very much
订阅者，而且不太在意
about how do I monetize on top of this
关于我如何在此基础上实现盈利
because nobody stays relevant forever
因为没有人能永远保持影响力。
online. And so, I think while you're in
在线的。所以，我认为当你在的时候
the spotlight, you do have to think
聚光灯下，你确实需要考虑一下。
about how you going to convert that
关于你打算如何转换
funnel in some way.
以某种方式流入。
&gt;&gt; That's a really great point. A lot of
这真是个非常好的观点。很多
the people you see blowing up online,
你在网上看到的那些爆红的人，
they do have a backend that monetizes it
他们的确有一个后端系统来实现盈利。
because to your point, it costs money.
因为正如你所说，这需要花钱。
you know, I probably spend 40 50,000 a
你知道，我大概每年要花4万到5万美元。
month just on retainers of people who
一个月只支付给那些人的保留费
are working on that stuff and
我们正在研究这些事情。
&gt;&gt; content.
内容。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Content related stuff and you know
是的。内容相关的内容，你知道的
because I have businesses that can
因为我拥有可以……的生意
monetize that then it it worth doing but
如果能将其商业化，那就值得做了。
it's hard to compete with that if you
如果你这样做，就很难与之竞争。
don't have a back end. The the other
没有后端。另一个
option is to work with someone who does
另一种选择是与这样的人合作
have a business and they do have
他们有自己的生意，而且他们确实有
experience. they do have something to
经验。他们确实有一些东西。
talk about, but they're busy and they
谈论这些，但他们很忙，而且他们
need someone to project manage this
需要有人来负责这个项目的管理。
because one thing that's happened is
因为发生的一件事是：
that to the traditional business owner,
对于传统企业主而言，
this personal brand thing and this
个人品牌这回事，还有这个
building a content empire uh that builds
打造一个内容帝国，呃，就是建立
your business, this is brand new to a
您的业​​务，这对您来说是一个全新的领域
lot of people. So, there are plenty of
很多人。所以有很多
people who've got a $50 million a year
年收入5000万美元的人
business and they're going, "Oh, should
商家们会说：“哦，应该……”
I show up online at all? Maybe I
我到底有没有上线？也许我
should." and they're just starting to
应该。”而他们才刚刚开始
tiptoe into the water and they've got a
踮着脚尖走进水里，他们就……
story, they've got a back-end business,
故事是这样的，他们还有后端业务。
they can monetize it, they can allocate
他们可以将其货币化，他们可以分配
budget to it, you could be the person
把预算考虑进去，你可能就是那个人
who does that and you'd be, if you did
谁会那样做？如果你那样做，你就会变成那样。
do that, you would be one of the very
那样做，你将成为最顶尖的人才之一。
special people in their life. Um, I had
他们生命中那些特别的人。嗯，我曾经
a guy come to me a couple of years ago
几年前有个男的来找过我
and said, "Daniel, I just cannot believe
然后他说：“丹尼尔，我简直不敢相信……”
you've written five books at the time.
当时你已经写了五本书。
You've got seven different companies.
你们有七家不同的公司。
You've got all this stuff going on and
你现在面临着这么多事情，
you've got a few thousand followers and
你已经有几千名粉丝了，
I've had a look online. You get like
我上网查过了。你会喜欢
10,000 views a month." And I'm like,
每月1万次浏览量。” 我当时就想，
"Yeah, but I'm busy. I'm running my
“是啊，但我很忙。我在经营我的……”
businesses." And he came to me and said,
企业。”然后他走到我面前说，
"I will project manage you into the
我将以项目经理的身份带领你进入……
millions per month." And he just
每月数百万美元。”而他只是
literally picked this up, a guy called
真的捡到了这个，一个叫
Martin, right? And he just said, "I I'm
是马丁吧？他只是说：“我，我是……”
going to do this and I'm going to turn
我要这么做，然后我要转身
up at your house, do a day of filming
到你家来，拍一天的片子
every month. I'm going to edit it. I'm
每月一次。我打算修改一下。我是
going to chop it all up. I'm going to do
我要把它们全部切碎。我打算这样做
all this stuff and I'll project manage
所有这些事情，我都会负责项目管理。
the whole thing." Now, the two of us are
整件事。”现在，我们俩是
very uh close now. We've got a good
差不多快了。我们有一个不错的
relationship. And he's now got an idea
关系。他现在有了一个想法
for an AI startup, and I'm going to back
对于一家人工智能初创公司来说，我会支持它。
that. Every single one of you watching
那。你们每一位观看的人
this right now has something to offer,
现在这确实有其优势。
whether it's knowledge or skills or
无论是知识还是技能，
experience. And that means you have
经验。这意味着你拥有
value. Stands, the platform I co-own,
价值。 Stands，我共同拥有的平台，
who are one of the sponsors of this
他们是本次活动的赞助商之一。
podcast, turns your knowledge into a
播客，将你的知识转化为
business through one single click. You
一键开启商务之旅。你
can sell digital products, coaching,
可以销售数字产品、提供辅导服务
communities, and you don't need any
社区，你不需要任何
coding experience either, just the drive
不需要编程经验，只要有动力就行。
to start. This is a business I really
开始。这是一项我非常重视的事业。
believe in. And already $300 million has
相信。而且已经有3亿美元了。
been earned by creators, coaches, and
由创作者、教练和
entrepreneurs just like you have the
像您一样的创业者
potential to be on Stan's store. These
有可能在斯坦的商店上架。这些
are people who didn't wait, who heard me
是那些没有等待，而是听到我说话的人。
saying things like this, and instead of
说出这样的话，而不是
procrastinating, started building, then
拖延了一段时间，然后开始搭建，
launched something and now they're
他们推出了一些东西，现在他们
getting paid to do it. Stan is
做这件事还能获得报酬。斯坦是
incredibly simple and incredibly easy.
极其简单，极其容易。
And you can link it with a Shopify store
而且你还可以将它与 Shopify 商店关联起来。
that you're already using if you want
如果你愿意的话，你已经在使用你正在使用的东西了。
to. I'm on it and so is my girlfriend
到。我和我女朋友都在用。
and many of my team. So, if you want to
以及我的团队中的许多人。所以，如果你想
join, start by launching your own
加入，首先创建你自己的项目
business with a free 30-day trial. Visit
企业版提供 30 天免费试用。访问
stephvenbartlet.stan. stan.store and get
stephvenbartlet.stan。 stan.store 并获取
yours set up within minutes.
您的设备几分钟内即可设置完成。
&gt;&gt; If you guys were starting from zero
如果你们是从零开始的话
today
今天
&gt;&gt; with AI in the picture and all of these
人工智能的加入以及所有这些
platforms and the way things are going,
平台以及发展趋势，
I I spent I've spent a lot of time
我花了很多时间
thinking about the next big opportunity
思考下一个重大机遇
in content and I think about the next
在内容方面，我思考着接下来的事情。
big platform. Where would you be
大型平台。你会在哪里？
starting today based on who you guys are
从今天开始，取决于你们是谁
and the skills that you have and the
以及你所拥有的技能和
things you're interested in is probably
你感兴趣的事情很可能
a better way of saying it. Would you be
更好的表达方式。你愿意吗？
on LinkedIn posting once a day? Would
在LinkedIn上每天发一条帖子？会
you be on Tik Tok making videos? Would
你在TikTok上拍视频吗？会
you be on YouTube starting a channel?
你打算在YouTube上开个频道吗？
Would you start a newsletter?
你会创办一份电子报吗？
And with AI in the picture, I think it
考虑到人工智能的介入，我认为……
changes the answer because content is
改变答案是因为内容是
going to become very easy to make. So
制作起来会变得非常容易。所以
where does the value acrew to? Like
价值最终会流向哪里？喜欢
where does the value move to in a world
在一个世界上，价值会流向哪里？
where every kid a kid in Mumbai could
孟买的每个孩子都可以
make uh a real or a quote picture now
现在就制作一张真实的图片或引用图片吧
with Chat Gyt? So where is the value
与 Chat Gyt 一起？那么价值在哪里呢？
going to acrew and how are you going to
去 acrew，你打算怎么做？
milk that cow? How are you going to
给那头牛挤奶？你打算怎么做？
capitalize? Like what is the one thesis
是否应该大写？比如，那唯一论点是什么？
you have about the future of content
你对内容的未来有什么看法？
that you haven't told anybody yet? Tell
你还没告诉任何人吗？告诉
me.
我。
&gt;&gt; Well,
出色地，
&gt;&gt; I'll tell you mine. I'll tell you mine.
我来告诉你我的故事。我来告诉你我的故事。
&gt;&gt; I want to ask a question too for
我也想问一个问题。
everybody at the end of I'll give you my
最后我会把我的
my quick thing. One, I will say like um
我的简短说明。第一，我会说，嗯
and I'd be curious if you all agree.
我很想知道你们是否都同意。
When I first started making content, um
当我刚开始制作内容的时候，嗯
most people that I knew thought it was
我认识的大多数人都认为是
really cringe. Actually, they're like uh
真是尴尬至极。实际上，他们就像……
why would you make content? If you've
你为什么要制作内容？如果你有
actually had any success that you
实际上你取得了任何成功
supposed to have had, why would you be
你本该有的，为什么会这样？
so idiotic as to be on the internet
蠢到上网
making content, it can't be true that
制作内容，这不可能是真的
you've done these things if you're
如果你做过这些事，那么你就是
making Tik Toks all day? And um and I
整天拍抖音视频？嗯，还有我
think they totally miss the boat that
他们认为他们完全错过了机会。
like the 21st century concern uh
就像21世纪的担忧一样
currency is attention and attention
货币就是注意力。
could be bought with ads or attention
可以通过广告或关注度来购买
could be bought in a different way but
也可以通过其他方式购买，但
through organic content creation. And so
通过自然的内容创作。所以
you go like cringe to content to
你就像那些令人尴尬的内容一样
conversion. And actually, I think all of
转换。实际上，我认为所有
us would probably agree it was a pretty
我们大概都会同意，这真是太棒了。
good play, but like I'm sure Did you
打得不错，但我确信你……
guys all get laughed at when you first
男生第一次见面时都会被嘲笑。
got on the internet?
上网了吗？
&gt;&gt; Of course.
当然。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Right.
是的。正确的。
&gt;&gt; Never.
绝不。
&gt;&gt; Like still get laughed at now.
现在还是会被人嘲笑。
&gt;&gt; I still get I still get laughed at. So
我仍然会被人嘲笑。所以
like I just want to prepare. If you get
我只是想做好准备。如果你得到
online, be prepared. People will think
在线上，做好准备。人们会想
you're idiotic and
你真是个白痴。
&gt;&gt; and your friends the shedding period
和你的朋友们一起度过换毛期
where you transition to
过渡到
&gt;&gt; 100%. And and people who are serious for
100%。以及那些认真对待此事的人
whatever reason have not figured out
原因尚不清楚
that there is a huge arbitrage
存在巨大的套利机会
opportunity with being known. Even if
成名带来的机会。即使
even if you don't care about the views
即使你不在乎浏览量。
and all I have as something that's a
而我所拥有的，仅仅是某种东西
differentiator is that if I ping Stephen
区别在于，如果我联系斯蒂芬
you'll respond to me because I am
你会回应我，因为我就是
somehow I have some prefence online.
不知为何，我对网络有某种偏好。
Same with Alex, you know, right with all
亚历克斯也是一样，你知道，他跟所有人都一样。
of us. And so one I just want to say
我们中的一些人。所以，我只想说一点。
that up front because it will suck. You
先说清楚，因为这会很糟糕。你
know, I'm in these creator groups and at
我知道，我加入了这些创作者群组，而且……
some point it just happened yesterday.
这件事就发生在昨天。
I'm in a group with like some of the
我和一些其他人在一个小组里
biggest creators in the world and uh all
世界上最伟大的创作者们，还有所有
of them were listening. I mean maybe 50
他们中有人在听。我的意思是，也许50
responses of a moment where um everybody
大家对那一刻的反应
hated them on the internet. it was super
在网上讨厌他们。太棒了
dark. You know, they couldn't stop
黑暗的。你知道，他们根本停不下来。
watching and reading the comments and
观看和阅读评论
they felt like there was like a fight
他们感觉就像打仗一样。
orflight situation from a bunch of
或航班情况来自一群
strangers. And so, I think it's worth
陌生人。所以，我认为这是值得的。
just saying content can have a little
只是想说内容可以有点……
bit of a downside and you got to like
有点缺点，你得喜欢
protect against that, but like also go
防范这种情况，但也要像……一样去
full [__] bore into it because who
全力以赴，因为谁
cares? Uh, you'll be forgotten anyways.
关心吗？呃，反正你迟早会被遗忘的。
And, um,
嗯，
&gt;&gt; embarrassment is the price of entry as
尴尬是进入这个行业的必要代价。
they say.
他们说。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And we've all all faced that and had to
我们都面临过这种情况，而且不得不这样做。
go through that to get to the other
穿过那里才能到达另一边
side. Now, I want your content secret.
边。现在，我想要你的内容秘密。
We talk about social media and I think
我们谈到了社交媒体，我认为
um there's been a lot of talk about it
嗯，关于这件事已经有很多讨论了。
shifting really more towards interest
越来越感兴趣了
media rather than social media. Right.
媒体而非社交媒体。正确的。
So I think this is extremely important
所以我认为这非常重要。
because what what Cody was referencing
因为科迪指的是什么？
earlier is again entertainment versus ed
之前又是娱乐与教育的对比。
education. And so Rihanna and Drake I
教育。所以蕾哈娜和德雷克
see both as entertainers. Now what's
将他们都视为艺人。现在是什么？
interesting is that where do they have
有趣的是，他们在哪里？
influence? So she used the word intent
影响？所以她用了“意图”这个词。
but fundamentally I say like how do we
但从根本上说，我想问的是，我们如何……
increase the likelihood that someone
增加某人发生这种情况的可能性
complies with a request or complies with
遵守请求或遵守
a solicitation. Right? Right? If I tell
招揽。正确的？正确的？如果我说
you to do something one, I mean, we've
让你做点什么，我的意思是，我们已经
all seen some creators who have tiny
都见过一些创作者，他们的作品很小。
audiences, but if they say, "Hey, go do
观众，但如果他们说，“嘿，去做……”
this thing." You know, they have 100%,
这东西。”你知道，他们有100%，
not really 100, but they have a huge
其实没到100个，但他们有一个巨大的
conversion on a very small audience. And
在受众规模非常小的情况下实现了转化。和
then other people, you know, I can name
然后还有其他人，你知道，我可以列举出来
some Tik Tockers right now that have,
现在有一些TikTok用户，
you know, 50 plus million uh followers
你知道，超过5000万的粉丝
that have had 13 failed launches because
已经经历了13次发射失败，原因是
they have views, but they have zero
他们有观点，但他们一无所有
influence. No one listens to them for
影响。没人听他们的，因为
their advice.
他们的建议。
&gt;&gt; And so, um, in order to create
所以，嗯，为了创造
influence, there's four things. So,
影响，有四件事。所以，
number one is, and so I just remember
第一点是，所以我只记得
SPCL, right? So, you have status. So
SPCL，对吧？所以，你拥有地位。所以
somebody who controls scarce resources.
掌握稀缺资源的人。
So a bartender at a bar, there's alcohol
所以，酒吧里的调酒师，有酒。
behind them. It's a scarce resource. In
在他们身后。这是稀缺资源。在
the bar, they have status. When they
在酒吧里，他们有地位。当他们
walk outside of the bar, no one cares
走出酒吧，没人会在意。
about them. But in the bar, they have
关于他们。但在酒吧里，他们却有
status, right? So that get so they give
地位，对吧？所以他们就给了
influence. The second is power. And so
影响。第二点是权力。所以
power is basically um say do
权力基本上就是……嗯，说……做
correspondence, meaning if I tell you to
通信，意思是如果我告诉你
do something, follow these instructions,
做点什么，按照这些指示去做。
and a good thing happens, then you I
好事发生后，你我
I'll increase the likelihood that you
我会增加你成功的可能性
comply with requests in the future. And
今后会配合相关要求。和
so like for example, Martha Stewart uh
比如，玛莎·斯图尔特……
was the first self-made female
是第一位白手起家的女性
billionaire. And I think there's there's
亿万富翁。我认为有……
a huge amount of reasons for that. And
原因有很多。和
one of the biggest ones is that she
其中最大的一点是她
literally gave people recipes and they
他们真的给了人们食谱，而且
followed their recipes and they had a
他们按照他们的食谱做了，而且他们还……
good thing happen. And then people told
好事发生了。然后人们就说
them they were great and this cake was
它们都很棒，这个蛋糕也很棒
great and this lasagna was amazing.
太棒了，这道千层面太好吃了。
Their family, their friends, they got
他们的家人，他们的朋友，他们得到了
they also got status. So a massive good
他们也获得了地位。所以这是件好事
thing happened after following explicit
事情发生在遵循明确的指示之后。
directions. And so then when she said
方向。所以当她说
follow my next directions and by this
请按照我的指示行事，并以此方式
thing, people said okay the last 10
事情是，人们说好的，最后10
times I did it, it worked. I'll do this
我这样做过几次，都成功了。我会这么做。
too. And so that's why she had so much
也。所以这就是她拥有那么多东西的原因。
influence. The next is credibility,
影响。其次是信誉度，
which is do you have proof? Right? Now,
你有证据吗？正确的？现在，
all of these can um happen at the same
所有这些事情都可能同时发生。
time or separately. So, I'm trying to
可以同时进行，也可以分开进行。所以，我正在尝试
give more isolated examples for each of
请针对每一项举出更多具体的例子。
them, but like one thing can check
它们，但就像一件事可以检查一样
multiple boxes. So, if I say, "Hey, I
多个箱子。所以，如果我说，“嘿，我
sold a company for $46.2 million." I
以4620万美元的价格出售了一家公司。
have money, which is where the status
拥有金钱，这就是地位的体现。
comes from, but I also have credibility
虽然我来自某个地方，但我也有信誉。
that the stuff that I do works. I
我做的事情确实有效。我
wouldn't have power yet though until I
不过，在我之前，我还没有电力供应。
say, "Hey, if you take what you're
比如说，“嘿，如果你接受你所拥有的……”
currently doing and then add a bonus,
目前正在进行，然后再加上奖金，
urgency, scarcity, a guarantee, you
紧迫性、稀缺性、保证、你
know, think about a value equation, all
知道，想想价值等式，所有
of a sudden you can sell it for way more
突然之间，你就可以把它卖个好价钱了。
money." And then you followed those
钱。”然后你就跟着那些人走了。
instructions and then you do make more
按照说明，然后你就可以制作更多了。
money. Then you're like now I'll be more
钱。然后你就会想，我现在会更……
likely to comply with this person's
可能会遵守此人的……
requests in the future. And so then that
未来的请求。所以，然后就是
person gains influence. And then the the
个人获得影响力。然后是
fourth L is likeness, right? Do they
第四个L是likeness（相似性）吗？他们会吗？
look like me, right? Do they act like
长得像我，对吧？他们表现得像
me? Which is both, you know, physical
我？这既是，你知道的，也是生理上的。
but also psychographic. Like do they
但也包括心理特征。他们真的会这样做吗？
have they share the same values as me?
他们和我拥有相同的价值观吗？
Are they similar? And so if I have two
它们相似吗？所以如果我有两个
people that both have SPC, so they have
两人都患有SPC，所以他们有
status, they have power, they have
他们拥有地位，他们拥有权力，他们有
credibility, and then one of them just
信誉，然后其中一个就……
also looks like me, I'm more likely to
也长得像我，我更有可能
listen to that person. So each of these
听那个人的。所以，这些
are additives. So if you have all four,
是添加剂。所以如果你拥有全部四个，
you'll be more influential, right? And
你会更有影响力，对吧？和
so, um, lading this back up to
所以，嗯，重新装载到
conversion, we think, okay, well, if I'm
转换，我们认为，好吧，如果我是
going to make content with the purpose
打算制作有目的的内容
of conversion, then I want to make stuff
转换之后，我想制作一些东西。
that demonstrates these four things,
这证明了以下四点：
right? And so, that is why educators
正确的？所以，这就是为什么教育工作者
typically have significantly smaller
通常较小
audiences, but can usually
观众，但通常可以
&gt;&gt; generate a lot more money than
比……赚的钱多得多
entertainers can. And entertainers
演艺人员可以。以及演艺人员
typically can monetize almost
通常几乎可以实现货币化
exclusively through sponsorships as the
完全通过赞助作为
most efficient means or vehicle. Now,
最有效的方法或交通工具。现在，
where does an entertainer have
艺人在哪里？
influence? Rihanna is beautiful and so
影响？蕾哈娜很漂亮，而且
she does have credibility in terms of
她在这一点上确实具有可信度。
beauty. She does have um and then
美丽。她确实有，嗯，然后
especially if she starts making content
尤其是如果她开始制作内容的话
around that stuff, she takes her
她带着她的东西，围绕着那些东西。
entertainment audience but she's talking
她是在为娱乐节目做宣传，但她却在谈论……
about something she has credibility to
关于她有信誉的事情
and then she can add power to that
然后她还可以增强这种力量。
because people start following what she
因为人们开始效仿她。
does, right? And then they start looking
确实如此，对吧？然后他们开始寻找
a good way and then they say, you know
一个好办法，然后他们会说，你知道
what, she really does know what she's
什么？她其实很清楚自己是什么。
talking about here. And then all of a
就在这里说。然后所有的一切
sudden when she does point people to,
她突然向人们指出……
you know, to to a thing that that that
你知道，为了做某件事，那件事
they can buy, then they're more likely
他们有能力购买，那么他们就更有可能……
to do so. And so it's it's it's how do
这样做。所以，这就是它，这就是它该怎么做
we merge those two things together? And
我们将这两件事合并起来？和
then when we're making the content, and
然后，当我们制作内容的时候，以及
I think a lot of people we're starting
我认为我们正在开始的很多人都在这样做。
out are very obsessed with views, which
有些人非常痴迷于浏览量，这
I would strongly recommend, especially
我强烈推荐，尤其
in this interest media time, that it's
在这个媒体关注的时代，它是
it's so irrelevant. And what I mean by
这完全无关紧要。我的意思是
that is if we think, all right, I want
也就是说，如果我们认为，好吧，我想要
to I want to start a a bait and tackle
我想开一家渔具店。
drop shipping business, whatever, right?
代发货业务，诸如此类，对吧？
You for for fishermen. Well, if I just
你为渔民服务。嗯，如果我只是
start making videos on philosophy, I
开始制作哲学视频，我
might get way more views than I do if I
如果我这样做，我的浏览量可能会比我多得多。
make, you know, videos on bait and
制作一些关于诱饵的视频，你知道的。
tackle stuff. But the likelihood that
处理事情。但这种可能性
the people who are watching philosophy
观看哲学的人
also want bait and tackle is very low.
鱼饵和渔具的价格也很低。
And because the content is now the
因为内容现在是
targeting for social, like if if
针对社交媒体进行定向，例如如果
anyone's run ads before, you have to
以前投放过广告的人，你必须……
select, okay, I think I want 42 year
选择，好的，我想我想要42年
olds and I want, you know, men and I
老家伙们，还有我想要的，你知道，男人和我
want, you know, whatever, right, as you
想要什么，你知道，随便什么，对吧，就像你
go through it. But the thing is is that
仔细阅读一遍。但问题是……
the algorithms are so good and the AI is
这些算法非常出色，人工智能也是如此。
so good at understanding what the
非常擅长理解
content is about. And they also know
内容是关于什么的。他们也知道
what type of people consume this type of
哪些类型的人会消费这种类型的食物。
content, they just do the targeting for
他们只负责内容投放，其他方面则负责定向推广。
you. And so if you want to reach a
你。所以，如果你想达到
certain type of person, you just only
某些类型的人，你只会……
make content that that certain type of
制作那种特定类型的内容
person wants to consume. It's actually
人有消费欲望。实际上
easier now than it was before. And so
现在比以前容易多了。所以
you can have a 40,000 person audience,
你可以拥有 4 万名观众，
but that 40,000 person audience might be
但那4万名观众可能是
made up entirely of fishermen who buy
完全由购买的渔民组成
tackle, which I'll bet you you'll crush.
擒抱它，我敢打赌你肯定能轻松搞定。
&gt;&gt; And so, um, that is how I kind of see
所以，嗯，这就是我的看法。
the the the quote future of of media at
媒体的未来
least, um, is that if you want to have
至少，嗯，如果你想要拥有
maximum persuasion or conversion power,
最大说服力或转化力
we want to make content that is
我们想制作这样的内容：
explicitly for a specific audience. And
专门针对特定受众。和
we want to demonstrate the proof that
我们想要证明这一点：
we've done, right? We want to have
我们已经做到了，对吧？我们希望拥有
things that they want. We want to give
他们想要的东西。我们想给予
them instructions that they follow that
他们向他们发出指示，让他们遵循这些指示。
good things will happen for them. and we
他们会有好事发生的。我们
want to look like them. And if you do
想长得像他们一样。如果你这样做的话
that, you have somebody who's gonna make
也就是说，你会找到一个能做到这一点的人。
a lot of money from an audience.
来自观众的大量资金。
&gt;&gt; That last point is super interesting as
最后一点非常有趣，
well. How do I make myself look more
出色地。我怎样才能让自己看起来更……
like my audience? And I think
喜欢我的观众吗？我觉得
relatability
亲和力
&gt;&gt; and humanizing yourself is one of the
而使自己人性化是其中之一
great ways to do that.
实现这一目标的绝佳方法。
&gt;&gt; I think it's a very fair point. I mean,
我认为这是一个非常合理的观点。我是说，
I also think it's not just physical
我认为这不仅仅是生理上的问题。
traits. So, you know, let's say that you
特征。所以，你知道，假设你
don't look like the audience that you
看起来不像你的观众
want physically. what are the values
生理上想要。这些值是什么？
that that audience has that you can have
那个观众群体拥有的，你可以拥有
them see themselves in you and and you
他们从你身上看到了自己，而你
know it's kind of like whether or not
我知道这有点像是否
you like the guy who cares but let's say
你喜欢那个关心你的人，但假设
you know Trump for instance really looks
你知道，比如特朗普看起来真的很像
not a lot like his audience
和他的听众不太像
predominantly you know in suits and ties
大多数人都是西装革履的。
constantly sort of a blueblood
一直有点像个贵族
billionaire from the east coast how does
来自东海岸的亿万富翁如何
he associate with this group of people
他与这群人交往密切
when really he doesn't look like them on
但实际上他看起来和他们一点都不像
average well it's because they believe
平均而言，这是因为他们相信
that he has a similar moral compass to
他的道德准则与……相似
them they believe that he has similar
他们认为他有类似的经历。
ethics to them. And so I don't think
对他们来说，这是道德问题。所以我觉得……
that creators have leaned into this
创作者们已经充分利用了这一点。
enough. And I don't mean to become
足够的。我并不想变成
clickbaity or political or or divisive
标题党、政治性或分裂性的
or anything like that. I mean that it is
或者类似的事情。我的意思是，就是这样。
rare to see people in business h take a
很少见到商界人士采取这种做法
stance that could hurt their business
这种立场可能会损害他们的业务。
values, for instance. And Chris and I
例如，价值观。还有克里斯和我
have a rule which is we don't have close
我们有一条规定，那就是我们不关门。
friends that haven't done something
那些还没做过某事的朋友们
publicly that could be against their
公开场合这可能与他们的观点相悖。
best interests. I I just don't want
符合最佳利益。我就是不想
friends that don't have that that
那些没有那种经历的朋友
haven't done that because I think that
我没有那样做，因为我认为……
the world is really hard and I want to
世界真的很艰难，我想
see if somebody's going to have like
看看有没有人想要
moral fiber before I become quite close
在我变得非常亲近之前，我的道德品质至关重要
with them.
和他们一起。
&gt;&gt; Super interesting.
非常有趣。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. And so I I think you could do that
是的。所以我觉得你可以这么做。
as somebody who is a content creator
作为一名内容创作者
today like be value aligned with your
今天就像你的价值观一样。
users and show that and um also to the
用户并显示这一点，嗯，也对
point about the algorithm becoming about
关于算法变得如此重要的观点
interest based. It's also becoming value
基于兴趣。它也变得有价值
based. We're seeing echo chambers emerge
基于。我们看到回音室效应正在出现。
around ways of thinking, right?
围绕思维方式，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Well, I the content that I saw of you
嗯，我看到了你的一些内容。
that most interested me was when you
我最感兴趣的是当你
were talking about um how important
我们在讨论……嗯，这有多重要
ownership is and you were talking about
所有权就是，而你刚才正在谈论的就是所有权。
just the philosophy of ownership and you
仅仅是所有权的理念，还有你
said there's a group of people who want
他说有一群人想要
you to own nothing and be happy about it
你一无所有，却为此感到快乐
&gt;&gt; and I was like I really resonate with
我当时就想，我真的很有共鸣。
that. I want people to own their
那。我希望人们能够拥有自己的
businesses and I want them to own their
企业，我希望他们拥有自己的企业。
stuff. And I liked the fact that you
东西。我喜欢你这一点。
were standing in front of a huge
我们站在一个巨大的……前面
audience taking that position and
持这种立场的观众
everyone knew that it was a little bit
大家都知道这有点……
of a a position to take and it wasn't
应该采取的立场，但事实并非如此。
specifically content about how to build
具体内容是关于如何构建
a business, but you were sharing
一项业务，但你当时在分享
something about yourself.
一些关于你自己的事。
&gt;&gt; I have a belief you don't actually ever
我相信你实际上从未
sell anybody anything. You only find
卖任何东西给任何人。你只会发现
those who are already predisposed to
那些已经倾向于
want the thing that you are selling.
我想要你卖的东西。
&gt;&gt; And if you believe that, then I think
如果你相信这一点，那么我认为
your business gets easier too, easier to
你的生意也会变得更轻松，更容易……
target people. That's why I never kind
目标人群。这就是为什么我从不友善。
of got off on that content. You know,
我对那些内容很感兴趣。你知道，
it's really big online on sales where
它在网上销售非常火爆，
it's like here's how you close them, you
就像这样，你就知道该怎么关它们了。
know, here's how you do this. Here's how
知道了，方法如下。方法如下
you you switch them and you give them a
你把它们交换一下，然后给它们一个
hot dog and then they buy the car
他们先吃热狗，然后买车。
because you gave them the hot dog
因为你给了他们热狗
because of reciprocity and you're like,
因为互惠原则，你会想，
"Huh, I've never bought a car because
“嗯，我从来没买过车，因为……”
somebody gave me a hot dog." But
有人给了我一个热狗。但是
apparently this is what works on
显然，这种方法有效。
Instagram. And so I don't think that's
Instagram。所以我觉得那不是……
actually true. I think you just find
确实如此。我觉得你只是发现
people at a trigger moment that they
人们在触发时刻会……
want something and then you give it to
想要某样东西，然后你就把它给别人。
them.
他们。
&gt;&gt; Mhm. Regarding content, for me
嗯。就内容而言，对我来说
personally,
亲自，
I find that the only reason I'm going to
我发现我去的唯一原因是
create content is if it's in alignment
如果内容符合要求，那就创建内容。
to a mission that I've got. So I don't
我肩负着一项使命。所以我不
actually want to create content. I don't
其实我想创作内容。我不
want to be out there naturally. I would
想自然地融入其中。我会
much rather be a way more private
我宁愿更加注重隐私。
person. Um, and you won't you won't find
人。嗯，你不会找到的。
a lot of stuff about my family or my my
很多关于我的家人或我的事
kids, my you know, very rarely do I post
孩子们，你知道，我很少发帖
anything like any of that sort of stuff.
类似的东西。
But for me, I do it in alignment with
但对我来说，我这样做是符合……的
the mission. I really believe that if
任务。我真的相信如果
you're on a mission, you've got
你肩负使命，你拥有
something you want to achieve in the
你想在……中实现的目标
world, you're going to need other people
世界啊，你需要其他人
to believe in it. You're going to need
相信它。你需要
other people to get involved. Um, you're
让其他人参与进来。嗯，你是
going to want to hire talented people.
想要招到优秀人才。
Those talented people are going to want
那些有才华的人会想要
to, you know, see you online first. And
你知道，这样就能先在网上见到你了。和
it's all about the building
一切都与建筑有关。
relationships at scale. And content is
大规模关系。内容是
just people discovering someone new like
就像人们发现了一个新朋友一样
you would a friend and then getting to
你会和一个朋友，然后……
know someone. And I think the big play
认识某个人。我认为关键在于……
in a postAI world is having really deep
后人工智能时代正在发生深刻的变化。
relationships with a lot of people using
与很多人建立关系
long form content
长篇内容
&gt;&gt; uh where you share who you are, what
呃，你在哪里分享你是谁，什么
you're about, what's your mission,
你是谁？你的使命是什么？
what's your origin story, what's your
你的身世故事是什么？你的
vision,
想象，
&gt;&gt; um what are your values and people then
嗯，你们的价值观和人际交往能力是什么？
say in a very noisy world I will pay
比如说，在一个非常嘈杂的世界里，我会付出代价
attention to what Steven says.
认真听史蒂文说话。
&gt;&gt; I agree. And so to give my answer to
我同意。所以，我的回答是……
this question, my thesis here in the
这个问题，我的论文主题是……
world of AI is actually that if you look
人工智能的世界实际上就是如果你仔细观察的话。
at who has the most loyal engaged fan
谁拥有最忠实、最活跃的粉丝
bases, it's not necessarily podcasters.
基地，不一定是播客。
We're doing pretty well, but it's not
我们做得还不错，但并非完美无缺。
podcasters. Podcasters can sell out
播客主播。播客主播可以出卖自己
arenas and when they go on tour, they
体育馆，当他们巡回演出时，他们
can sell out globally. Streamers.
全球均可售罄。主播。
&gt;&gt; And it's I think it's because of this
我认为这是因为这个原因。
the depth of the parasocial relationship
准社会关系的深度
is the the equity value of the
是股权价值
connection. And I was sat with a
联系。我当时和……坐在一起
streamer who's 18 years old, massive in
18岁的主播，人气爆棚
Europe. And we were on we're playing at
欧洲。我们当时正在玩游戏
Old Trafford for the for the soccer aid.
老特拉福德球场是为了足球援助而建。
And I got just got to sit down with him.
我得和他坐下来好好谈谈。
So I was like, "Explain to me what you
所以我就说：“给我解释一下你是什么意思……”
do." He goes, "So I wake up in the
照做。”他接着说，“所以我醒来时发现自己在……”
morning." I go, "Then what?" He goes, "I
早上好。”我问：“然后呢？”他说：“我
sit there." And I go, "For how long?" He
“就坐在那儿。”我问：“要坐多久？”
goes, "Eight hours." And I go, "What do
说道：“八小时。”然后我就说：“怎么办？”
you do?" He goes, "Like nothing." And I
真的吗？他回答说：“什么都没有。”然后我
go, "How many people tune in?" He's
问：“有多少人收看？”他是
like, "100,000." I'm like, "Concurrently
例如，“100,000”。我心想，“同时
100,000 people sit there with you." He
“有十万人和你一起坐在那里。”
goes, "Yeah, people are quite lonely. I
他说：“是啊，人们都很孤独。”
sit there and what we do is we watch TV
我们坐在那里，然后就看电视。
together." Now the So when when we got
在一起。”现在，所以当我们在一起的时候。
to the the stadium, 70,000 people in the
体育场内有7万人
stadium, we're playing soccer. The
体育场，我们正在踢足球。这
stadium when they announced your name,
体育场，当他们宣布你的名字时，
the size of the cheer correlates to the
欢呼声的大小与……相关
amount of hours you spend with your
你花在身上的时间
audience. The streamers are the
观众。主播们是
celebrities.
名人。
&gt;&gt; The podcasters sometimes come in, but
播客主播们有时会来，但是
the the actors almost, you know, but the
演员们几乎，你知道，但是
but the streamers own the stadium. When
但主播们拥有体育场。什么时候
you play Soccer Aid, it doesn't matter
你参加足球援助赛，这没关系。
how much money you've got or how big
你拥有多少钱，或者你有多大
your following is, the streamers are the
你的粉丝群，也就是主播群
ones. the streamers have this particular
一。主播们有这种特殊之处。
streamer has less of an audience than
主播的观众人数比其他人少。
me, but he sits with them for 7 to 8
我会陪着他，但他会和他们一起坐7到8个小时。
hours a day,
每天数小时，
&gt;&gt; deep connection.
深层联系。
&gt;&gt; So, if we think about depth as the as
所以，如果我们把深度看作是……
the metric that you you can you can
你可以使用的指标
exchange on, especially if you have
继续进行交易，尤其是如果你有
authority in a niche and you're
在某个细分领域拥有权威，你就……
educating, as Alex was saying,
正如亚历克斯所说，这是在进行教育。
&gt;&gt; that's why I think a lot about my behind
这就是为什么我经常想我的屁股
thes scenes channel. I think it's when
这些场景频道。我认为是当
we go on tour, it's so funny. We we do
我们去巡演，真是太有趣了。我们做
we did a tour in Australia and
我们在澳大利亚进行了一次巡回演出，
remarkably I'd say about 50% of people
令人惊讶的是，我认为大约有50%的人
were talking to me about Dario and then
他们当时在跟我谈论达里奥，然后
50% of people were talking to me about
50%的人都在跟我谈论……
behind the diary which is the behind the
日记背后，也就是日记的背后
scenes channel where you get to know me
场景频道，让你了解我
a bit better
好一些了
&gt;&gt; and that that channel has a fraction of
而该频道只占一小部分
the viewership and actually that same
收视率，实际上也是如此。
thesis is the reason I started
论文是我开始写作的原因。
podcasting. I was doing Facebook watch
播客。我当时在看Facebook Watch
videos. They were getting tens of
视频。他们得到了几十个
millions of views, which by the way, no
数百万次的观看量，顺便说一句，没有
one remembers because no one remembered
因为没人记得，所以才有人记得。
any of them. And no one came up to me in
任何一个。没有人走过来和我说话。
the street and said, "I love that
街上，他说：“我喜欢这样。”
two-minute viral philosophical video you
两分钟爆红的哲学视频
made about motivational fluff." No one
都是些励志鸡汤之类的东西。” 没人
ever said that. Then I started this
他曾说过这样的话。然后我开始做这件事
podcast and it got a thousand downloads.
播客节目获得了上千次下载。
And it felt like I was like Oprah
感觉自己就像奥普拉一样。
Winfrey. Like people were coming up to
温弗瑞。就像人们走过来一样
me and I was like, "Oh, there's this
我当时就想，“哦，还有这个
interesting correlation between like the
有趣的关联性，例如
depth of the medium and the resonance
介质深度和共振
and the memorability and therefore the
以及记忆度，因此
value." So just pursue depth as much as
所以，要尽可能地追求深度。
you can. the strength of the parasocial
你可以。准社会的力量
relationship
关系
&gt;&gt; part of the brain that has short-term
大脑中负责短期功能的部分
memory. We've driven a truck through
记忆。我们开着卡车穿过
that.
那。
&gt;&gt; You know, we've now got just hundreds of
你知道，我们现在只有几百个
things a day that hit that. But then
每天都会发生一些事，其中就包括这种情况。但是后来
there's this other part of the brain
大脑还有另一部分。
where I've spent seven hours with
我在那里待了七个小时
someone and if that's the depth.
有人，如果这就是全部的深度的话。
&gt;&gt; Are you guys thinking about that?
你们在考虑这个问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Because you guys, you all make content
因为你们都在创作内容
which is educational but is less
具有教育意义，但较少
personal. And I mean you you two
个人的。我是说你们俩。
podcast, Alex and Cody, you both
播客，Alex 和 Cody，你们俩
podcast. You don't podcast yourself.
播客。你不会自己录制播客。
&gt;&gt; I'm a guest.
我是客人。
&gt;&gt; You're a guest.
您是客人。
but you don't like run your own podcast.
但你不喜欢自己运营播客。
So, are you thinking about a deeper
所以，你是在考虑更深层次的探讨吗？
format for for yourselves? What are you
你们自己用的格式吗？你是做什么的
thinking about?
在想什么？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, there's two things I want to
是的。嗯，我有两件事想说……
talk about there. One, I think it's it's
谈谈那里的情况。第一，我认为是它的
depth, but I would also wonder if it's
深度，但我同时也想知道它是否……
not rawness like in an era in which we
不像我们那个时代那样粗犷
cannot trust what we see anymore because
我们不能再相信我们所看到的了，因为
of AI and anything can be recreated,
人工智能和任何事物都可以被重新创造，
reproduced, and overproduced.
复制和过度生产。
Increasingly, a stream is interesting
溪流越来越有趣了。
because it is raw. it is it is for a
因为它未经加工。它是，它是为一个
thous% whatever is happening on there is
那里发生的一切都百分之千
happening in real time and thus we can
实时发生，因此我们可以
actually trust it and so I think as I
实际上我信任它，所以我认为……
mean we've all seen it content has
意思是我们都看过它的内容了
gotten so produced and overdone and that
变得如此过度制作和矫揉造作，以至于
actually I think decreases trust because
实际上，我认为这会降低信任度，因为
we can't tell if something is real or
我们无法判断某件事是真是假。
not because it's been edited and
并非因为它被编辑过，
filtered and overlaid
过滤和叠加
&gt;&gt; we say with our 40 person teams yeah
我们说，我们40人的团队是这样的。
great
伟大的
&gt;&gt; but it's true but think about think
但这是真的，想想再想想
about the content even like this is like
关于内容，即使像这样也像是
sort of tact practical, but um maybe a
有点策略性，也算务实，但是，嗯，也许是……
year ago, the big content uh change in
一年前，内容方面发生了重大变化
video on Instagram was that you had a
Instagram 上的视频显示你有一个
lot of um B-roll and images overlaid on
很多B卷镜头和叠加的图像
top of videos. And I don't know if you
视频顶部。我不知道你是否
guys have noted, but that doesn't work
有人注意到了，但这行不通。
very well anymore. Actually, the more
现在情况好多了。实际上，越多
that you have third-party assets in your
您在您的账户中拥有第三方资产
video and it's been overdone, the less
视频已经过度使用了，所以越少越好
the video works,
视频可以播放。
&gt;&gt; the more you're just walking along with
你越是随波逐流，就越是如此。
your handout,
你的讲义，
&gt;&gt; right? Because it's it's more real. So,
正确的？因为它更真实。所以，
I think it might actually be like depth
我觉得它可能实际上就像深度一样。
and rawness.
还有那种原始感。
&gt;&gt; Rawness. Yeah. Authenticity, I guess.
原始。是的。我想，大概是为了真实性吧。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. [__] hate that word, but yes.
是的。我真他妈讨厌这个词，但没错。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. It's like 60 minutes versus Joe
是的。这就像《60分钟》对阵乔·乔
Rogan, you know? 60 minutes is like just
罗根，你认识他吗？ 60分钟就像……
it's just
只是
&gt;&gt; no cuts.
不删减。
&gt;&gt; No cuts. Yeah. Yeah.
不删减。是的。是的。
&gt;&gt; And then when it comes to am I thinking
然后，当涉及到“我是否在思考”这个问题时……
about this for our channel? Yeah. I
关于我们频道的相关事宜？是的。我
mean, I think about it. We we have
我的意思是，我会考虑这个问题。我们有
something that we teach everybody which
这是我们教给每个人的东西，
is like the marketing affinity loop. And
就像营销亲和力循环一样。和
and basically it goes like this. I'll
基本上是这样的。患病的
show the graph so you can see it, but
把图表展示出来，这样你就能看到了，但是
you start with awareness, right? And
一切都始于意识觉醒，对吧？和
that awareness is what we're all talking
我们都在谈论的就是这种意识。
about. How do we get more people to just
关于。我们如何才能让更多的人参与进来
see us? And then we go to consideration.
看到我们了吗？然后我们进入考虑阶段。
Okay, I maybe I like this person. Maybe
好吧，我可能喜欢这个人。或许
I'll follow them. I'll give them a quick
我会跟随他们。我会给他们一个快速的
follow. And then we go, well, I actually
跟随。然后我们就去了，嗯，实际上
I like them. I follow them. And I might
我喜欢它们。我关注他们。我或许
buy something from them. Okay, that's
从他们那里买点东西。好的，就是这样。
interesting. And then I might not only
有趣的。然后我可能不仅
buy something from them, but advocate
从他们那里买东西，但要提倡
for them. Write a testimonial, a review,
对他们来说。写一篇客户评价或评论
something like that. And then finally, I
差不多就是这样。最后，我
might be loyal to them. Aka, I'll refer
可能会对他们忠诚。也就是说，我会提到
a friend. I'll sign up for their
朋友。我会报名参加他们的活动。
year-long program. I'll buy again and
为期一年的项目。我会再次购买。
again. And so, we go from awareness to
再次。因此，我们从意识层面走向
consideration to purchase to advocacy to
考虑购买以进行倡导
loyalty. And like, if you can get most
忠诚。而且，如果你能获得大部分
people stop at awareness. Very few
人们止步于意识层面。极少
people can get somebody to go from
人们可以找人从
awareness to purchase. Even fewer people
购买意识。更少的人
can get them to advocate for them, leave
可以让他们为自己发声，离开
a review, and the very very fewest refer
评论，以及极少数的提及
a friend. And so like the holy grail of
朋友。所以就像圣杯一样
business is always have your clients
经营之道在于始终拥有客户。
tell other people nice things about you.
告诉别人你的好话。
And so I think in content, what I think
所以我认为，就内容而言，我认为
about is I don't always care that people
我的意思是，我并不总是在意别人怎么想。
buy things from me at this point. Like I
现在就可以从我这里买东西了。就像我
I love money, don't get me wrong. I want
别误会，我爱钱。我想
to keep making it, but I actually really
继续做下去，但我其实真的
care that they're loyal and they tell
关心他们的忠诚，他们会说
other people about what we're doing. And
告诉其他人我们正在做什么。和
that is something we now measure for
这是我们目前衡量的一个指标。
videos. We can actually now measure with
视频。我们现在实际上可以用……来测量
like a little UTM link how many of all
就像一个小小的 UTM 链接，总共有多少个？
of our videos get shared and how many of
我们的视频有多少被分享，以及有多少……
those shares actually go to a a purchase
这些股份实际上用于购买
or something that goes a little bit
或者说，有点儿……
deeper. And so I I am thinking about
更深。所以，我正在思考……
that. But then I think you also have to
那。但我认为你还必须
decide what's your personal line is. So
确定你的个人底线是什么。所以
for me, I can't imagine wanting to
对我来说，我无法想象自己会想要……
stream all of my life continuously
持续直播我的生活
because I'm not sure that's good for the
因为我不确定这对……是否有好处
audience actually. I think they should
实际上是观众。我认为他们应该
live not watch. So it's like I just have
现场直播，而不是观看。所以就好像我只是……
a line that like I kind of don't want to
一句我不太想说的话
cross.
叉。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And Chris and I actually have a rule
我和克里斯之间其实有个不成文的规定。
too. We only post so much about our
也。我们只会发布这么多关于我们的内容
relationship. We actually because it
关系。实际上，正是因为如此。
always does well. So the team's like
一直都做得很好。所以团队就像
just full send Chris shirtless nipples
克里斯赤裸上身，露出乳头，全力以赴
every day. The internet loves it. And
每天。互联网很喜欢它。和
and and Chris has been really good about
克里斯在这方面真的很好。
saying no, we have to keep some things
即便说不，我们也必须保留一些东西。
sacraant. And so I think you have to
圣餐。所以我认为你必须
decide how deep you want to go down the
决定你想潜入多深
rabbit hole in order to win.
为了赢，掉进兔子洞。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I've I've been the same with my
是的。我一直都和我一样
kids. it's their decision as to whether
孩子们。是否同意由他们决定。
they want to build a profile and how
他们想建立个人档案，以及如何建立个人档案。
they want to build it. So you won't, you
他们想建造它。所以你不会，你
know, I won't put them in that position.
我知道，我不会让他们陷入那种境地。
The depth that I'm loving is writing
我所热爱的深度在于写作。
books because someone who reads a book
书籍，因为读书的人
like you really get to go deep with a
就像你真的可以深入了解一个
book. Um, and also live experiences. So
书。嗯，还有现场体验。所以
every year for the last four years, I've
过去四年，我每年都……
taken about 80 of my clients to the uh
带了大约 80 位客户去……
to the snow and we go skiing. and those
到雪地里，我们去滑雪。以及那些
80 clients who if if someone has gone on
80 位客户，如果有人继续……
my ski trip, the level of loyalty and
我的滑雪之旅、忠诚度和
depth because we've shared fund
因为我们共享了资金，所以有深度。
together, I'm about to take 30 clients
我一共要接待30位客户。
to Neker Island and spend a week with uh
去内克岛和呃一起待一周
Sir Richard. And I' I'm convinced that
理查德爵士。而且我确信
just doing that with 30 people will
仅仅对30个人做这件事就会
build, you know, lifelong like
建立，你知道，终身的
friendships. So this idea that like
友谊。所以这个想法就像
there, you know, that you do stuff in
你知道，就是你做事情的地方。
the online and offline world, you know,
你知道，线上和线下世界都是如此。
that you actually figure out who are the
你实际上要弄清楚谁是
people who are at the core group, those
那些处于核心群体的人，那些
real uh dieh hard fans, and then let's
真正的铁杆粉丝，然后我们……
do something together and and and do fun
一起做点什么，玩得开心
stuff together. Go skiing, go to
把东西堆在一起。去滑雪，去
islands, go sailing, that sort of stuff.
去岛屿游玩，出海航行，诸如此类。
&gt;&gt; Alex, I see you wrote uh it looked like
Alex，我看到你写了“呃，看起来像……”
you drew the universe or something.
你画出了宇宙之类的东西。
&gt;&gt; Oh, I was thinking about um again, it
哦，我又在想那个……
was we're just talking about like
我们刚才只是在谈论……
authenticity. Um, and so with each with
真实性。嗯，所以每个……
each of like SPCL, right, all of them
每个都像SPCL，对吧，所有它们
exist in a continuum, right? And so I
它们存在于一个连续体中，对吗？所以，我
can say credibility. I could say, "Hey,
可以说可信度。我可以说，“嘿，
I sold a company." But I if you see a PR
我卖掉了一家公司。”但如果你看到公关稿
article, that will increase the
这篇文章将增加
credibility. If you were uh somebody you
信誉。如果你是某个人，你
heard about it from somebody else,
我是从别人那里听说的。
that'll increase the credibility of that
这将提高其可信度。
specific credibility driven event.
以信誉为导向的特定事件。
Likeness is the same thing. And so I
相似度也是一回事。所以，我
think um like the connection between
想想看，比如两者之间的联系
streamers and having huge influences
主播和拥有巨大影响力
that they have tremendous likeness and
它们非常相似，而且
that because they are quote authentic
因为它们是引言的真实性
and that there's very few there's
而且数量非常少。
there's very little ability to distort
几乎没有扭曲的能力
you have basically when you what you see
基本上，当你看到什么的时候，你就拥有了你看到的一切。
is what you get. And so if you're the
这就是你所得到的。所以，如果你是
type of person who likes that particular
喜欢那种特定类型的人
streamer then you'll have super strong
如果你是主播，那你就会拥有超强的直播能力。
you know affinity towards them and
你知道你对他们的亲近感，
you'll be likely to you know comply with
你很可能会遵守
their requests like show up to a stadium
他们提出的要求包括到体育场观看比赛。
so that you can support me. Um but you
这样你们就可以支持我了。嗯，但是你
know even authenticity is again a term
甚至连真实性本身也是一个术语。
it's like how do you define authenticity
这就像你如何定义真实性一样。
right which I see is how you how you act
没错，我看到的就是你的行为方式。
when you have no risk of punishment and
当你没有受到惩罚的风险时
so
所以
different way of saying this is like how
另一种说法是，就像……
do you act when you're alone when no one
当你独自一人时，如果没有其他人在场，你会采取行动吗？
else is around and so I see the
周围还有其他东西，所以我看到了
discrepancy between how you behave when
你的行为方式与你的行为方式之间的差异
you're alone and how you behave in
你独自一人，你的行为方式
public as basically your authenticity
公开就是你的真实性
you know score right the question is or
你知道得分正确，问题是或
the problem is that no one really knows
问题在于，没有人真正知道
how you behave when you're alone and so
你独处时的行为等等
&gt;&gt; unless you're
除非你是
unless you're like streaming all the
除非你像我一样整天都在看流媒体
time
时间
&gt;&gt; right yeah and So,
对，是的。
&gt;&gt; so you're saying authenticity is that
所以你的意思是，真实性就是……
there's not a difference between how you
你们的方式之间没有区别。
act when there's when there's no risk of
在没有风险的时候采取行动
punishment and how you act normally. Is
惩罚以及你正常的反应。是
that okay? Got it.
这样可以吗？知道了。
&gt;&gt; Right. And I think that also being like
正确的。而且我觉得这也就像……
very candid for all of us is like they
对我们所有人来说，这非常坦诚，就像他们一样。
were like sure we have audiences that
我们当时就像是，我们肯定有观众。
can punish us with their comments I
他们可以用评论惩罚我们。
guess but our like we've all built
猜猜看，但我们就像我们所有人建立的那样
enough of call it a fortress if you will
如果你愿意的话，就称它为堡垒吧。
of currency network relationships etc
货币网络关系等
that like even even within our companies
甚至在我们公司内部也是如此。
like if you go into the room like I can
就像如果你像我一样走进房间一样
be really authentic in my company
在我的公司里要真正做到真诚。
because no one can fire me right like my
因为没有人能像我一样解雇我
risk of punishment is low is is lower
惩罚风险较低
than saying employees is and So, it's a
与其说是员工，不如说是……所以，这是一个……
a relatively I'd never use this word,
相对而言，我永远不会使用这个词。
but it's a relatively privileged, you
但这是一种相对特权，你
know, um position to be in to to be more
知道，嗯，要处于更有利的位置。
authentic because no one can really
真实性，因为没有人能真正做到
punish you. And I think this is kind of
惩罚你。我觉得这有点像
the the essence of the like [__] you
就像去你的一样，本质就是
money that people want to get to, which
人们想要得到的钱，也就是
is like I just want to be me, but I
我只想做我自己，但我
can't be me because I have this risk of
不可能是我，因为我有这种风险
punishment.
惩罚。
&gt;&gt; And so, um since degrees of freedom
所以，嗯，因为自由度
basically, um I think your happiness is
基本上，嗯，我认为你的幸福是
is very correlated with your degrees of
与你的学位密切相关
freedom.
自由。
&gt;&gt; So, Elon's authentic.
所以，埃隆是真诚的。
&gt;&gt; I mean, I don't think anyone would argue
我的意思是，我觉得没人会反对。
that he's not authentic. They might not
他不够真诚。他们可能不会
agree with him, but I don't think they
我同意他的观点，但我认为他们
think that he's he's trying to pull one.
我觉得他是在耍花招。
&gt;&gt; I do think that when like if you're
我确实认为，当你像……一样的时候
going to go online, one of the ways to
上网是其中一种方法
inoculate yourself against being
做好预防感染的准备
cancelled or to inoculate yourself
取消或接种疫苗
against caring so much is to do
反对如此在意就是要做
ridiculous things every so often that
偶尔会发生一些荒唐事
are super authentic to who you are out
展现你最真实的自我
loud because then what happens is the
大声点，因为接下来发生的事情是……
people that hate you, they leave. Uh and
恨你的人，会离开你。呃，还有
the people that like you kind of like
喜欢你的人有点像你
you a little bit more or trust you a
你多一点，或者更信任你一点
little bit more for it. So I think um
价格略高一些。所以我觉得……
you know one of the things that that I
你知道，其中一件事就是……
do not really on purpose but it it is
并非故意，但确实如此
just like it's like getting a vaccine.
就像打疫苗一样。
You go out on the internet and you say
你上网说
something that you know other people are
你知道其他人是
not going to like but you believe
你不会喜欢，但你相信
strongly in. And when you do that kind
强烈地投入。当你做那种事的时候
of consistently over time I also think
随着时间的推移，我也一直这么认为。
that increases your trust because we've
这会增强您的信任，因为我们有
all met like other creators that you're
你们都像其他创作者一样相遇了。
like
喜欢
&gt;&gt; ah man like you're just never going to
啊，老兄，你好像永远都不会……
say anything that's not PC. Like I can
说任何不符合政治正确的话。就像我可以
think of two in my head where I'm like
我脑海里浮现出两个画面，就像这样：
they're never going to say anything and
他们永远不会说任何话，
if it could hurt their audience, they're
如果这样做会伤害他们的观众，他们就会
not going to say it. And that just
我不会说的。仅此而已
decreases my trust level. And I think
降低了我的信任度。我觉得
the audience is really smart. People are
观众都很聪明。人们是
smart. And so um I think you should
聪明的。所以，嗯，我觉得你应该
inoculate yourself more often.
更频繁地接种疫苗。
&gt;&gt; Before we move on to a little game that
在我们开始玩一个小游戏之前……
I've prepared for us here, um I you're
我已经为我们准备好了，嗯，你……
all very good at pitching and you all
你们都很擅长投球，你们所有人
have your own frameworks for pitching.
建立你自己的推介框架。
&gt;&gt; So I wanted to to pause on that for a
所以我想暂停一下。
second. What is Daniel? What is your
第二。但以理是谁？你的
framework for pitching a business or an
用于推介业务或
idea? There there's two things to start
主意？首先，有两件事需要做。
with which I believe that
我对此深信不疑。
entrepreneurship is the journey of a
创业是一段旅程
thousand pitches. That basically what we
一千次投球。基本上，这就是我们
do as entrepreneurs is we pitch stuff
作为创业者，我们所做的就是推销产品。
into existence. Um and the penalty for
使其存在。嗯，还有处罚
an average pitch is that you do a
平均而言，你做的是
thousand pitches and you get nothing to
投了一千次球，却一无所获。
show for it at the end of it. And the
最后会展示出来。以及
payoff for a great pitch is that you do
好的推销的回报是，你确实
a thousand pitches and you end up with
一千次投球后，你最终会得到
10 to$100 million. You end up with an
1000万至1亿美元。你最终得到一个
amazing team of people and lots of
一个非常棒的团队，还有很多
customers and everything everything's
顾客和一切的一切
great. I think treat entrepreneurship as
伟大的。我认为应该把创业视为
the journey of a thousand pitches and
千音之旅
also treat pitching as
也将投球视为
this magical thing where you get what
这种神奇的东西，你能得到什么
you pitch for and you can't switch it
你投出的球，你不能换。
off. So for example, if you say the
离开。例如，如果你说
economy is bad, the economy is bad, the
经济形势不好，经济形势不好，
economy is bad, as if by magic the
经济形势很糟糕，仿佛一夜之间……
economy is going to be bad. Uh if you
经济形势会很糟糕。呃，如果你
say I'm seeing lots of opportunities
我说我看到了很多机会
right now, I'm seeing lots of
现在，我看到很多
opportunities right now. You you start
现在就是机会。你开始
conversations where people go, oh I I've
对话中人们会说，哦，我，我
seen an opportunity as well. So,
我也看到了机会。所以，
whatever you're out there talking about,
不管你们在外面谈论什么，
you tend to bring those conversations to
你往往会把这些对话引向……
the surface and then it's a
表面，然后就是一个
self-fulfilling loop. With that said,
自我实现的循环。也就是说，
you have to have a framework for
你必须有一个框架
pitching. If you're going to do a good
投球。如果你想做好
pitch, it's got to be a framework. I've
提案必须有一个框架。我已经
got social pitching framework, scheduled
已制定社交推广框架，并已安排好
pitching framework, and sales pitching
推销框架和销售推销
framework. So, social pitch, name, same,
框架。所以，社交宣传、名称，都一样。
fame, pain, aim, game.
名誉、痛苦、目标、游戏。
&gt;&gt; What's a social pitch?
什么是社交推介？
&gt;&gt; Social pitch is on social media.
社交推广是指在社交媒体上进行推广。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. or um in a social situation, it's
是的。或者，嗯，在社交场合中，它是
basically a situation where you've got
基本上，你遇到的情况是这样的：
about 30 seconds before someone thinks
大约在有人思考之前30秒
that you're being uh too obtuse.
你真是太迟钝了。
&gt;&gt; Okay?
好的？
&gt;&gt; Right? So, you've got about 30 seconds
正确的？所以，你还有大约30秒时间。
of people's attention, and you're going
吸引人们的注意力，然后你就走了
to say, "What is your name? What are you
问：“你叫什么名字？你是做什么的？”
the same as that they already
和他们之前的情况一样
understand? What makes you famous or
理解？是什么让你出名？
different? Uh what are you aiming for
不同的？呃，你的目标是什么？
right now? What's your bigger game? Or
现在？你更大的目标是什么？或者
what pain do you solve? What are you
你解决了什么痛点？你是做什么的
aiming for? What's your bigger game?"
目标是什么？你更大的目标是什么？
So, there's a few things you can put in
所以，你可以添加一些东西
there and it rhymes so you can remember
就在那里，而且押韵，所以你很容易记住。
it in a in a social situation. scheduled
在社交场合中。已安排
pitches, I always do something called
在推销产品时，我总是会做一些叫做……的事情
capstone. And it's clarity, authority,
毕业设计。而且是清晰度、权威性，
problem, solution, traction, or the why,
问题、解决方案、进展或原因
either way, opportunity, next steps, and
无论如何，机会、下一步以及
an emotional ending. Right? So, that
一个感人的结局。正确的？以便
spells out capstone. Now, is that the
拼写为capstone。现在，那就是……
best pitching framework? Maybe, maybe
最佳推介框架？也许，也许
not. Maybe there's better frameworks.
不是。或许还有更好的框架。
But the point is is that you've got a
但重点是，你已经拥有了
framework that you're not just winging
构建一个框架，让你不再只是凭感觉行事。
it. You're not just, you know, randomly
它。你并非只是，你知道，随机地
spewing words. you've actually gone
滔滔不绝地讲着话。你真的走了
through the process of thinking through
通过思考的过程
your pitch uh in a framework approach.
你的推介方式是框架式的。
One thing that's really fascinating is
真正令人着迷的一件事是
the three of us have a framework for
我们三人有一个框架……
everything like we we're just like very
一切都像我们一样，我们就像非常
framework thinkers and I've noticed that
框架思考者们，我注意到……
with a lot of entrepreneurs. Um do you
有很多创业者。嗯，你呢？
guys have pitching frameworks? Be
各位，你们有推销框架吗？是
shocked if you didn't.
如果你没注意到，我会很惊讶。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I do. I mean I think I'm like lazy
是的，我有。我的意思是，我觉得自己有点懒。
intellectually and frameworks help you
从智力上和框架上帮助你
remember things and so if you don't have
记住事情，所以如果你没有
very good memory then it's just easy to
如果记忆力很好，那就很容易了。
put it in something that can make sure
把它放在一个可以确保……的地方
that you remember it. It's why when we
你记得这件事。这就是为什么当我们
were in school, you know, they used to
他们还在上学的时候，你知道，他们过去常常
make us sing songs about how to remember
让我们唱起关于如何记住的歌
the varian states. If if if I wanted to
瓦里安州。如果如果我想
raise a bunch of money from other people
从其他人那里筹集一大笔钱
that didn't know me and I wanted to
那个人不认识我，而我想……
never have a problem raising money
筹款从来不成问题
again, I didn't want to use any of my
再说一遍，我不想用我的任何
money ever, I would use what I learned
即使没有钱，我也会运用我所学到的东西。
in venture capital, which is the
在风险投资领域，即
mightest touch. And and basically, I
最有可能的触碰。基本上，我
think you need one of these four in
你觉得你需要这四个中的一个吗？
order to raise money. You don't have to
筹集资金的命令。你不必
have all four, but if you do, that makes
如果你拥有全部四个，那就意味着
it really, really easy. The easiest one
真的非常简单。最简单的
is profit, right? If you have a business
就是利润，对吧？如果你有一家企业
right now that's making money profit in
现在这正在盈利
your pocket, you can raise capital. You
你可以用自己的钱筹集资金。你
can raise money from people as long as
只要能够从人们那里筹集资金，就可以这样做。
that amount that you're raising is
你筹集的金额是
reasonable to the amount of profit. If
与利润数额相符。如果
you don't have any profit, but you have
你没有任何利润，但你有
growth, let's say like Replet, we were
增长，比如说像Replet那样，我们曾经是
talking about a big AI company, great.
谈论的是一家大型人工智能公司，很好。
You can raise a bunch of money if you
如果你这样做，你可以筹集到一大笔钱。
got growth, too. The third thing, if you
也实现了增长。第三件事，如果你
don't have either one of those, you
你两者都没有，你
don't have profit, you don't have
没有利润，你就没有
growth, but you have a history. I've
你既有成长，也有历史。我已经
sold a company before. I've built this
我之前卖过一家公司。我已经建造了这个
before. you can raise purely on the fact
前。你可以仅凭这一事实就提出上诉。
that you've done this before. And if you
你以前做过这件事。如果你
haven't done any of those three, you've
如果你这三件事都没做过，你就……
done nothing in life, then you need a
如果你的人生一事无成，那么你需要一个
really good story. And the story is
故事很精彩。故事是这样的
something that you can often raise money
你通常可以通过某种方式筹集资金
off of. So I believe that we are going
关掉。所以我相信我们会走
to create the next XYZ. And if we do
创造下一个XYZ。如果我们这样做的话
this thing, then you will all make
这件事，你们都会去做。
money, I will make money, and we will
钱，我会赚钱，我们会……
change the world together. And so I call
携手改变世界。所以我打电话
it the touch because I think people who
触摸是因为我认为人们
accum if you can accumulate this over
如果你能积累这些，那就积累吧
your life, it's not that hard, right? So
你的生活其实没那么难，对吧？所以
eventually at some point you'll have a a
最终，在某个时候你会拥有一个
history which is your proof. Then you
历史就是最好的证明。然后你
can craft a story. You'll get better at
能够创作故事。你会越来越擅长
it as you continue to grow. You will
随着你的不断成长，它会越来越好。你会
learn how to get profit in some way. And
学习如何通过某种方式获利。和
because you've driven profit before,
因为你之前已经创造过利润，
you'll know how to get growth. So I
你会知道如何实现增长。所以，我
think like almost any entrepreneur over
像几乎所有企业家那样思考
time, if you focus on those four things,
如果你专注于这四件事，时间就会缩短。
can raise money. And you start with only
可以筹集资金。而你一开始只有
the story when you have nothing.
当你一无所有时的故事。
&gt;&gt; Alex, I have a lot of pitching.
亚历克斯，我有很多投球机会。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Um I I I'll say first and foremost like
嗯，首先我想说的是……
if you're trying to sell anyone
如果你想卖东西给任何人
anything, um proof will always be
任何事，嗯，证据永远都会是
promised. And I can say that, you know,
答应了。我可以这么说，你知道，
a thousand times in a row. Like you
连续一千次。就像你一样
could literally say nothing, get on
完全可以什么都不说，继续前进
stage and then just hit next on
进入下一阶段，然后点击“下一步”。
testimonials for 60 minutes and you will
听取60分钟的客户证词，你将
close a percent. Like literally the last
成交量达到百分之几。就像最后一次一样
slide just says like go over there to go
幻灯片上只写着“去那边走”。
buy something and you could say nothing
买点东西，你就可以什么都不说了。
and you will you will sell.
你会卖掉的。
&gt;&gt; Why?
为什么？
&gt;&gt; Because I think um proof acts as a as a
因为我认为嗯，证据起到了一种作用……
as a an an approximation of something
作为某种事物的近似值
that would happen uh for the prospect.
这对潜在客户来说就是如此。
And so like the only reason that like
所以，唯一的原因就是
that proof works is that they think, oh,
这个证明有效的地方在于，他们认为，哦，
some element of this is like me. And so
这其中有些元素与我相似。所以
if I do the same thing that this person
如果我做和这个人一样的事
did, and the closer the proof is to the
确实如此，而且证据越接近……
prospect, the more compelling it is for
前景越是令人信服，就越有吸引力。
that specific prospect, which is like
那个具体的前景，就像
when we used to um, you know, run ads
当我们过去投放广告的时候……你知道的
for different markets, we'd go into
针对不同的市场，我们会进入
like, you know, an entirely black market
就像，你知道的，一个完全黑市
and surprise surprise, if we had black
令人惊讶的是，如果我们有黑色
testimonials, the pages would convert
用户评价，页面转化率会提高。
better than if we had white testimonials
比我们有白人证词要好得多
and then flip-flop in the other
然后又反过来
direction, too. And so, right, and so we
方向也是。所以，没错，所以我们
want to show as many different types of
想展示尽可能多的不同类型的
proof as we possibly can. And obviously,
尽可能提供证据。显然，
not all proof is created equal. You can
并非所有证据都具有相同的价值。你可以
have live proof versus recorded proof.
有现场证据，也有录像证据。
You can have a demonstration of
您可以观看演示
something that like us using the thing
就像我们使用那个东西一样。
is going to be more compelling uh than
将会比……更有吸引力
than than not using and just describing
与其不使用而只是描述，不如使用
it, right? If I have a um like and so
对吧？如果我有一个嗯，比如，所以
there's there's a bunch of things on
有很多东西
proof. But that's just like big thing
证明。但那只是件大事。
number one. And so that's why for me if
第一。所以对我来说，如果
somebody's going to sell something, I
有人要卖东西，我
recommend most people just get five or
建议大多数人只买五件或
10 clients for free up front with the
预付10个客户免费
primary purpose of getting proof because
获取证据的主要目的在于
you're going to make more money on the
你会在以下方面赚到更多钱：
proof than you will have trying to, you
你尝试之后会发现，这比你实际拥有的证据要多得多。
know, just get the the tiny amount that
知道，只要得到那一点点就行了。
you can charge with absolutely no proof.
即使没有任何证据，你也可以提出指控。
Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; So, it's like, don't do that. Just get
所以，我的意思是，别那样做。就这么办
10 and on your 11th, you'll be able to
10岁，到11岁，你就可以……
charge 10 times more because you'll be
收费提高10倍，因为你会……
able to say, "Hey, look at the 10 people
能够说：“嘿，看看这10个人。”
that I helped." And realistically,
我帮了忙。” 而实际上，
you'll get more out of that than they
你会从中得到比他们更多的好处
will because you probably suck.
因为你可能很菜。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; So, so it's probably for everyone's best
所以，这或许对大家都有好处。
interest that you don't charge anything.
你不收取任何费用，利息却很低。
Um, but from an actual like closing
嗯，但从实际的结束方式来看
perspective, and I'll talk about this
视角，我会谈谈这个。
from a from appointments, I think to use
从预约的角度来看，我认为应该使用
uh Daniel's language, I've taught the
呃，丹尼尔的语言，我教过……
closer framework for a very long time.
长期以来，框架一直很紧密。
Um, which is C L O S E R. Uh, and so C
嗯，就是 C L O S E R。呃，所以 C
is clarify why they're there, which is,
就是要解释清楚他们为什么在那里，那就是：
and typically anybody who's going to be
通常情况下，任何要……的人
in that appointment has taken some
那次任命花了一些时间。
action. So whether that's they
行动。所以，不管那是不是他们
responded, you know, to a post, they
他们回复了帖子，你知道，他们回复了帖子。
commented, they liked, they actually, I
评论了，他们喜欢，他们实际上，我
mean, if someone's already set an
意思是，如果有人已经设定了一个
appointment or they walked in the door,
无论是预约还是直接走进门，
like there's always some like why'd you
总会有人问你为什么
pick up the phone? Like there's always
接电话？就像总是有……
some reason like, "Why'd you give me 5
诸如“你为什么给我5分”之类的理由
seconds?" There's always something
几秒钟？总会有事发生。
they've done that you could say, "Hey,
他们已经做到了，你可以说，“嘿，
so tell me why, right?" And so then
所以告诉我为什么，对吧？”然后就……
you're you're you're clarifying why
你正在解释原因
they're there, why they're still
它们就在那里，为什么它们还在？
listening. So you listen to them because
正在听。所以你听他们的，因为
we often think about sales as me just
我们通常认为销售就是我。
hitting you with [__]
用他妈的
&gt;&gt; So the perfect salesman says nothing and
所以，完美的推销员什么也不说。
only ask questions
只问问题
&gt;&gt; because there's nothing to disagree
因为没有什么可反对的。
with.
和。
&gt;&gt; And fundamentally they're going to
从根本上讲，他们将会
believe way more of what they say than
比起
what you say. So you want them to say
你说的话。所以你想让他们说
it, not you. And so you clarify whether
它，不是你。所以你要澄清一下是否
they're there. See,
它们就在那里。看，
&gt;&gt; it reminds me of spies. I've interviewed
这让我想起了间谍。我采访过
a couple of CIA spies now and every
现在有几个中央情报局间谍，而且每个
single one of them, I was expecting some
我原本期待的是其中任何一个。
like incredible technique or whatever.
比如高超的技巧之类的。
They all say, "No, we just spend six to
他们都说：“不，我们只是花了六个小时。”
eight weeks in the back of the cab
在驾驶室后座待了八周
listening to the Iranian taxi driver to
听着伊朗出租车司机说话
figure out what that his son has a
弄清楚他儿子有什么事
health issue that we can then leverage
我们可以利用的健康问题
later to get him to turn against his
后来让他背叛他
country." For the first eight weeks,
国家。”在前八周，
you're just listening to him offload.
你只是在听他倾诉而已。
And they're like, "It's crazy how people
他们会说：“人们的行为真是太疯狂了。”
will just offload if you let them.
如果你放任不管，他们就会卸货。
Everyone wants to talk."
每个人都想说话。
&gt;&gt; Oh, 100%. So, one is, you know, clarify
哦，百分之百。所以，第一点是，你知道，要澄清。
where they're l is label them with a
它们所在位置的标签是a
problem that you can solve. So it's like
你可以解决的问题。所以就像
okay so it sounds like you're here you
好的，听起来你在这里。
respond to my ad you DM me thing or you
回复我的广告，你私信我，或者你
you whatever it because of this reason
你不管它是什么，都是因为这个原因
is that right? Right. So you get
是这样吗？正确的。所以你得到
confirmation on the problem uh which is
关于问题的确认，呃，就是这个。
L. Then you O which is overview past
L. 然后你 O，这是对过去的概述。
experiences or past pain. So it's like
经历或过去的痛苦。所以就像
what have you done so far to try and
为了尝试……，你目前做了哪些努力？
solve this? And this is important
解决这个问题吗？这一点很重要
because uh motivation is the equal
因为呃，动机是相等的。
opposite of deprivation. So the more
与匮乏相反。所以越多
deprive someone is of something the more
剥夺某人的某些东西，就更甚。
motivated they are to solve it. And so
他们有动力解决这个问题。所以
like if you haven't eaten in an hour
比如你已经一个小时没吃饭了。
you're probably not that motivated. If
你可能动力不足。如果
you haven't eaten in two days you're
你已经两天没吃饭了。
very motivated. If you haven't slept in,
非常有动力。如果你还没睡懒觉，
you know a day or you're normal
你知道，一天下来，你很正常。
motivated. I guess that was a bad one.
积极主动。看来那次不太顺利。
But if you haven't slept in 3 days,
但如果你三天没睡觉了，
you'll be incredibly motivated to sleep.
你会非常渴望睡觉。
And so we want to find we want to find
所以，我们想要找到，我们想要找到
what they're deprived of and then try to
他们被剥夺了什么，然后试图
increase that deprivation uh in the
加剧这种匮乏感
conversation. Basically, uh make them
对话。基本上，呃，制作它们
more aware of the deprivation, the
更加意识到匮乏，
things that they don't have, right? Then
他们没有的东西，对吧？然后
once we have, you know, enough
一旦我们拥有了足够的……
deprivation that it's very clear it's
很明显，这是一种匮乏感。
like, okay, this is this is what why
好吧，这就是原因
you're here. This is you agreed with
你在这里。这是你同意的
this is the problem that you want to
这就是你想解决的问题。
solve. You've tried all these things and
解决。你已经尝试过所有这些方法了，
it hasn't worked for you. I can imagine
它对你不起作用。我能想象
how frustrating that would be. Um S,
那该有多么令人沮丧啊。嗯，S，
which is then you sell, right? you sell
然后你就卖掉了，对吧？你卖
the vacation, which typically is just
假期，通常只是
three points. Um I I usually keep it to
三分。嗯，我通常会把它保留下来
three cuz most people can't remember
三个，因为大多数人记不住。
more than that anyways. And the three
远不止这些。还有这三个人
points are usually you can always find
通常情况下，你总能找到一些要点。
three. And if you need two, you can
三。如果你需要两个，你可以
chunk up if you've got five. And if
如果你有五个，就分摊开来。如果
you've got, you know, two chunk down as
你知道，你已经砍掉了两块。
in like break into smaller pieces. But
就像碎成小块一样。但
like when I was in the fitness world, it
就像我以前在健身界的时候一样，
was fitness, nutrition, accountability.
是健身、营养和责任感。
If when I was selling, you know,
如果我当时在卖东西的时候，你知道，
mortgage leads, it's like you want the
抵押贷款线索，就像你想要的那样
leads to be unique, you want them to be
为了让它们独一无二，你希望它们如此。
timely, and you want them to be
及时，而且你希望它们
exclusive, right? And so like or
独家报道，对吧？所以就像或
qualified. And so it's like there's
合格的。所以就好像……
always three things that you can usually
通常总有三件事你可以做到
triangulate. But when you say the three
三角测量。但当你提到这三个时
points, you don't then feature, you
积分，你就不会出现，你
know, Jarble about the the points. You
贾布尔知道这些要点。你
then just usually put like a one
然后通常就写一个一
sentence analogy of of what that thing
用句子类比那个东西
is. So, it's kind of like this. And so,
是。大概是这样的。所以，
these are like little 30 secondond sound
这些就像是30秒的短音频。
bites to make the three points. That
咬三口，拿下三分。那
should never last longer than 90 seconds
持续时间不应超过90秒
cuz um most people waste all this time
因为大多数人都浪费了这些时间
on the selling part and that doesn't
在销售方面，但这并没有……
really matter because the more we can
这一点至关重要，因为我们能做的越多，就越能……
talk about them, the more they're going
谈论它们，它们就越会走。
to want to buy. Um and then E, like at
想要购买。嗯，然后是E，就像在
the end of that, you say, "Cool, ready
最后，你会说：“酷，准备好了。”
to get started, ready to rock and roll,
准备开始，摇滚起来！
ready to start on Monday, whatever it
无论如何，我已经准备好从周一开始工作了。
is." And then E, E and R around what
是。”然后是E、E和R围绕着什么
happens if they say no, right? You
如果他们拒绝会发生什么，对吧？你
explain it with their concerns. E, and
解释他们的顾虑。 E，以及
then R is you reinforce the decision.
那么 R 就是你强化了这一决定。
And so R was actually something I added
所以R实际上是我后来添加的。
much later when I was teaching, you
很久以后，当我教书的时候，你
know, many sales people because um after
我知道，很多销售人员都是因为……之后
they would like explain away and then
他们会想方设法解释，然后
close, they would just like see you
走近了，他们只是想见你。
later. I got the credit card. It's like
之后。我拿到信用卡了。就像
you're dead to me. Um but the R is like
你对我来说已经死了。嗯，但是R就像
no, no, like reinforce the decision like
不，不，就像强化这个决定一样
I think it's a great decision. I'm going
我认为这是一个非常好的决定。我要去
to introduce you to Polly. Paulie's
向大家介绍波莉。保利的
going to get you onboarded. And then
我会帮你完成入职流程。进而
Polly also continues the R and being
Polly 也继续 R 和 being
like you know Jack definitely helped you
你知道，杰克肯定帮了你很多忙。
out. Let me let's get you all squared
出去。让我来帮你把一切都理顺。
away.
离开。
There's no safe like Simply Safe, the
没有比 Simply Safe 更安全的了。
sponsor of today's episode. A few years
今天的节目赞助商。几年
ago, someone broke into the Diary of a
很久以前，有人闯入了……的日记。
SEO studio and stole all of our cameras
SEO工作室偷走了我们所有的相机。
and a few key hard drives, and it was
还有几块关键的硬盘，就是这样。
devastating and one that led us on a
令人痛心，也让我们陷入了困境
quest to figure out how we could secure
探索如何确保安全
our building. And through this, we
我们的大楼。通过这一点，我们
discovered Simply Safe. Interestingly,
发现了Simply Safe。有趣的是，
we did have security at the time, but
当时我们确实有保安，但是
the type that we had only triggered an
我们遇到的那种类型只会触发一个
alarm once intruders were inside the
入侵者进入室内后会发出警报。
building. What I like about Simply Safe
建筑。我喜欢Simply Safe的原因
is their active guard outdoor protection
他们的主动防护措施是户外防护。
notifies you and their live monitoring
通知您并进行实时监控
agents when suspicious characters are
当可疑人物出现时，特工们会……
outside, but it also means that guards
外面，但也意味着守卫
can trigger alarms or turn on spotlights
可以触发警报或打开聚光灯
to deter someone from entering your
阻止某人进入你的
building. If we had had Simply Safe, we
建筑。如果我们当初买了Simply Safe保险，我们
would have known earlier that intruders
本来应该更早知道入侵者
were trying to get in. So maybe this is
我们当时正试图进去。所以也许这是
your reminder to make sure your home and
提醒您确保您的家和
workplace is secure. Simplysafe is
工作场所安全。 Simplysafe 是
offering my listeners in the United
向我在美国各地的听众致谢
States an exclusive discount of 50% off
提供独家五折优惠
their new Simplysafe security system
他们的新Simplysafe安全系统
when you sign up by visiting
当您通过访问网站注册时
simplysafe.com/doac
simplysafe.com/doac
to claim 50% off your new system with a
使用以下方式购买新系统可享受 50% 的折扣：
professional monitoring plan and get
专业监控计划并获得
your first month free. That's
首月免费。那是
simplysafe.com/doac.
simplysafe.com/doac。
There's no safe like Simply Safe.
没有比Simply Safe更安全的了。
I've just invested millions into this
我刚刚在这上面投入了数百万美元。
and become a co-owner of the company.
并成为公司的共同所有人。
It's a company called Ketone IQ. And the
这是一家名为 Ketone IQ 的公司。以及
story is quite interesting. I started
故事很有趣。我已开始
talking about ketosis on this podcast
本期播客节目讨论了生酮饮食。
and the fact that I'm very low carb,
而且我严格控制碳水化合物的摄入量，
very, very low sugar, and my body
血糖非常非常低，而且我的身体
produces ketones which have made me
产生酮体，这使我
incredibly focused, have improved my
注意力高度集中，我的
endurance, have improved my mood, and
耐力增强了，心情也改善了，而且
have made me more capable at doing what
使我更有能力去做什么
I do here. And because I was talking
我在这里。因为我当时正在说话。
about it on the podcast, a couple of
在播客节目中谈到这件事，有几个
weeks later, these showed up on my desk
几周后，这些东西出现在我的桌子上。
in my HQ in London, these little shots.
这些小照片是我在伦敦总部拍摄的。
And oh my god, the impact this had on my
我的天哪，这件事对我的影响太大了
ability to articulate myself, on my
我表达自己的能力，就我而言
focus, on my workouts, on my mood, on
专注于我的锻炼，我的情绪，以及
stopping me crashing throughout the day
防止我全天崩溃
was so profound that I reached out to
这件事意义如此重大，以至于我主动联系了……
the founders of the company and now I'm
公司创始人，现在我是
a co-owner of this business. I highly,
这家公司的共同所有人之一。我非常，
highly recommend you look into this. I
强烈建议你调查一下。我
highly recommend you look at the science
强烈建议你看看这方面的科学研究。
behind the product. If you want to try
产品背后的故事。如果你想尝试
it for yourself, visit
亲自去看看吧。
ketone.com/stephven
ketone.com/stephven
for 30% off your subscription order. And
订阅订单可享七折优惠。和
you'll also get a free gift with your
你还会获得一份免费礼物
second shipment. That's
第二批货物。那是
ketone.com/stephven.
ketone.com/stephven。
And I'm so honored that once again, a
我非常荣幸，再一次，
company I own can sponsor my podcast. A
我拥有的公司可以赞助我的播客。一个
lot of people say that 70 60 80% of our
很多人说我们70%、60%、80%的人
communication is body language. Do you
沟通也包括肢体语言。你
think much about that, Alex? You have a
你仔细想过这个问题吗，亚历克斯？你有一个
with or without you energy body
无论你的能量体是否存在，它都能发挥作用。
language. It's a casual It's a very
语言。这是一种随意的，这是一种非常
casual body language, which in fact
随意的肢体语言，实际上
reinforces your authority in a way. So
在某种程度上，这能增强你的权威。所以
do you think about if people are right
你会思考人们是否正确吗？
that 60 or 70% of our communication is
我们60%到70%的沟通是
the things we don't say. Do you think
我们没说出口的话。你觉得
about training people on how to hold
关于培训人们如何持有
themselves, how to be you kind of
他们自己，如何成为你那种人
alluded to something there which I think
那里暗示了某些事情，我认为
people don't think about which is
人们不会去想哪个是
actually the less you say sometimes the
其实有时候少说话反而更好。
higher conviction and the more I believe
信念越坚定，我就越相信
you.
你。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And some people can oversell because
有些人可能会过度推销，因为
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, I'll So, I'll because I think
是的。所以，我会，因为我认为
getting So, I'll just There's so many
所以，我只想说，有很多……
variables here, but I'll just try and
这里有很多变量，但我会尽量尝试。
focus on the ones that um a lot of
专注于那些……很多
people sell over the phone and even via
人们通过电话甚至通过其他方式进行销售。
Zoom, it's harder to see body language
放大后，肢体语言就很难看清了。
as well, which nowadays I think a lot of
而且，现在我觉得很多
selling happens in those two
销售发生在这两个地方。
environments, even more than in person,
环境，甚至比现实生活中更甚，
even though that's where I came from,
虽然我就来自那里，
which I actually think is the best place
我个人认为那才是最好的地方。
to learn because you have to control
学习是因为你必须控制
every variable. And then you have far
每个变量。然后你就远远地
more leeway on the phone or on Zoom than
在电话或Zoom会议上比在电话会议中拥有更大的灵活性
you do in person.
亲自去做。
&gt;&gt; And so, to that extent, um there's
所以，从这个程度上来说，嗯，是这样的
basically five things you can control
基本上，你可以控制五件事。
about how you talk. And so you have your
关于你的说话方式。所以你就有了你的
speed of talking, like how t how fast
说话速度，比如语速快慢
you talk. You have your cadence. You
你说话。你有自己的节奏。你
have your um basically your um your
基本上，你的嗯，你的嗯
annunciation, like do I pronounce every
发音，比如我是否应该发音每一个
letter in the words that I'm saying? You
我说的这些话里，哪个字最能代表你？你
have the volume that you speak at
保持你说话时的音量
because if I talk too low like you on a
因为如果我像你一样说话声音太小……
phone, it doesn't really matter because
手机其实并不重要，因为
they're just going to increase the
他们只会增加
volume. But if I lower what I'm saying
体积。但如果我降低音量说话呢？
right now, it sounds more important in
现在看来，这似乎更重要。
person. It's more important to volume is
人。更重要的是销量。
more important in person. And so those
面对面交流更重要。所以那些
first three I consider there's kind of a
前三个我认为有点……
persuasive tone which all three are
这三者都具有说服力。
constant. And the only point of those is
持续的。而这些的唯一意义在于
to maximize comprehension. It's just
为了最大限度地理解。只是
that they can hear you, that they can
他们能听到你说话，他们能
understand what you're saying because
我明白你的意思，因为
you're talking in a speed that they can
你的语速快到他们能听懂。
understand. Like I'm somebody who talks
理解。就像我是个爱说话的人一样
fast and I have to I have to pull back
速度很快，我必须，我必须退缩
how fast I talk when I'm in like a
当我像……一样说话时，我的语速非常快。
selling situation. There's only two that
销售情况。只有两个
you that I teach sales people to try and
我教销售人员要努力做到……
actively control, which is going to be
积极控制，这将是
pauses
停顿
to draw attention
吸引注意力
and when do I raise my voice.
我什么时候可以提高嗓门？
And the reason that those are the only
而原因就在于，这些是唯一的
two things you really need to teach a
有两件事你真的需要教给A
salesperson outside of the persuasive
不具说服力的销售人员
tone, which is that that you're going to
语气，也就是你要……
talk at a certain speed, which usually
以一定的语速说话，这通常
about 150 to 170 words a minute, because
大约每分钟150到170个单词，因为
that's the amount of speed that most
这是大多数人能达到的速度。
people can understand. You're going to
人们都能理解。你要去
enunciate the words, which is going to
清晰地发音，这将会
force you to actually speak at that
迫使你真的开口说话
speed.
速度。
&gt;&gt; Um, and you're going to talk loud enough
嗯，而且你要大声说话。
they can understand you. This sounds
他们能听懂你的话。这听起来
very simple, right? Like this sounds
很简单，对吧？听起来像这样
like so simple, like I can't believe
就这么简单，简直难以置信
people don't do this. Except they don't
人们不会这样做。但他们并没有。
and they don't close. And so the only
而且它们不关门。因此，唯一
things that you have to teach a
你必须教给……的东西
salesperson and these are so important.
销售人员，这些都非常重要。
Like there's been three independent
就像已经有三个独立的
studies that are like massive
类似大规模研究
metaanalyses of sales people,
销售人员的荟萃分析，
the sales people who one speak less
那些少说话的销售人员
close more. And number two, the sales
关闭更多。第二，销售额
people who know when to shut up most
最懂得何时闭嘴的人
importantly after you ask for the sale,
重要的是，在你提出销售请求之后，
like if you wait 8 seconds after you ask
比如，你问完问题后等8秒钟。
someone to buy, you close 30% more sales
如果有人想买，你的成交量会提高 30%。
&gt;&gt; if you wait 8 seconds.
如果你等8秒钟。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So you ready to start?
是的。准备好了吗？
&gt;&gt; Okay. So
好的。所以
&gt;&gt; Mhm. And so people they'll like they'll
嗯。所以人们会喜欢他们
close themselves but the sales people
他们自己关门了，但销售人员
are so afraid of that silence that they
他们如此害怕那种沉默，以至于
then jump back in. It's like you had the
然后又重新跳进去。就像你曾经……
sale just shut up. And so I used to talk
销售人员，请闭嘴。于是我过去常常说话
about how emphasis was super important.
关于强调重点有多么重要。
And so like a very easy example to
举个非常简单的例子
demonstrate this in terms of
请用以下方式证明这一点：
communication is that if I say I didn't
沟通就是，如果我说我没有……
say he hit his wife. I didn't say he hit
说他打了妻子。我没说他打人了。
his wife. I didn't say he hit his wife.
他的妻子。我没说他打了妻子。
I didn't say hit his wife. Those all
我没说要打他老婆。所有这些
mean very different things. But
意思截然不同。但
fundamentally it's just cuz I change
根本原因就是我改变了
where I pause. Right. Mhm.
我在此停顿。正确的。嗯。
&gt;&gt; What word? So, I'm emphasizing a
什么词？所以，我强调的是……
different word. And so, I used to talk
不同的词。所以，我过去常常说话
about emphasis a lot, but I've I've
关于强调很多，但我已经……
trained more and more and more and more
接受越来越多的训练
sales people over time. I just say, when
随着时间的推移，销售人员会逐渐增多。我只是说，当
do you shut up and when do you raise
你闭嘴吗？你什么时候提拔？
your voice? That's it. The rest of this
你的声音？就是这样。其余部分
we we speak in the exact same tone. And
我们说话的语气完全一样。和
the reason that I feel very confident
我感到非常自信的原因
about this is that AI is doing
关于这一点，人工智能正在做什么？
increasingly good job at ads. If I don't
广告做得越来越好。如果我不
know if you you've noticed this, but
不知道你是否注意到这一点，但是
like a lot of ads are just being voiced
很多广告都只是配音而已。
over AI and they convert higher because
人工智能过剩，转化率更高，因为
people can understand them.
人们都能理解他们。
&gt;&gt; I think a huge part of it is just they
我认为很大一部分原因就在于此。
can comprehend it. they can actually
能够理解。他们实际上可以
hear all the words and it's set in a
听清所有歌词，故事发生在一个
tone that's loud enough and there's
声音足够响亮，而且还有
annunciation and they actually get it
他们真的领会了。
cuz most like it's like one of the
因为大多数情况下，它就像是其中之一
easiest ways you can improve copy on a
如何以最简单的方式改进文案
website is just get it below third grade
网站简直烂到家了，连三年级以下都达不到。
reading level like 50% of people can't
阅读水平大概有50%的人看不懂。
read above sixth grade
阅读水平高于六年级
&gt;&gt; in the US
在美国
&gt;&gt; it's crazy
太疯狂了
&gt;&gt; so you're you're alienating 50% of the
所以你疏远了50%的人
market now you might think oh well those
现在市场上你可能会想，哦，好吧，那些
are the idiots no I know plenty of
那些白痴？不，我认识很多。
people I mean like I've got two friends
我的意思是，像我这样的人，我只有两个朋友。
who dropped out of high school and are
那些高中辍学的人
super super successful entrepreneurs
超级成功的企业家
barely can write their names and they
他们几乎不会写自己的名字，而且
like they make fun of it, but like
就像他们嘲笑它一样，但又像
they're smart. They just didn't weren't
他们很聪明。他们只是没有……
educated. Those are different things,
受过教育的。这是两码事。
right? And so I say this to say like if
正确的？所以我说这话的意思是，如果
if you're if you're in these selling
如果你是，如果你从事这些销售工作
situations and you're like because what
情况就是这样，你会想：因为什么？
happens is you get nervous, right? You
你会感到紧张，对吧？你
get this fight, flight, freak out, the
搞清楚这种战斗、逃跑、惊慌失措的反应。
ones that Daniel was saying earlier. And
丹尼尔之前说过的那些话。和
so your adrenaline kicks up and so you
于是你的肾上腺素飙升，于是你
want to talk faster, you want to talk
想说快点，你想说话
louder, uh you interrupt the other
声音更大些，呃，你打断了对方。
person. And all those things are
人。所有这些都是
antithetical to closing. And so just
与关闭相反。所以就这样
teaching someone to be okay with pauses
教人如何接受停顿
can increase the likelihood that people
可以增加人们发生以下情况的可能性
pay attention to the words that they
注意他们说的话
say. Because all we do is we draw
说。因为我们所做的就是画画。
attention when we pause. You have short
在我们停顿的时候，请集中注意力。你短
pauses that draw attention. And then you
引人注目的停顿。然后你
have long pauses that solicit response.
留出较长的停顿，以引起回应。
If I pause long enough, what do people
如果我停下来足够长的时间，人们会做什么？
do? They talk.
做？他们交谈。
&gt;&gt; And I just think of someone as being
我只是觉得某人是
higher value if they if they're taking
如果他们接受，价值会更高
pauses. Mhm.
停顿。嗯。
&gt;&gt; Um, one of my one of my great mentors
嗯，我的一位伟大的导师
early in my career, he
在我职业生涯早期，他
there's something about the way that he
他身上有一种特质。
spoke, he was incredibly slow with the
他说话很慢。
way he sp he was like that. And the
他说话的方式，他就是这样的人。以及
minute he started speaking when when my
他开始说话的那一刻，我的
company were over there and having these
公司在那边，而且有这些东西
men mentorship sessions with him,
他为男性提供指导课程
everybody would stop and just like was
所有人都停下来，就像……
fixated on him. And then I remember this
目不转睛地盯着他。然后我想起了这件事
girl who worked in my New York office,
曾在我纽约办公室工作的女孩，
he was
他是
&gt;&gt; opposite.
对面的。
&gt;&gt; And it's just it's just the use of your
而这仅仅是你的使用而已。
this instrument. Yeah.
这个乐器。是的。
&gt;&gt; Um, do you think much about that? Do you
嗯，你对此有过深入思考吗？你
think much about how you present
多想想你的表达方式。
yourself? Do you think much about your
你自己？你经常思考你的
body language?
肢体语言？
&gt;&gt; I think it it's natural. I think more
我认为这很自然。我觉得更多
important is the distinction between are
重要的是区分以下两者：
you coming across as a newbie? Are you
你看起来像个新手吗？你是
coming across as a standard worker be or
表现得像个普通工人
are you coming across as high status,
你给人的感觉地位很高吗？
key person of influence level? And each
关键人物级别？以及每一个
one of those has body language
其中之一有肢体语言
associated. It has different ways of
联系。它有不同的方式
presenting yourself. But it's a
自我介绍。但这却是
self-identity thing. And if you can
自我认同的问题。如果你能
shift that selfidentity, you can
转变自我认同，你可以
naturally become more of a key person of
自然而然地成为关键人物
influence. When we meet someone, we
影响。当我们遇到某人时，我们
within a few seconds, we evaluate their
几秒钟之内，我们就评估了他们的
status level relative to us. And you
相对于我们的地位水平。你呢
can't switch it off. And there's plenty
关不掉。而且数量很多。
of evidence to say that like
有证据表明，就像
unfortunately, you just do it
很遗憾，你只能这么做。
automatically. I've seen people
自动地。我见过人们
completely change their life by just
仅仅通过以下方式就彻底改变了他们的生活
simply changing the way that they pitch
只需改变他们的投球方式即可
from a a newbie worker B to a key person
从一名新员工B到关键人物
of influence. I can think of an example.
影响力。我能想到一个例子。
There's this woman who I asked her,
我问过那个女人，
"What do you do?" And she said, "I'm a
“你做什么工作？”她说：“我是一个
financial planner. I can help anyone
财务规划师。我可以帮助任何人
with their financial planning. If anyone
以及他们的财务规划。任何人
wants to talk about their wills or any
想谈谈他们的遗嘱或其他任何事情
of those sorts of things, then that's
如果是这类事情，那就是……
what I can help people with, right? And
我可以帮到别人，对吧？和
it sounds workery. And her her body
听起来很费工夫。还有她的身体
language was kind of like this.
语言大概就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Uh I asked her a question. I said, "When
呃，我问了她一个问题。我说：“当
did you do something special that was
你做了什么特别的事情吗？
really transformational, something
真的很有变革性，某种
something important?" She said, "Last
有什么重要的事吗？她说：“最后
month, I went out to the countryside. I
一个月前，我去了乡下。我
worked on a farm and I worked with the
我在农场工作，我和……一起工作
owner of the farm and their kids and
农场主和他们的孩子
their grandkids to get alignment between
他们的孙辈们要达成一致
the three generations. the farm was
三代人。农场是
going to be sold off to private equity
将被出售给私募股权公司
and instead I helped them to get
相反，我却帮助他们获得了
alignment as to how they're going to
他们如何达成一致
keep the family farm. And I said, "How
保住家族农场。我说：“怎么会这样？”
did you do that?" And she said, "Well, I
你做了那件事吗？”她回答说：“嗯，我
used to be a city girl and then I
我以前是个都市女孩，然后我
married a country boy and I I learned
我嫁给了一个乡下男孩，然后我学会了
how to do it." I got her to change her
怎么做呢？”我让她改了她的
pitch and I said, "Pitch yourself as a
我说：“把自己推销成……”
key person of influence at that." So she
她还是个关键人物呢。”所以她
stood up in front of the group and she
她站到众人面前。
said, "For the last 20 years, I've been
他说：“过去20年来，我一直……”
working with rural families who own
与拥有土地的农村家庭合作
farms and I help them with their
我帮助他们打理农场。
financial planning and I secure their
财务规划，我确保他们的
family farm for the next two
接下来两年都在家庭农场度过
generations."
一代又一代。
&gt;&gt; And her body language just went like
她的肢体语言就像这样
like key person of influence and
比如关键人物和
everyone just responded differently. And
每个人的反应都不一样。和
when I asked the audience, in the first
当我问观众时，首先
instance, what do you think her day rate
例如，你觉得她日薪是多少？
was? Everyone said $500. I said, in the
曾是？大家都说500美元。我说，在
second instance, what do you think she
第二点，你觉得她怎么样？
charges per day? 10 grand. And it was
每日收费？ 10000美元。确实如此。
just the ability to pitch yourself as
仅仅是能够把自己推销出去的能力
that key person of influence in the
那位关键人物
room.
房间。
&gt;&gt; You know what's fascinating is there are
你知道最令人着迷的是什么吗？
actual studies now that show for women
现在的实际研究表明，对于女性而言
in particular that you make more money
尤其是你赚更多钱
if you do one thing which is you wear
如果你做一件事，那就是穿
makeup which is wild. So they did
妆容非常狂野。所以他们这么做了。
there's three studies that have been
已有三项研究……
done totally different groups one by
完全不同的组逐一完成
Harvard one by Stanford and I can't
哈佛大学和斯坦福大学都比不上，我没办法。
remember it was either Oxford or
记住，要么是牛津，要么是
Cambridge and the studies showed that
剑桥大学的研究表明
women who there was no attractiveness
没有吸引力的女性
differential between them but one wore
它们之间存在差异，但其中一个穿着
makeup consistently uh at work and one
工作时经常化妆，而且……
didn't. They made anywhere from 20 to
没有。他们赚的钱从20到
40% more money inside of this study.
这项研究涉及的资金比预期多 40%。
What I thought was really interesting
我觉得真正有趣的是
about that, because I'm not really
关于这一点，因为我其实不太清楚。
historically a makeup girl, although
从历史上看，她是一名化妆师，尽管
being fully face painted for this, is
为此需要全身涂上油彩。
that that actually makes sense in a lot
这在很多情况下确实有道理。
of ways because we do have this initial
因为我们确实有这种初始方法，所以有很多方法。
reaction that we always have uh with
我们总是会有这种反应。
people. You know, we judge somebody like
人们。你知道，我们评判一个人就像……
you talked about almost immediately. And
你几乎立刻就谈到了这件事。和
so when I saw that study, I thought,
所以当我看到那项研究时，我想，
well, first of all, that's interesting.
首先，这很有意思。
You don't have to be smarter, better
你不必更聪明、更好。
looking uh or anything else, and you can
看看呃，或者其他任何东西，你可以
make more money just by the way you
仅仅通过以下方式就能赚更多钱：
present yourself. And so I thought
自我介绍一下。于是我想
thought, well, what about the way that
我想，那么，这种方式又如何呢？
you dress? Is is that also the same? And
你穿什么衣服？那也是一样的吗？和
there are studies that back this as well
也有研究支持这一观点。
that in fact you can make more money as
事实上，你可以通过以下方式赚更多钱：
a man for dressing one way and as a
一个男人因为穿着某种特定的服装而受到批评，并且……
woman and women are interesting because
女人和女性之所以有趣，是因为
you are not the norm.
你与众不同。
&gt;&gt; What am I missing?
我漏掉了什么？
&gt;&gt; You got the lumberjack.
你找到了伐木工。
&gt;&gt; I've got 20% sitting on the table right
我桌上放着20%的钱呢。
now.
现在。
&gt;&gt; But what's fascinating is, you know, I
但最令人着迷的是，你知道，我
like things where you don't have to you
比如那些你不必亲自去做的事情
don't have to be better than anybody
不必比任何人更优秀
else. You can just use human psychology
别的。你可以直接运用人类心理学。
to make more money. And so if I'm a
为了赚更多的钱。所以如果我是一个
woman, I know that the way that I dress,
女人，我知道我的穿着打扮，
so when I pay attention to my dress and
所以当我注意我的穿着时
dress professionally, whatever that
无论如何，都要穿着得体。
means in this instance, in the study
就此而言，是指在研究中
that I saw, it was like, you know, what
我看到的，就像，你知道，什么
what I would have on a blouse, a suit,
我会把图案印在衬衫、西装上，
something like that, women make two
差不多是这样，女人会生两个
times more than men when they dress when
她们穿衣时的频率是男性的数倍
they dress better. Men, it actually is
他们穿衣打扮更好看。男人，这确实是
less important. Still more important
不太重要。更重要的是
though, if you dress professionally in a
不过，如果你穿着得体，展现出职业素养的话……
suit and you don't have all the other
西装，而且你没有其他所有东西
proof and things you have, you have this
证据和你所拥有的东西，你有这些
sort of interesting thing that's like a
有点意思，就像……
you have sort of um diametric
你有点……嗯……直径
opposition. I make a lot of money and
反对。我赚了很多钱，
yet I care so little about money that I
但我对金钱却毫不在意，以至于
dress in a wife theater. Yeah. Exactly.
在妻子剧院里穿衣服。是的。确切地。
And so and so men make somewhere between
所以，有些男人的收入介于两者之间。
15 and 18% more when they dress in
穿衣打扮时，他们的消费额会增加 15% 到 18%。
suits. So I think there's a a real um
西装。所以我觉得确实存在一个……
argument to be made for if you're going
如果你要去的话，需要提出一些论点。
to pay attention to the way your voice
注意你的声音
sounds. That takes some training.
声音。那需要一些训练。
Doesn't take much training to change the
改变这一点不需要太多的培训。
way that you look professionally and and
你看起来专业的方式以及
how you dress. And the only other thing
你的穿着打扮。还有唯一其他的事
that I would talk about on sales and
我会谈谈销售和
pitching is we tell all of our company
推销就是我们告诉公司所有人的事。
people. Um the line is show don't tell.
人们。嗯，关键在于要展示，而不是讲述。
We increasingly do not believe the
我们越来越不相信
things that were heard. So like think
听到的一些事情。所以就像这样想
about a sales pitch that goes like this.
一段推销话术大概是这样的。
Um you know uh we for instance have a
嗯，你知道，例如我们有一个
lot of home service companies. So these
许多家政服务公司。所以这些
home service companies are selling a
家庭服务公司正在销售
homeowner on let's say landscaping. And
比如说，房主进行园林绿化。和
so I'm going to come and we're going to
所以我要来了，我们要……
clean up your lawn and here's what we're
清理你的草坪，这就是我们要做的。
going to do and this is how much it's
要做的，费用是这么多。
going to charge. I'm going to charge and
即将充电。我要充电了
this is how long it's going to take. And
需要这么长时间。和
you can tell the client that we're an
你可以告诉客户我们是一家
expert at this. I've been in business
这方面的专家。我一直从事商业活动。
for 42 years. We have, you know, 1,000
42年。我们有，你知道，1000
reviews on Trustpilot, etc. Or you could
在 Trustpilot 等网站上查看评论。或者你可以……
do something that'll double your
做一些能让你的收入翻倍的事情
conversion, which is simply bring a
转换，也就是简单地带来
phone or an iPad with you and say, "Can
带上你的手机或iPad，然后说：“可以吗？”
I show you what we did for your
我给你看看我们为你做了什么
neighbors down the street?" And just
街对面的邻居？”还有，就……
show them the image of it. Just go, "We
给他们看看图片。就走吧，“我们
do have a thousand Trust Pilot views. I
在 Trustpilot 上有上千次浏览量。我
don't right here. We could see what the
不要在这里。我们可以看到什么
last one said. Click on it. Show them
最后一个人说。点击它。给他们看看
the Trust Pilot review." You don't have
Trustpilot 评论。”你没有
to train that. And I really like my
训练那个。我真的很喜欢我的
salespeople to not have to become
销售人员不必成为
experts but to be enabled by what's
专家，但要由以下因素促成：
called sales enablement or technology
称为销售赋能或技术
just to show because we are a visual
只是为了展示，因为我们是视觉型的
species. And so wherever possible if you
物种。因此，只要有可能，如果你
want to increase your conversions I tell
想提高转化率？我告诉你
my team you are not allowed to close a
我的团队，你们不允许关闭一个
sale without showing something.
不展示任何内容就进行销售。
&gt;&gt; Some visuals
一些图片
&gt;&gt; you have to have a visual because it's
你必须要有视觉参考，因为……
just a trust transfer and a higher
仅仅是信托转移和更高的
signal. What's wild now is that in that
信号。现在最不可思议的是，在那
same business, you could take a photo
同样，你也可以拍照
&gt;&gt; just right there in chat GBT say do the
就在聊天窗口GBT里说做
landscape gardening and then show them
景观设计，然后向他们展示
this is your house. Exactly.
这是你的房子。确切地。
&gt;&gt; Fully landscaped. People are vis 70% of
景观已全部完成。人们看到70%
the brain is visual processing.
大脑负责视觉处理。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. And then you believe it and
确切地。然后你就相信了。
then you've already seen it happen.
那么你已经亲眼目睹过这种情况发生了。
&gt;&gt; I work with a lot of entrepreneurs and I
我与很多创业者合作，而且
get them to create a brochure
让他们制作一份宣传册
&gt;&gt; like a physical brochure for their
就像他们的纸质宣传册一样
business and people are like what on
企业和个人都在想：这到底是怎么回事？
earth am I creating a brochure for in
我正在为地球制作一本宣传册
2025? I because the the act of creating
2025年？我因为创造的行为。
a brochure gets what's in your head, out
宣传册能把你脑子里的东西表达出来。
of your head, and into a document we can
把你的想法整理成一份文件，我们可以
all explore. And I I still think a
探索一切。而且我仍然认为
brochure is actually one of the coolest
宣传册实际上是最酷的宣传品之一。
things that an entrepreneur can do as an
企业家可以做的事情
activity to really just solidify what
这项活动旨在真正巩固什么
they do.
确实如此。
&gt;&gt; I saw you scribbling again, Daniel.
丹尼尔，我又看到你在涂涂画画了。
&gt;&gt; Oh, I have lots of things, but yeah. No,
哦，我有很多东西，不过，是的。不，
I was thinking about like uh makeup
我当时在想，呃，化妆的事儿。
versus suits and whatnot. And so, you
对抗诉讼等等。所以，你
know, one it's like if you have if you
你知道，这就好比你拥有……
have zero status, you have no credit,
信用等级为零，你没有任何信用记录。
like SPCL like we went through, then
就像我们之前经历的SPCL那样
it's like, well, then what are the
这就像，好吧，那还有什么？
smallest versions of that that you can
最小的版本，你可以
demonstrate? And so, I would also bet
证明？所以，我敢打赌
that if the girls did makeup like hooker
如果女孩们化着像妓女一样的妆
makeup and then you also do like
化妆，然后你也喜欢
professional makeup, I'll bet you
我敢打赌，这是专业化妆师的作品。
there's a very different outcome that
还有一种截然不同的结果：
happens because if you have like
发生这种情况是因为如果你有喜欢
understated business makeup, then that
低调的商务妆容，然后是
probably signals a certain level of
可能表明达到某种程度的
status and they will treat you like
地位越高，他们就会越尊重你​​。
other people that they have treated in
他们治疗过的其他人
the past because that associates with
过去，因为它与……有关
the status people had. Same thing with a
人们的地位。同样的情况也适用于
man in a suit. Like literally fancy
穿西装的男人。就像真的花哨一样
pants, right? Um, it's like this guy's
裤子，对吧？嗯，就像这个人……
got fancy pants, therefore he is must be
他穿了条考究的裤子，所以他一定是……
15 18% better on average. Now, to to to
平均提升 15% 至 18%。现在，到到到
comment on on on Cody's point earlier,
对科迪之前提出的观点进行评论，
it's like I have other statusinducing
感觉我好像还有其他提升地位的方法。
points that are superior to a suit and
比一套西装更胜一筹的要点
so I don't need one,
所以我不需要。
&gt;&gt; right? So, like how how do I get away
正确的？所以，我该如何逃脱？
with that? It's like, yeah, like having
就那样吗？就像，是啊，就像拥有
a suit only means that you have $500,
一套西装只意味着你有500美元。
right?
正确的？
&gt;&gt; But billionaires don't wear Louis
但亿万富翁们并不穿路易威登。
Vuitton because in the status game
路易威登，因为在身份地位游戏中
they're playing that would be an inverse
他们玩的那套把戏正好相反。
signal of wealth.
财富的象征。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. Yeah. Who you're trying to And
确切地。是的。你想和谁在一起？
then um to Cody's point about proof,
然后，嗯，回到科迪关于证据的观点，
like proof is always number one, right?
好像证据永远是第一位的，对吧？
And so like
所以就像
trust pilot reviews is a kind of proof.
Trustpilot 上的评论也是一种证明。
Somebody down the street is a closer
街对面有人离得更近
approximation which is a higher form of
近似值是更高形式的
proof. And so proof is always going to
证明。因此，证明总是会……
be number one what you can lead with.
成为你最擅长的领域的第一名。
You can almost immediately in any sales
你几乎可以立即在任何销售中做到这一点
process if they don't have one of these
如果他们没有这些工具之一，则按以下步骤操作。
just implement a video sales letter and
只需制作一份视频销售信即可
increase sales by 20 to 40% with like
通过类似产品将销售额提高 20% 至 40%。
really doing nothing else. Um sometimes
真的什么也没做。嗯，有时候
more. And so that typically is like,
更多的。所以通常情况下就是这样，
okay, what's the what's the promise that
好的，承诺是什么？
we're gonna, you know, what do we do?
我们要做什么呢？
What's the pain that we're solving? What
我们要解决的痛点是什么？什么
is the uh plan or sorry, what is the
呃，计划是什么？或者抱歉，是什么？
proof that we have that we can solve it?
我们有什么证据证明我们可以解决这个问题？
And then what is the plan for the rest
那么，其余部分的计划是什么呢？
of this video? And then typically after
这段视频？然后通常在之后
you have you've demonstrated each of
你已经展示了每一项
those P's, you then say great picture
然后你说那些P，很棒的照片
number five. Uh which then gives you
第五名。呃，然后就给你
kind of the visual road map. And then
有点像可视化的路线图。进而
after that, I typically like to have
之后，我通常喜欢……
people just respond to the all of the
人们只是对所有这些都做出了回应。
biggest objections that people have
人们最大的反对意见
around whatever the specific service is
围绕着任何具体的服务
um as the main points of the video. And
嗯，这就是视频的主要内容。和
then after that, you just make your call
然后，你只需拨打电话即可。
to action or you just reinforce the
采取行动还是仅仅强化……
appointment. Say, "Hey, like if you like
预约。就说，“嘿，喜欢就点赞吧”
this video, text me this keyword. That
看完这个视频，给我发短信告诉我这个关键词。那
way, I know you watched it and we'll
我知道你看过，我们会……
give you an extra 5% on whatever." And
任何商品都额外赠送5%。”
that way the salesperson knows the
这样销售人员就知道了
person watched it. Um and it gives them
有人看过。嗯，它给了他们
incentive to do so. So it's like, "Hey,
这样做的动机。所以就好像，“嘿，
if you watch the video, you get 5%."
观看视频可获得5%的奖励。
It's like, "Oh [__] that's amazing." Um
感觉就像，“我的天，太棒了。”嗯
but then that way they know that they
但这样他们就知道自己
actually watched it. The one other thing
我真的看过了。还有一件事
that I've found that is the most
我发现这是最
powerful sales closer
强大的销售终结者
&gt;&gt; is to pitch the assessment. And to pitch
目的是提出评估方案。并进行推销
the assessment is, I don't know if I can
评估结果是，我不知道我是否能做到
help you, but if we answer these 40
可以帮助你，但如果我们回答这40个问题
questions and we go through this
我们会提出问题并讨论这些内容。
assessment, then we'll figure out
评估之后，我们再来决定。
whether we can help you or not. So, it's
无论我们是否能帮到你。所以，就是这样。
kind of like if you went to the doctor
就像你去看医生一样
and said, I don't know whether you need
然后他说，我不知道你是否需要
anything, but we'll put you through a
任何事，但我们会让你经历一番考验
blood test and and an X-ray and then
验血、拍X光片，然后
we'll see. So one of the biggest way I
我们拭目以待。所以，我最大的方式之一
I've scaled multiple companies where you
我曾帮助多家公司实现规模化发展，而你
pitch the assessment. You just you don't
提出评估方案。你就是不喜欢
tell people whether you can can or can't
告诉别人你能不能做到。
help them. You just simply say the next
帮助他们。你只需简单地说下一句。
step is to take an assessment and when
步骤一是进行评估，当……
we do the assessment it will tell us
我们进行评估，结果会告诉我们。
whether I can help you or not. And it's
无论我是否能帮到你。而且是
one of the best sales closing
最佳销售成交法之一
techniques.
技术。
&gt;&gt; There's a lot of psychology around that.
这其中有很多心理学因素。
They did that the study where they had
他们在那项研究中做了那件事。
the boring focus group and they had one
那个无聊的焦点小组，他们只有一个
group of people who were allowed
获准进入的一群人
straight into the boring f community
直接进入无聊的F社区
group and then they had the other group
一组，然后他们还有另一组
of people who had to take a survey to
那些必须参加调查的人
get in and the group of people that took
进去，然后是那群人。
the survey to get into the boring
调查是为了进入无聊的领域
community group all said that it was
社区团体一致认为，
great in there.
里面很棒。
&gt;&gt; So much better.
好多了。
&gt;&gt; And there's something about how friction
摩擦力也会带来一些影响。
upon entry makes you value the thing
进入其中会让你更加珍惜它。
more
更多的
&gt;&gt; bazillion%. Like I can't I cannot I c I
亿万%。就像我不能，我不能，我c
can't emphasize this more. Like in every
这一点我怎么强调都不为过。就像在所有
single CRO split test that we increase
我们增加的单个 CRO 拆分测试的
friction or increase the quality of
摩擦或提高质量
leads, we make more money.
获得线索，我们就能赚更多钱。
&gt;&gt; CRO split test.
CRO 拆分测试。
&gt;&gt; So conversion optimization test that
所以，转化率优化测试是
you'd run across a a landing page or
你会遇到一个着陆页或
funnel or sales sales motion. Um like
销售漏斗或销售流程。嗯，就像
when you add more friction and it's good
增加摩擦力是好事。
friction ideally, meaning you're not
理想情况下是摩擦力，也就是说你不是
getting out bad people, you're getting
把坏人赶出去，你就会得到
sorry, getting out good people, which is
抱歉，好人被遣返了，这
bad friction. You want good friction
摩擦力过大。你需要良好的摩擦力。
which gets out bad people.
这样就能把坏人放出来。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. um you will typically always
是的。嗯，你通常总是
increase the cost per action. So your
提高每次操作的成本。所以你的
lead cost will go up, your cost per call
线索成本将会上升，每次通话成本也会上升。
will go up, but your show rates will go
会上涨，但你的演出费也会上涨
up and your close rates will go up and
上涨，你的成交率也会上涨。
your cash collected will go up.
你收到的现金将会增加。
&gt;&gt; And it seems counterintuitive to apply
而且，应用这种方法似乎有悖常理。
friction to a process, but
对过程的摩擦，但是
&gt;&gt; and I can almost promise that like it I
我几乎可以保证，我喜欢它。
I have so few examples where it didn't
我很少看到它没有奏效的例子。
work that I almost believe that it's law
这项工作我几乎相信它是法律。
at this point. And I think it's law
在此刻。我认为这是法律。
because it's so counterintuitive because
因为它太违反直觉了，因为
it's scary to add friction because you
增加摩擦力很可怕，因为……
know that you're actively decreasing
要知道你正在积极减少
your lead flow and increasing your cost
您的潜在客户流量和增加您的成本
per lead. You're decreasing your calls,
每根铅。你的通话次数正在减少。
you're increasing your cost per call.
你正在增加每次通话的成本。
Like that is frightening for just about
那简直太可怕了
every business, which is usually why it
每个企业，通常就是因为这个原因。
works.
作品。
&gt;&gt; At the Louis Vuitton store, they put a
在路易威登专卖店里，他们放了一个
security guard to keep you out and then
保安会阻止你进去，然后
it pushes the prices up.
这会推高价格。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Like they they after co none of
是的。就像他们之后一样，没有一个
them stopped doing because they're like,
他们停止这样做是因为他们觉得，
"Oh, wow. We made more sales during CO
“哇哦。我们在新冠疫情期间的销售额更高了。”
because we had people wait in line and
因为有人排队等候，
showed scarcity."
显示出稀缺性。
&gt;&gt; It's like, isn't it? You don't even get
是啊，不是吗？你甚至都得不到
to pick the bag you get and you have to
挑选你得到的包，你必须这样做。
join a waiting list. Then they interview
加入等候名单。然后他们进行面试
you to buy the bag
你去买这个包
&gt;&gt; and then they decide whether they should
然后他们决定是否应该
let you have
让你拥有
&gt;&gt; what do you bring to the table.
你能为团队带来什么？
&gt;&gt; That's how Ferrari works. You're not
这就是法拉利的运作方式。你不
allowed to buy Ferraris unless you go
除非你去，否则不允许购买法拉利
through this list. And if you're ever so
通过这份清单。如果你有那么一天
shown to to flip them or sell them,
展示出来是为了转手倒卖或出售它们，
you'll never buy another Ferrari again.
你以后再也不会买法拉利了。
So
所以
&gt;&gt; I've got three boxes here and these
我这里有三个盒子，还有这些
three suitcases contain different
三个行李箱里装着不同的
amounts of money. One of them contains
金额。其中之一包含
$1,000. one of them contains $10,000 and
1000美元。其中一枚硬币装有 10,000 美元，
one of them contains $100,000. You're
其中一枚硬币里装有 10 万美元。你是
going to pick a suitcase and you're
你正准备挑选一个行李箱，然后……
going to tell me what you would do with
你打算告诉我你会怎么做？
that amount of money if you were
如果你有那笔钱的话
starting with that amount of money today
今天就从这笔钱开始。
to build a scalable business.
打造可扩展的业务。
&gt;&gt; So,
所以，
&gt;&gt; do we keep the money?
我们保留这笔钱吗？
&gt;&gt; He wants to buy a watch.
他想买块手表。
&gt;&gt; I'm like, I'm feeling 100,000.
我感觉自己棒极了。
&gt;&gt; All right. What do we got?
好的。我们得到了什么？
&gt;&gt; Oh, I have $1,000.
哦，我有1000美元。
&gt;&gt; So, do I get to keep the money? Is that
那么，我能把钱留下吗？是吗？
how this works?
这是怎么回事？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you can keep it. It smells smells
好的，你可以留着。它闻起来很臭。
like money. Okay, so I have $1,000. So I
就像金钱一样。好的，我有1000美元。所以，我
would um take the $1,000, put it in my
我会收下那1000美元，把它放进我的……
pocket, do nothing with it, and I would
放进口袋，什么也不做，我会
watch YouTube videos on AI integration
观看 YouTube 上关于人工智能集成的视频
into small businesses. And then I would
进入小型企业。然后我会
go to small businesses, and once I had a
去小企业，有一次我……
specific integration that I would do,
我将进行的具体整合工作是：
which I would probably bet would be
我大概会打赌是
around likely email list activation
可能的电子邮件列表激活
because that's typically like fastest,
因为那通常是最快的，
easiest money that most business owners
大多数企业主都能轻松赚到的钱
have, is their contact list. They've
他们拥有的是联系人列表。他们有
got, you know, they've been in business
你知道，他们一直在做生意。
10 years. They've got, you know, 8,000
10年。他们有，你知道，8000
customers they've sold over that whole
他们在整个过程中销售的客户
time period and maybe a list of, you
时间段，或许还有一份清单，你
know, call it 20,000 leads that they've
我知道，就叫他们有2万条潜在客户线索吧。
had. They never email them ever. If they
有。他们从来不给他们发邮件。如果他们
do, it's just like, here's our random
没错，就像这样，这是我们的随机结果。
discount that we send once a quarter for
我们每季度都会发送一次折扣信息。
Christmas or whatever. And I would say,
圣诞节什么的。我会说，
hey, um, I will email those people and I
嘿，嗯，我会给那些人发邮件，而且我
will uh get everything approved by you
我会确保所有事情都得到你的批准。
and don't pay me anything. Just pay me a
别给我任何报酬。付我钱就行了
percentage of the sales that we generate
我们销售额的百分比
afterwards. How's that sound? And that
然后。这样如何？而那
offer tends to do well. And I know that
优惠活动往往效果不错。我知道这一点。
because I've done it. So, that's what I
因为我已经做到了。所以，这就是我
would do. in the thousand dollars, I
可以。一千美元，我
would, you know, go buy Leila something
你知道，我会去给莱拉买点什么。
for a little bit of time so that she can
给她一点时间，这样她就可以
stay with me until uh I make the money
陪着我直到我赚到钱为止
for my my email reactivation campaign.
用于我的电子邮件重新激活活动。
&gt;&gt; See what I get?
看看我得到了什么？
I got the 10K.
我拿到了10K。
&gt;&gt; Ah,
啊，
&gt;&gt; all right. We're going around the circle
好的。我们正在绕圈。
here. Um, I like it.
这里。嗯，我喜欢。
I would find the person who would buy
我会找到愿意购买的人
what I was selling for the highest
我卖的最高价
dollar amount humanly possible, which
人类所能达到的美元金额，即
means I would probably go to private
这意味着我可能会去私立学校。
equity companies. So, Alex gave me the
股权公司。所以，亚历克斯给了我
idea for Main Street. I I know that Main
主街构想。我知道主线
Street businesses are like often cash
街头小贩通常都像现金交易一样。
crunched, right? They don't have a lot
被碾碎了，对吧？他们没有很多东西。
of money and they often cannot extract
他们往往无法提取资金。
enough value from a lead that I need
我需要的潜在客户价值。
them to. So, Alex would need to find the
让他们也这样做。所以，亚历克斯需要找到
perfect company to do that and there's
非常适合做这件事的公司，而且还有……
lots of them or he would build his own
他会建很多，否则他就会自己建。
which would be great. I think in my
那太好了。我认为在我的
specific instance, I want to go to the
例如，我想去……
people who are already good at
已经擅长
extracting the most value humanly
以人为本，榨取最大价值
possible. So, I'd probably try to go to
可能的。所以，我可能会尽量去
a private equity firm. And I would
一家私募股权公司。而我会
&gt;&gt; What's a private equity firm?
什么是私募股权公司？
&gt;&gt; It's basically a fancy way for saying
这其实就是另一种比较文雅的说法。
that people use their own money to buy
人们用自己的钱去购买
businesses as opposed to public equity
企业而非公开股权
where people use the stock markets
人们使用股票市场的地方
dollars to buy businesses. And so,
用于收购企业的美元。所以，
examples would be like u you know KKR,
例如，你知道KKR队，
Carile, uh Cberus are some of the
Carile，呃，Cberus是其中一些
biggest in the world.
世界最大。
&gt;&gt; So, they go around buying people's
所以，他们到处买别人的东西
businesses with their own money.
使用自有资金的企业。
&gt;&gt; That's right. Yeah. Yeah. they find
这是正确的。是的。是的。他们发现
entrepreneurs right about the point
企业家们说得对。
where they cannot take it anymore and
他们再也无法忍受了
they buy those businesses and then they
他们收购了这些企业，然后他们
they grow them hugely and and and again
他们把它们养得非常茂盛，而且……
because I'm better at partnerships I
因为我更擅长合作
would want to go to them and I would
我会想去他们那里，我也会
want to say and it really what's
想说的，其实是什么呢？
interesting is I bet all of us are going
有趣的是，我敢打赌我们所有人都会去
to be really similar the money actually
实际上，钱真的非常相似。
doesn't matter and so even though I have
没关系，所以即使我有
$10,000 10x what Alex has it doesn't
10,000 美元，是 Alex 拥有的 10 倍，但它并没有。
actually matter because what I would do
实际上很重要，因为我会做什么
still $10,000 is not enough for me to
1万美元对我来说仍然不够。
make a couple million which is what I
赚几百万美元，这就是我的目标。
would want to do with this so what
你会想用这个做什么？
actually is the differentiator what is
实际上，区别在于……
the business model I choose? Who do I go
我选择的商业模式是什么？我该去哪里？
to sell it to so that I can get the most
卖给谁才能获得最大收益
value out of it? And with these PE
从中能得到什么价值？以及这些PE
companies, what I would do is I would go
对于公司，我会做的就是去
to them and they're buying companies all
对他们来说，他们正在收购所有公司。
the time. And so there's two ways to
时间。所以有两种方法
sell to a PE company and I'd see which
卖给私募股权公司，我会看看哪种更合适。
ones I could get them to sign up for. On
那些我能让他们报名参加的活动。在
one hand, there's something called a
一方面，有一种东西叫做……
deal sourcing fee, which is if you can
交易撮合费，如果您可以的话
find companies that are in the niche
找到专注于特定领域的公司
that PE companies want to buy, they will
私募股权公司想要收购的，他们会
pay you for sourcing the company. Um,
支付你介绍这家公司的报酬。嗯，
and I know this because I pay deals
我知道这一点，因为我参与过交易。
fees. And so I would go to private local
费用。所以我会去当地的私人机构。
private equity companies. You're not
私募股权公司。你不
going to be able to get to Cberus or the
能否到达Cberus或
big guys. So I would go to the ones in
大块头。所以我会去那些
my local neighborhood that you could
我的本地社区，你可以
find by searching on AI to say local
通过人工智能搜索找到本地信息
private equity companies buying these
私募股权公司购买这些
types of companies. I would reach out to
公司类型。我会联系
the GPS. Those are the general partners
GPS。这些是普通合伙人。
of the company, the guys who run it. And
公司，以及管理公司的人。和
I would say what type of companies are
我想问的是，这些公司属于哪种类型？
you actively purchasing right now?
你现在有在进行购买吗？
What's your investment thesis and
你的投资理念是什么？
dealbox? And if I could get them to
交易箱？如果我能让他们
respond to me, great. If not, I'd
请回复我，太好了。如果不是，我会
search, what do private equity companies
搜索，什么是私募股权公司
typically want to buy? what what is the
通常想买什么？什么是什么
deal box or investment thesis of a
交易箱或投资理念
private equity company? I would find
私募股权公司？我发现
that dealbox and then I'd play the game
那个交易箱，然后我就会玩游戏。
of doornocking. I'd go to a bunch of
敲门拜访。我会去参加很多
these businesses and try to find
这些企业，并尝试寻找
companies that wanted to sell and then
那些想要出售的公司
when they tell me they want to sell and
当他们告诉我他们想卖掉房子的时候
I have a buyer, which is the private
我有一个买家，是私人买家。
equity uh company, the private equity
股权公司，私募股权
company will pay me either a percentage
公司会按一定比例支付我报酬。
of the sale or a flat fee for sourcing
销售佣金或采购固定费用
it.
它。
&gt;&gt; What might that look like in terms of a
从某种意义上说，这可能看起来是什么样的呢？
percentage and dollar number? Yeah, I
百分比和金额是多少？是的，我
mean, if you're like a a
意思是，如果你像一个
non-institutional player doing this, I
非机构玩家这样做，我
think you would go to them and say, "Can
你觉得你会去问他们：“可以吗？”
I get like 10k for every company that I
我每与一家公司合作就能拿到大约1万美元。
source you that's over a million dollars
消息来源告诉你，这超过一百万美元
in revenue that's profitable and within
在盈利且在一定范围内的收入
your dealbox?" They'd probably say yes.
你的交易清单？”他们可能会说是的。
The normal sourcing fee is somewhere
正常的采购费用大概是某个数额。
between 3 and 5%. But you're not going
介于 3% 和 5% 之间。但你不会去
to get that when you're brand new. So,
当你还是个新手时，就能获得这种体验。所以，
but I like the idea of making 10K on one
但我喜欢一次赚1万美元的想法。
deal to start. Then, what else am I
交易开始。那么，我还能是什么呢？
learning while I'm doing this? I'm also
我一边做一边学习？我也是
learning simultaneously how do you buy
同时学习如何购买
businesses? What type of businesses? How
企业？哪些类型的企业？如何
do you find businesses for sale? I think
你们提供待售企业信息吗？我认为
this is the highest leverage activity I
这是我杠杆率最高的活动。
know how to do. Like I just I know more
知道如何去做。就像我知道的更多
how to buy a business that's already
如何收购一家已成立的企业
making money and make it make more money
赚钱并让钱赚更多钱
with a higher degree of certainty
确定性更高
because if it's already profitable, it
因为如果它已经盈利了，它
gets out of the valley of death, which
走出死亡之谷，
is where a company starts and never
那是公司起步的地方，而且永远如此。
actually makes any profit. And so I
实际上并没有盈利。所以，我
would start there and then what would I
就从那里开始，然后呢？
do for that? Well, the second that they
为此做什么？嗯，他们第二个
see that I'm good at sourcing deals,
看出我擅长寻找交易机会，
there's going to be they're going to be
将会有，他们将会有
throwing offers at me. But what I might
他们不断向我抛出橄榄枝。但我可能会
do instead is go to those GPS and say,
你应该做的是去那些GPS导航仪那里说：
"Hey, I'm pretty good at doing the
“嘿，我很擅长做……”
hardest part of private equity, which is
私募股权投资中最难的部分是
finding the deals. Why don't you guys
寻找优惠。你们为什么不呢？
back me for me to find the deals for
支持我，让我找到这些优惠
you?" Maybe they'll invest in my company
你会吗？也许他们会投资我的公司。
for me to then run a private equity
然后我就可以经营一家私募股权公司了。
firm. Or maybe they'll say, "Come work
公司。或许他们会说：“来工作吧。”
for me, and then I can make a couple
对我来说，然后我就可以做几个了。
hundred,000. I can learn what I think is
十万。我可以学习我认为的东西
the best uh skill out there to learn,
最值得学习的技能，
which is dealm. And I can use my
这就是 dealm。我可以使用我的
leverage, which is knowing what a
杠杆作用，也就是知道如何利用……
company's worth and how to buy it using
公司价值以及如何购买它
other people's money in order to
挪用他人的钱
increase uh my earnings. And that's
增加我的收入。就是这样。
&gt;&gt; interesting. You'd both use the money
有趣的。你们俩都会用这笔钱。
for personal things, probably just pay
个人物品的话，可能直接付钱就行了。
your rent or take your
你的租金或拿走你的
&gt;&gt; doesn't make a difference at that level.
在这个层面上，这无关紧要。
And I mean,
我的意思是，
&gt;&gt; no,
不，
&gt;&gt; even the hundred is close to I mean,
即使是一百也接近我的意思是，
it's more than 10 in one, but
它包含十多种功能，但是
&gt;&gt; yeah. And and this is just one idea. I
是的。这只是其中一个想法。我
think there's so many things you could
我觉得有很多事情你可以做。
do with one and
用一个和
&gt;&gt; but they're all very similar in their
但它们在以下方面都非常相似：
fundamentals
基本面
&gt;&gt; where you go to find some like the
你去哪里找类似的东西？
leverage comes from going tapping into
杠杆作用来自于利用
existing networks. You find an existing
现有网络。你找到一个现有的
business and either you're selling the
要么你正在出售业务，要么你正在出售
business as the product or you're
企业本身就是产品，或者你是
selling the product of that business.
销售该企业的产品。
Right. Exactly. So you're selling either
正确的。确切地。所以你是在卖……
way and all of it is promotion. You're
这一切都是为了推广。你是
selling and you're trying to get a
出售，你正试图获得
percentage of upside. I'm getting a
上涨空间百分比。我正在收到一个
percentage of because like to Cody's
因为喜欢科迪的百分比
point, a lot of mainstream businesses
观点，很多主流企业
don't have money and you're like, "Cool,
你没钱，然后你会想，“酷，
pay me on money that I make you and
你赚的钱就付给我。
they're usually very very generous with
他们通常非常非常慷慨
money they don't have yet."
他们还没有钱。
&gt;&gt; Um, same same for, you know, a deal that
嗯，同样的道理也适用于，你知道，一笔交易……
we haven't made yet, I'll give you, you
我们还没做完，我会给你，你
know, a fee for those things. Again, it
我知道，这些东西是要收费的。再说一遍，它
depends on the timeline. If I have 30
取决于时间安排。如果我有30
days, then like
几天后，就像
&gt;&gt; getting a deal done in 30 days will be
在30天内完成交易将是
tough.
艰难的。
&gt;&gt; Um, but like getting a brick and mortar,
嗯，就像拥有一家实体店一样，
it's like probably do that in 48 hours
大概48小时内就能完成。
to get somebody to say yes to free money
让某人同意免费获得金钱
for like no risk and I do all the work.
几乎没有任何风险，而且所有工作都由我来做。
It's an easy offer. So again, I think it
这是一个很容易答应的条件。所以，我再次认为
dep that's where like the constraints of
依赖项，比如限制条件
the initial prompt is like how much
最初的提示是：多少
money and how much time. If it's a year,
金钱和时间。如果是一年的话，
it's like all of this changes. If it's
感觉一切都变了。如果是
30 days and I have nothing, it's like
30天了，我什么都没得到，感觉就像……
well then we want to generate as much
那么，我们希望尽可能多地产生
cash as we can in little time as
我们尽可能在短时间内拿到现金
possible with no risk.
可行且无风险。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Daniel's about to invest in the S&amp;P 500.
丹尼尔准备投资标普500指数。
&gt;&gt; Right. Because
正确的。因为
&gt;&gt; he's like, I take your your $10,000 and
他就像是说，我拿走你的1万美元，
I raise you. Yeah.
我加你。是的。
&gt;&gt; So I have 100,000.
所以我现在有10万。
&gt;&gt; So
所以
&gt;&gt; he's leaving with it.
他要带着它离开。
&gt;&gt; This this is a dangerous amount of
这是一个危险的量
money.
钱。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. This is the worst case scenario
是的。这是最糟糕的情况。
for most people because if you have a
对大多数人来说，因为如果你有一个
thousand, you know, you don't have
一千，你知道，你没有
money. If you have 10,000, okay, you
钱。如果你有10000，好吧，你
might get a cleaner, you might get an
可能会找个更干净的人，你可能会得到一个
assistant, you might do a few little
助理，你可能会做一些小事。
things with it. The danger of a h
和它有关的东西。 h的危险
100,000 is you can kid yourself into
100,000 是你可以自欺欺人的说法。
thinking that you've got money. And it
你以为自己有钱。而且它
will make your head spin how fast you
速度快得让你头晕目眩
can blow through $100,000 if if you
如果你这样做，可能会花掉10万美元。
don't know what you're doing. If you
你不知道自己在做什么。如果你
give me a Formula One car and ask, "What
给我一辆一级方程式赛车，然后问：“什么？”
am I gonna do with it?" I'm gonna crash
我该拿它怎么办？我要崩溃了。
it, right? if I can get it even started
对吧？如果我能让它启动的话
in the first place. So, I've got to come
首先。所以，我得来了
up with something that the first problem
想出一个办法来解决第一个问题
that I have is I don't have the
我没有的
knowledge. I don't have the network. I
知识。我没有网络连接。我
don't have the reputation. So, here's
没有这样的名声。所以，这就是……
what I'm going to do. I'm going to
我打算做什么。我要
leverage Cody's. I'm going to go to Cody
利用科迪的资源。我要去科迪
and I'm going to say, "Cody, can I do a
然后我会说，“科迪，我可以……”
deal with you? I would like to start a
跟你交易？我想开始一个
business. I know you've got lots of
商业。我知道你有很多
ideas that you just don't have time for.
你根本没时间去实现的想法。
I'm going to invest $100,000 as debt for
我打算以债务形式投资10万美元。
equity for 10%. So, I'm going to put 100
10%股权。所以，我打算填100。
grand in and that'll come out of the
盛大入场，那将来自
business at some point, but debt for
在某个阶段，企业可能会面临债务问题。
equity on 10%. and I'm going to do sweat
10%的股权。我要出汗了
equity for 10% and you keep 80%. And
出资 10%，你保留 80%。和
it's your idea and it's your network and
这是你的想法，这是你的网络，
it's your reputation, but I'll be the
这是你的名誉，但我会是……
person who's heavily invested in this.
对此投入巨资的人。
And the only condition is that as the
唯一的条件是，作为
business becomes profitable, we can
如果企业盈利，我们就可以
repay the 100 grand. Um, and then once
偿还10万美元。嗯，然后一次
it's repaid the 100 grand, either you
它已经偿还了那10万美元，要么你
buy it or we can sell the business.
要么我们买下它，要么我们卖掉这家公司。
Now, what I'm doing there is I'm
现在，我在那里做的是……
basically acknowledging I don't know
基本上承认我不知道
what I'm doing. I'm acknowledging I
我正在做的事情。我承认我
don't have the reputation. I don't have
没有这样的名声。我没有
the knowledge. um all I have is this 100
知识。嗯，我只有这100个。
grand and I have a very strong desire or
宏伟壮丽，我对此有着非常强烈的渴望。
will to be an entrepreneur. Now, what's
有志成为企业家。那么，什么是……
going to happen is that probably with an
接下来可能会发生的事情很可能是……
hour of Cody's time per month, she's
科迪每月花费一小时的时间，她
going to be able to say, "Here's the
能够说，“这是……”
idea. Here's here's my CFO. Talk to my
主意。这是我的首席财务官。跟我说话
CFO. Here's my head of marketing. Talk
首席财务官。这是我的市场部主管。讲话
to my head of marketing. Here's my
致我的市场营销主管。这是我的
friend who's actually got even more
朋友，实际上还有更多
money and wants to invest." And she's
她有钱，想投资。”而且她
just going to like fire off a few emails
我打算发几封邮件。
and she's going to love the idea because
她一定会喜欢这个主意，因为
it's her idea. And I'm going to I'm
这是她的主意。我要去……
going to work hard, right? And what's
你会努力工作的，对吧？什么？
cool is that when the time comes that
酷的是，当时机成熟时……
that business becomes valuable, I've got
那项业务变得有价值，我就有了
one buyer on the table. Cody's either
桌上只有一位买家。科迪要么
going to say, "Hey, look, I'll buy you
我会说，“嘿，你看，我买下你”
out because it's only 20% and now I own
退出，因为它只有20%，而我现在拥有
the whole thing." Uh, or we go to market
整个事情。”呃，或者我们去市场。
and Cody will know someone who can buy
科迪会认识能买得起东西的人。
the business and I get 20% of the exit.
公司退出后，我和公司各占20%的股份。
So, but the key here is that just that
所以，关键就在于此。
acknowledgement that the it's really
承认这一点确实
it's the knowledge, the network, and the
是知识、人脉和……
reputation that is the valuable bit. And
声誉才是最宝贵的。和
the money is a bit of a red herring.
钱的问题其实是个转移视线的幌子。
&gt;&gt; And you're going to get Cody's skills
你将会获得科迪的技能
because you're going to be in her
因为你会在她身边。
proximity. you're going to get a little
距离近。你会得到一点
bit of her reputation
她名声的一部分
&gt;&gt; at the end of that deal. I will then
在那笔交易结束时。然后我将
have knowledge. I'll then have
具备相关知识。然后我就会拥有
reputation. I'll then have uh all of
名声。然后我就会拥有所有的
those things will have leveled up for
这些事物将会升级。
me.
我。
&gt;&gt; You know what else is interesting too?
你知道还有什么也很有趣吗？
It's really what you're proposing is is
你真正提出的方案是……
something that I used to not like and
我以前不喜欢的东西
since have think and since think that
因为我思考过，而且因为思考过
when you find the right ones, it's it's
当你找到合适的人时，那就是……
really fascinating which it's a
真是太迷人了，这是一个
franchise model. You're essentially
特许经营模式。你基本上
saying which is what you do when you
也就是说，当你这样做的时候
come to a franchise. If you come to
加入加盟店。如果你来
Resibrands, you go, "Okay, I have
Resibrands，你会说，“好的，我有
$75,000. I don't know anything about
75,000美元。我对此一无所知。
window cleaning. I don't know anything
擦窗。我什么都不知道。
about running a business. But I do know
关于企业运营。但我知道
that you know how to do it. And I know
你知道该怎么做。我知道
that you have all these case studies,
您拥有所有这些案例研究，
aka proof of other people just like me
也就是证明还有其他人也和我一样
that have done it. So, I'm actually
已经做到了。所以，我其实是
going to pay you for this business for
我会付钱给你做这笔生意。
the right for you to take a percentage
您有权提取一定比例的金额
of my ownership forever in perpetuity.
我永远拥有所有权。
Um, but I will teach you how to or you
嗯，但我会教你怎么做，或者你
will teach me how to run the business.
会教我如何经营这家企业。
And so I think that's actually I I think
所以我觉得这其实就是……
I used to think that franchises weren't
我以前认为特许经营权不是
good for entrepreneurs because I am
这对创业者来说是好事，因为我就是
relatively unemployable and I don't like
就业前景相对黯淡，我不喜欢
to be told what to do. But for people
被告知该做什么。但对于人们来说
that have never run a business before
那些以前从未经营过企业的人
like what you're saying is like I'm
就像你说的，就像我是
paying you for the right to learn
付钱给你学习的权利
because you have a proven system that if
因为你拥有一个行之有效的系统，如果
I use it over time I have a lower
随着时间的推移，我的使用量逐渐减少
likelihood of failure because we know
因为我们知道，失败的可能性很大。
the truth which is 90% of startups fail.
事实是，90%的创业公司都会失败。
&gt;&gt; Most startups never make any money. you
大多数创业公司都赚不到钱。你
pay for the right to maybe potentially
付费以获得可能的权利
one day make money. And so I do think
总有一天会赚到钱。所以我认为
stealing other people's homework is is
偷别人的作业是……
real and valuable. I
真实且有价值。我
&gt;&gt; I wanted to ask you all a question which
我想问大家一个问题，
I have an answer to. So I assumed you
我有答案。所以我以为你
would but maybe you don't, which is what
你会这么做，但也许你不会，这就是原因。
is the one thing about entrepreneurship,
这是创业的本质，
wealth creation, finance that you think
财富创造，你所认为的金融
most people undervalue that you you put
大多数人低估了你所付出的。
a a disproportionate amount of weight
不成比例的重量
on. So like for me, I can think of a
在。比如对我来说，我可以想到一个
game in business. I think of business as
商业游戏。我认为商业是
a set of games we're playing. I can
我们正在玩的一系列游戏。我可以
think of a particular game in business
想想商业中的某个特定游戏
that I don't think other entrepreneurs
我不认为其他企业家会这样。
understand the value of and I'm
我理解它的价值，而且我是
wondering if you all have an answer to
想知道你们有没有答案
that as well. Is there one game in this
也一样。这里面有一款游戏吗？
game of business, one fundamental game
商业游戏，一项基本游戏
that you think most entrepreneurs
你认为大多数企业家
listening now don't appreciate and they
现在听着，他们并不欣赏，而且他们
should from the entrepreneurs you've
应该从你认识的企业家那里获得
worked and invested in and being one
努力工作并投资，成为其中一员
yourself?
你自己？
&gt;&gt; Well, I think I'll say one that everyone
嗯，我想我会说一句大家都会喜欢的话。
here at the table will agree with. But I
在座各位都会同意。但我
think that brand and distribution is
认为品牌和分销是
still wildly undervalued. M
仍然被严重低估。 M
&gt;&gt; I mean I think that's the reason that
我的意思是，我认为这就是原因所在。
all of us decided to get into it is
我们都决定参与其中。
because you just I mean at least I saw
因为你，我的意思是，至少我看到了
just the wild discrepancy between cost
仅仅是成本方面的巨大差异。
of of building brand and building
品牌建设和建设
distribution versus the value of that
分布与该值的关系
distribution and you know the the primes
分布情况，你知道质数。
the lunches the you know some of these
你知道，这些午餐中的一些
in insane zero to many billion dollar
从零到数十亿美元的疯狂转变
case studies uh term huda beauty proper
案例研究呃术语huda beauty proper
proper uh whatever it is for yeah like
合适的，呃，不管它是什么，是的，就像
there's there's so many examples at this
这里有很多例子。
point that it's almost trite um I still
这一点几乎是老生常谈了，嗯，我仍然
think it's undervalued distribution,
我认为它的分销价值被低估了。
which is building an audience that you
也就是建立一个你
own
自己的
&gt;&gt; that has a high likelihood of of
极有可能
complying with requests,
遵照要求，
&gt;&gt; aka brand.
又名品牌。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I mean, well, I think that's a
是的。我的意思是，嗯，我认为那是一个
very good one. And and the reason that
非常好。原因在于……
we know that it's so undervalued is
我们知道它被严重低估了。
we're all offered things all the time
我们总是会收到各种各样的邀约。
that do not I mean, I remember talking
我的意思是，我记得我说过
to my president of my company, and I was
致我公司总裁，而我当时
the former president of Mr. Beast. It
Mr. Beast 的前任总裁。它
was interesting is he said like every
他说这很有趣，就像他说的每一个
deal we looked at,
我们考察过的交易，
&gt;&gt; we almost regretted doing it. Like we
我们几乎后悔这么做了。就像我们
couldn't I think you and I talked about
难道我不能认为你和我谈过这件事吗？
this. We we we couldn't do a deal that
这。我们没能达成那样的交易。
the other party fully understood the
对方完全理解
power of our distribution upfront. We
我们前期分销渠道的优势。我们
almost had to like prove it, put in a
几乎不得不证明这一点，投入……
bunch of milestones on a later date
稍后将迎来一系列里程碑
because the deal is so good. And I found
因为这个交易太划算了。我发现
the same thing in the deals that I did.
我经手的交易也是一样的情况。
Like we've talked about like I mean I
就像我们之前讨论过的，我的意思是，
did a bunch of deals early on where I
早期做了很多交易，我
bought businesses and they couldn't
收购企业后，他们却无法做到。
benefit from distribution. All my
从分销中获益。我的所有
laundromats, my car washes, like it
自助洗衣店，我的洗车店，我喜欢它
doesn't matter that I have a big
我身材高大也没关系。
audience online and so the leverage
在线受众群体及其影响力
wasn't there for me. So I think um I
当时我不在。所以我觉得嗯……
think distribution and brand are huge.
我认为分销和品牌至关重要。
Uh the secondary thing that I do not
呃，第二件事，我没有
think most entrepreneurs understand is
我认为大多数企业家都明白这一点
financial engineering. The richest
金融工程。最富有的人
people in the world are rich if if they
如果世界上有人……，他们就是富有的。
didn't get it from daddy and mommy and
不是从爸爸妈妈那里遗传来的，
they didn't get it from uh investing in
他们并非通过投资获得这些资金。
third party companies. They got it from
第三方公司。他们从……那里得到的
um they got it from owning companies and
嗯，他们是通过拥有公司获得的。
buying them over time. Like every
慢慢买入。就像所有
billion there is not a billion dollar
十亿，没有十亿美元。
company that exists that hasn't bought
一家尚未收购的公司
other companies. It doesn't exist. When
其他公司。它并不存在。什么时候
you say financial engineering, how do
你说金融工程，那该如何操作呢？
you simplify that for someone that's 16
你把它简化成一个16岁孩子能理解的样子。
years old?
几岁了？
&gt;&gt; Man, understanding how to get other
伙计，了解如何获得其他
people's money, to say it really simply,
说白了，就是人民的钱。
like how to get other people's money,
比如如何骗取别人的钱，
which sounds a little scammy, except
听起来有点像骗局，但
it's not. You know, most businesses are
它不是。你知道，大多数企业都是
bought with the SBA loans, loans from
用美国小企业管理局贷款购买的，贷款来自
the government that allow you to buy a
允许你购买的政府
business. Businesses need lines of
商业。企业需要生产线
credit. That's just money from the bank
信用。那只是银行的钱而已。
for future state. So, like if you
为了未来状态。所以，就像如果你
actually understood how money and
真正理解了金钱和
finance works in your business, it's
财务在你的企业中发挥作用，它是
harder to die because cash flow is what
更难死去，因为现金流才是关键
keeps your company alive. And also, it's
它能让你的公司生存下去。而且，它也是
easier to buy your competitors because
收购竞争对手更容易，因为
whoever is most funded wins typically.
通常情况下，资金最多的人会获胜。
&gt;&gt; Um, and so I think
嗯，所以我觉得
&gt;&gt; I think more entrepreneurs need to
我认为更多企业家需要
obsess on the thing that uh isn't the
执着于那件并非……的东西
magic. Like the magic is coming up with
魔法。就像魔法正在发生一样
an idea, having the grit, doing the
一个想法，拥有毅力，付诸行动
brand, doing the distribution. That
品牌方负责分销。那
stuff's actually really really hard.
事情其实真的很难。
financial engineering is is modelable.
金融工程是可以建模的。
It's just it's the same every single
只是每次都一样而已。
time. It's just been gatekept by by Wall
时间。它一直被墙把守着。
Street
街道
&gt;&gt; money games. I I had this I had such an
金钱游戏。我曾拥有过这个，我曾拥有过这样一个
epiphany moment when I was like 20 23 24
顿悟时刻发生在我20、23、24岁的时候
years old when my um a German group had
我小时候，我妈妈是德国人，她当时在一个德国团体里。
basically bought the majority of my
基本上买下了我的大部分东西。
company out and I got to spend a lot of
公司不在家，我有很多时间
time because we now had this German
因为我们现在有了这位德国人，所以时间紧迫。
office. So, I was there a lot and I just
办公室。所以，我经常去那里，我只是
observed this one individual who I shan
我观察到这个人，我叫他
and I I I'm there building this business
而我，我正在那里建立这家企业。
and pitching to clients and doing all
向客户推销并完成所有工作
this hard work and I met him and he
他的努力工作让我遇到了他，他
says, "I don't want to do any hard work.
他说：“我不想做任何辛苦的工作。”
I just want to do deals."
我只想做成交易。
&gt;&gt; And I was like, "Tell me more." And I
我当时就想：“跟我说说更多吧。”我
lent in. I'm like, "What do you mean
我凑近问道：“你什么意思？”
deals?" Cuz I'm like, "I'm not sleeping
交易？”因为我心想，“我睡不着。”
here." And this guy looks like he's
就在这里。” 这家伙看起来像是
sleeping like tremendous amounts of
睡得像很多
hours. And he was like, "I just want to
小时。他当时说：“我只想……”
play money games.
玩真钱游戏。
&gt;&gt; I want to be in the middle of the
我想处于中心位置
transaction of the deal and taking
交易的进行和接受
some." But then he's also when he says
有些。”但当他又说……
money games is like leverage and
金钱游戏就像杠杆一样。
arbitrage
套利
&gt;&gt; raising money against an asset,
以资产作抵押筹集资金
overvaluing that asset and buying lots
高估该资产并大量买入
of cheaper assets with the value of the
价格更低的资产，其价值为
expensive asset.
昂贵的资产。
&gt;&gt; And he made a lot of money doing exactly
他正是靠做这件事赚了很多钱。
that and almost never working cuz he
而且他几乎从不工作。
understood exactly what you're saying is
我完全明白你的意思了。
that really really rich people
那些真正富有的人
understand money games.
了解金钱游戏。
&gt;&gt; Just how to use money leverage to make
如何利用资金杠杆来赚钱
more money.
更多钱。
&gt;&gt; Look at the Forbes 100 list. It's all
看看福布斯100强榜单。这一切都是
comprised of people who do financial
由从事金融行业的人员组成
arbitrage in one way or another.
以某种方式进行套利。
&gt;&gt; How do I go learn that skill? Do I have
我该如何学习这项技能？我是否拥有
to go work in finance?
去金融行业工作？
&gt;&gt; No, you don't have to work in finance.
不，你不一定要从事金融行业。
But I mean, the best business school is
但我的意思是，最好的商学院是
always be in business. So, get into
永远不要停止经营。所以，进入
business and then obsess on one like I
做生意，然后像我一样痴迷于某件事。
think it's like tiered. Bottom level is
感觉像是分层的。最底层是
like understand a P&amp;L. Most
例如，了解损益表。最多
entrepreneurs don't have a profit and
企业家没有利润，
loss statement. They don't actually
损失报表。他们实际上并没有
track their profit and loss statement. I
跟踪他们的损益表。我
mean, we invested at a $60 million a
也就是说，我们投资了6000万美元。
year year business. The guy didn't have
年度业务。那家伙没有
an up-to-date profit and loss statement.
一份最新的损益表。
It's incredibly common. I'm sure you see
这种情况非常普遍。我相信你看到了
it. you look at a bunch of businesses
它。你看看很多企业
too. Second level after a profit and
也。利润之后的第二层级
loss statement is do I understand where
损失报表我是否理解？
my financing is coming from? All you
我的资金来源是什么？你们所有人
need to do to understand that is talk to
需要做的就是与……交谈
your bankers like do you have a bank
你的银行家会问：你有没有银行账户？
that will lend you money? Understand
哪家公司会借钱给你？理解
why. Uh explain to them what you do and
为什么。呃，向他们解释一下你是做什么的。
see if they understand it and how much
看看他们是否理解，以及理解多少。
money they'll give you. And then the
他们会给你的钱。然后是
third level of the game is go and talk.
游戏的第三关是去交谈。
Every like learning that needs to be
每个人都喜欢学习，这是必要的。
done is just getting in the room with
完成就是进入房间。
other people who have their Tuesdays are
其他周二也有自己安排的人是
like your dream days. So I think you
就像你梦寐以求的日子。所以我觉得你
know you want to get in a room with a
我知道你想和某人待在一个房间里
bunch of people who are doing deals.
一群正在进行交易的人。
That's how you do more deals.
这样才能达成更多交易。
&gt;&gt; When I um I told you earlier we were
我之前跟你说过，我们当时
talking about psychedelics before we
在谈论迷幻药之前
started recording.
开始录制。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Um when I left my last company I had
嗯，当我离开上一家公司时，我……
that year and a half where I invested in
在那一年半的时间里，我投资了
this massive psychedelics company and it
这家庞大的迷幻药公司及其
was the pandemic. So we're working from
是新冠疫情。所以我们正在从
everyone was working from home. I was
大家都在家办公。我当时
working from the billionaire's apartment
在亿万富翁的公寓里工作
in London. And I got to see in the
在伦敦。我得以在……中看到
leadup to the IPO he did 10 IPOs a year.
在IPO之前，他每年进行10次IPO。
So I got to sit in his kitchen and he we
于是我就坐在他家厨房里，我们
used to work over there and I just got
我以前在那边工作，我刚……
to see what was going on. And all he was
看看发生了什么事。而他的一切
doing was making phone calls to people
当时我所做的就是给人们打电话。
with lots and lots of money and he was
他有很多很多钱，而且他
giving them access to the IPO before it
使他们能够在IPO之前获得参与机会
IPOed at a valuation which we all knew
IPO时的估值我们都知道。
was going to 10x. And I just thought, oh
原本要达到10倍。我当时就想，哦
my god, like this is how rich people
我的天，这就是有钱人的生活吗？
make money. They have some kind of
赚钱。他们有某种
access or arbitrage and they move money
他们进行套利或获取资金，并转移资金。
around to capitalize on on these
围绕这些方面来获利
multiples. And I thought, [__] hell,
倍数。我当时想，真是见鬼了。
like that's
就像那样
&gt;&gt; that's the game.
这就是游戏规则。
&gt;&gt; Get around billionaires. I know it's a
与亿万富翁们周旋。我知道这是一个
crazy thing, but you started a podcast.
真是不可思议，你居然开始做播客了。
&gt;&gt; I've done a podcast. Well,
我做过播客。出色地，
&gt;&gt; I'm slightly older than you guys. Like,
我比你们年纪稍大一些。喜欢，
I remember before the internet, before
我记得互联网出现之前，在……之前
YouTube, before all of this sort of
YouTube，在这一切发生之前
stuff. There was no access to the this
东西。无法访问此
information. You couldn't get this
信息。你不可能得到这个
information. And now you can you can
信息。现在你可以了
listen to podcasts. You can chat to chat
听播客。你可以聊天
GBT. You don't even have to get in the
GBT。你甚至不需要进入
room and like it's it's all on the
房间，就像一切都在……
internet. And it blows my mind because I
互联网。这让我难以置信，因为我
remember a time before that. I I love
还记得之前那段时光吗？我爱
what you said. I totally agree with what
你说的话。我完全同意。
you said. I'm going to go with um the
你说。我打算和……一起去。
one game that most people don't
一款大多数人都不玩的游戏
understand is bananas.
理解起来就像香蕉一样。
That's the end of the podcast.
播客到此结束。
&gt;&gt; In lesson one of every economics class,
在每节经济学课的第一课中，
they say if you've got 10 bananas and a
他们说，如果你有10根香蕉和一个
100 people want a banana, you're going
一百个人想要香蕉，你就得去。
to have high prices and profit. Demand
追求高价和高利润。要求
outstrips supply. If you've got 10
供不应求。如果你有10
bananas and only one person wants
香蕉，只有一个人想要
banana, you're going to drop the price
香蕉，你要降价了
of those bananas and you're going to
那些香蕉，你打算
make a loss and your business is going
亏损，你的生意就完了。
to go badly. And what most people do not
情况会变得很糟糕。而大多数人却不这么认为。
understand is that the whole game
理解的是，整个游戏
relates to constrained supply and excess
涉及供应受限和过剩。
demand. And if you can't constrain the
要求。如果你无法限制
supply and create excess demand, you
供给并制造过剩需求，你
won't get a profit. You can take
不会盈利。你可以拿
something like Google Maps, which
类似谷歌地图之类的东西，
probably costs 500 million to set up and
建设成本可能高达5亿美元。
and launch satellites and everything,
还有发射卫星等等，
they have to give it away for free
他们必须免费赠送。
because they have infinite supply. They
因为它们的供应是无限的。他们
have they can supply everyone on the
他们能否为所有人提供所需物品？
planet with Google Maps. So, because
使用谷歌地图绘制地球。所以，因为
there's infinite supply, they just give
供应无限，他们只是给予。
it away for free. But Google Ads,
免费获得。但谷歌广告，
there's a limited number of people who
人数有限
can advertise on every search. So
可以在每次搜索中投放广告。所以
because that's limited, the the price
因为数量有限，所以价格也高。
goes up. So I have a client who saves
上升。我有个客户很节俭。
lives and they do first aid training and
他们活着，并且接受急救培训。
they're an amazing person and they
他们是很棒的人，而且
literally save children's lives and all
确实能拯救孩子的生命等等
this sort of stuff. And she's telling
诸如此类的事情。她正在讲述
me, you know, why aren't I able to
你知道，为什么我不能
trade, you know, charge more money? I'm
你知道，就是通过交易来提高价格？我是
literally saving lives. I'm a really
真正意义上的救人。我真是个
good person and I'm very valuable. I say
我是一个好人，而且非常有价值。我说
because the whole game, no one that
因为整场比赛，没有人……
that's not the game. The game is demand
那不是游戏规则。这款游戏很受欢迎
outstrip supply. So you need to
供不应求。所以你需要
constrain the supply of something and
限制某种东西的供应和
you need to manufacture excess demand
你需要制造过剩需求
and unfortunately as as much as you
不幸的是，正如你所说……
might be the most amazing human being if
如果……他可能是最了不起的人
you can't manufacture demand and supply
你无法人为制造需求和供给。
tension you can't make a profit.
紧张到无法盈利。
&gt;&gt; I was hoping and thinking someone might
我当时希望并认为可能会有人
say hiring
招聘
&gt;&gt; because for me my answer is hiring.
因为对我来说，我的答案就是招聘。
That's the first thing I go to. I
那是我首先要做的事情。我
remember Richard Branson sitting me down
记得理查德·布兰森叫我坐下。
when we spoke in New York and saying
我们在纽约交谈时说
listen I built one of the biggest groups
听着，我创建了最大的团队之一。
in Europe and my CFO had pulled me out
我当时在欧洲，我的首席财务官把我调走了。
of the room and said I don't know what
房间里，他说我不知道​​什么
net profit is and he says my CFO got
净利润是，他说我的首席财务官得到了
crayons and a piece of paper and drew
用蜡笔和一张纸画画
fishes in a net in an ocean and said
海洋里渔网里的鱼，然后说
Richard that's your net profit and then
理查德，那是你的净利润，然后
they walked back in the room and he was
他们走回房间，他
at the time running one of the biggest
当时经营着一家规模最大的公司之一。
groups in Europe.
欧洲的团体。
When he said that to me, I was like,
他跟我说这话的时候，我当时就想，
"Wow." He was like, "You don't really
“哇。”他当时说：“你其实并不……”
need to know much if you're a really
如果你真的想了解很多，那就需要知道很多。
masterful delegator."
一位杰出的授权者。
&gt;&gt; And he said I was a dyslexic thinker.
他说我是个有阅读障碍的思考者。
So, I was always forced from the very
所以，我从一开始就总是被迫的。
beginning to just find someone to do it.
开始找人来做这件事。
That was exceptional. And actually, the
那真是太棒了。实际上，
further I've gone in my career, the more
我的职业生涯越走越远，就越觉得
just like you figure out like
就像你发现的那样
&gt;&gt; the game, this game, that it's actually
这场游戏，这个游戏，它实际上是
just a couple of fundamental things that
只是几个基本要点。
sway the outcomes. Like most of the
影响结果。像大多数
returns come from like a couple of
收益来自几个方面
things. In business, I've just come to
事物。在商业领域，我刚刚开始
learn the further I've got that my
我越走越远，就越明白我的
returns come from truly exceptional
回报来自真正卓越的事物。
people, binding them with a culture and
人们，将他们与一种文化联系在一起，
then setting them the sort of strategy
然后为他们制定策略。
or more technical things that
或者更技术性的问题
&gt;&gt; I would agree with that. And the reason
我同意。原因
you can find such amazing talented
你可以找到如此才华横溢的人才
people and so could Richard Branson is
人们，所以理查德·布兰森也可能如此。
because first he could create excess
因为他首先能够创造过剩。
demand for that role and then you could
要求担任那个职位，然后你就可以……
choose from that list.
请从列表中选择。
&gt;&gt; So I go back to when I was 18. I was 18,
所以我要追溯到我18岁的时候。我当时18岁，
broke, drop out of university, parents
破产，大学辍学，父母
aren't speaking to me, shoplifting food.
他们不跟我说话，还偷东西。
I managed to get a guy called Chris who
我设法找到了一个叫克里斯​​的家伙，
was running a business to
经营一家企业
um stop his business. He was he was
阻止他的生意。他就是他
double my age and successful to stop his
年龄是我的两倍，而且成功阻止了他
business and to decide to come and build
开展业务并决定前来建设
a social network with a kid who was
一个有孩子的社交网络
stealing Chicago town pizzas in
在芝加哥镇偷披萨
Manchester who had never built a
曼彻斯特从未建造过
technology company before in exch I
科技公司之前在交易所
didn't pay him in exchange for 30% of
没有付钱给他，而是给了他30%的股份。
the company. And this goes back to this
公司。而这又回到了这一点。
whole thing about offers. My pitch, my
一切都与优惠有关。我的演讲，我的
offer at that time, I was trading in
当时我正在进行以旧换新的交易
future money, equity, and he believed in
未来的金钱、股权，以及他所信仰的
the value of the future money. So I say
未来货币的价值。所以我说
to kids all the time, actually, you
实际上，你一直都在对孩子们这么说。
don't need to be in my position now.
我现在不需要处于这种境地。
You've all got future money. And the
你们都有未来的钱。以及
future money is determined by how good
未来的财富取决于你的表现。
your pitch is. Yeah.
你的推销方式是……是的。
&gt;&gt; Your sell is.
你的卖点是。
&gt;&gt; But I think that goes back to that like
但我认为这要追溯到那个时候……
how I talk about pitching for money.
我如何谈论如何筹集资金。
That's your mightest touch. You didn't
那是你最厉害的一击。你没有
have profit.
有利润。
&gt;&gt; You didn't have growth. You didn't have
你没有取得进步。你没有
a track record. What did you have? An
过往业绩。你有什么？一个
incredible [__] story. Yeah. So if
真是个不可思议的故事。是的。所以如果
you got nothing else but a story, then
那你除了故事就什么都没有了。
you can hire people much smarter.
你可以雇佣到更聪明的人。
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
确切地。
&gt;&gt; This actually brings me to a point that
这其实引出了我的观点：
I haven't told the world about yet. I've
我还没来得及告诉全世界。我已经
just built something called culture
刚刚建立了一种叫做文化的东西。
test. You can find it at culture
测试。你可以在文化领域找到它。
test.com. Essentially, the thinking is
test.com。本质上，这种想法是
that one bad hire, as I'm sure all of my
那次糟糕的招聘，我相信我所有的……
guests here will agree, can ruin your
这里的客人都会同意，这会毁了你的生活。
business. It can ruin your idea. So,
商业。它会毁了你的想法。所以，
culture test helps you figure out and
文化测试可以帮助你弄清楚和
spot red flags and people you're
发现危险信号和你身边的人
thinking of working with or currently do
考虑与……合作或目前正在与……合作
work with by making a personalized
通过制定个性化方案来合作。
culture test survey and it scores that
文化测试调查及其得分
person in terms of how aligned they are
就其契合程度而言，这个人
to you and your mission. It has been a
致你和你的使命。这已经是一段
gamecher for my business. We've culture
游戏玩家为我的生意服务。我们有文化
tested about 40,000 people. I just wish
对约4万人进行了检测。我只是希望
I was doing this before. Check it out.
我之前就做过这件事。一探究竟。
Cultureest.com. Make your own culture
Cultureest.com。创造你自己的文化
test. Use it and thank me later. Alex,
测试。用它，以后你会感谢我的。亚历克斯，
you you've got this book about to drop
你手里的这本书马上就要出版了。
called 100 million money models. What is
被称为1亿资金模型。什么是
the one money model in this book that's
这本书中唯一一个货币模型是……
added the most to your net worth?
哪件事对你的净资产贡献最大？
&gt;&gt; So, it's more the concept. So, like each
所以，关键在于概念。所以，就像每个
of the the so offers had the value
因此，这些优惠具有价值。
equation which is kind of the core
这算是核心方程式。
concept that the book was built around.
本书围绕这一概念展开。
Uh the lead's book was about the core
呃，主角的书是关于核心的。
four um the ways to promote anything.
四种推广任何事物的方法。
And so, $100 million money models is
因此，1亿美元的资金模型是
about client finance acquisition which
关于客户融资获取
is fundamentally how you get customers
从根本上讲，这就是你如何获得客户的方式。
to fund your own expansion. And so Cody
为自身扩张提供资金。所以科迪
said this earlier, but depending on the
之前说过，但这取决于……
source, it's roughly like 80% of
来源，大约占80%
businesses fail because of uh poor cash
企业倒闭是因为资金不足。
flow or they they just don't have enough
流量不足，或者他们根本就不够用。
money, right? And the other 20 is
钱，对吧？剩下的20个是
probably just people just give up. And
可能只是人们放弃了。和
so as long as you don't give up, the
所以只要你不放弃，
reason you go to business is you just
你去经商的原因很简单
don't have cash flow. And so that book
没有现金流。所以那本书
solves cash flow, which is why the sub
解决了现金流问题，这就是为什么该子程序
headline is how to make money, which is
标题是“如何赚钱”，也就是
pretty pretty on the nose. But
鼻子很漂亮。但
fundamentally like each of the examples
从根本上来说，每个例子都与上述例子相似。
that I had in my business um and I
我在我的生意中拥有的，嗯，而且我
define that within client fun
在客户端乐趣中定义这一点
acquisition as I define it when you have
我所定义的收购是指当你拥有……
like a $100 million money model is that
就像一个价值1亿美元的资金模型是这样的。
you're able to get a customer to pay you
你能够让客户付款。
twice as much as you spend on them in
是你花在它们身上的钱的两倍
the first 30 days. And by doing that the
前30天。这样做
the more specific equation would be that
更具体的等式是：
your 30-day gross profit from a customer
您从客户处获得的 30 天毛利润
exceeds two times CAC plus COGS meaning
超过 CAC 加 COGS 的两倍
CAC is in cost of car customer plus cost
CAC 是汽车客户成本加上其他费用。
uh COGS which is cost of goods sold. So,
呃，COGS，即销售成本。所以，
how much does it cost me to get them?
购买它们需要多少钱？
How much does it cost me to deliver
送货需要多少钱？
them? Times two. If I can get that from
他们？乘以二。如果我能从
one person, then for the rest of my
一个人，然后剩下的时间……
expansion, all the customers finance the
扩张，所有客户都提供资金
acquisition of the next customer and
获取下一个客户和
then cash flow is no longer a constraint
那么现金流就不再是制约因素了。
of the business. You'll still have
这家公司。你仍然会拥有
constraints, you'll still have supply
即使存在供应限制，你仍然会有供应。
constraints, you still have hiring
受限于各种条件，你仍然需要招聘
constraints, you'll still have other
即使存在其他限制，你仍然会有其他问题。
constraints, but cash won't be one of
存在一些限制，但现金不会是其中之一。
them. And so, as a result, you can grow
他们。因此，结果是你可以成长
B pretty much as fast as you can handle.
B 的速度几乎和你能控制的速度一样快。
And so, that is how I've grown all the
所以，这就是我成长为这一切的方式。
companies that I've started without
我创办的公司没有
funding and been able to grow very fast
获得资金并得以快速发展
in each of them um is with that core
在它们每个人身上，嗯，都与那个核心有关。
concept.
概念。
Thank you. Thank you for uh choosing to
谢谢。感谢您选择
be here today. And I invited you here
今天务必到场。我邀请你来这里
because you're the three people that
因为你们三个人
guide me, that I listen to, that I think
指引我，让我倾听，让我思考
have the most credible, important
拥有最可信、最重要的
information that can guide my audience.
能够指导我的听众的信息。
And I know who they are. They're people
我知道他们是谁。他们是人
that want to improve their lives in some
那些想要在某些方面改善生活的人
subjective medium to that the northstar
主观媒介，即北极星
that they have. And you all represent
他们有。你们都代表着
different perspectives and also
不同的视角，以及
different strategies. But there's so
不同的策略。但是还有很多
much so many overlaps that I think
重叠的部分太多了，以至于我认为
actually getting three people like you
实际上，你竟然能找到三个像你这样的人。
around the table to understand where we
大家围坐在桌旁，了解我们身处何方。
overlap and where you think the same is
重叠部分以及你认为相同的地方
incredibly powerful. Um, I highly
威力无比。嗯，我非常
recommend everybody goes and reads Cody
推荐大家去读科迪的书。
Sanchez's book, Main Street Millionaire,
桑切斯的著作《大街上的百万富翁》
&gt;&gt; how to make extraordinary wealth buying
如何通过购买获得巨额财富
ordinary businesses, which is really
普通企业，实际上
what, you know, one of the things Cody
你知道，科迪的其中一件事
has pioneered the idea of um, and made
率先提出了“嗯”这个概念，并制作了
accessible to the masses because most
大众都能接受，因为大多数
people didn't think you could do that.
人们当时认为你不可能做到这一点。
So many of my friends are now buying
我的很多朋友现在都在买
boring businesses, as Cody says, because
正如科迪所说，那些生意很无聊，因为
Cody has laid out a framework to do that
科迪已经为此制定了一个框架。
and to create wealth in this book. And
并通过这本书创造财富。和
my favorite book of Daniel, if I was
如果我是但以理书中我最喜欢的一本书，那就是
over subscribed, how to get people
报名人数过多，如何吸引人
lining up to do business with you. And
排队等着和你做生意。和
there's so many that I could have chose
我本来可以选择的太多了。
from, but also you all have YouTube
不仅如此，你们也都有 YouTube。
channels and your YouTube channels are
频道和您的 YouTube 频道是
amazing. So, I'd ask my audience, I'm
惊人的。所以，我会问我的听众，我是
going to link them all below, to go and
下面我会把它们全部链接起来，方便大家查看。
check out your YouTube channels. Um,
查看一下你的YouTube频道。嗯，
Daniel, you're just starting out on
丹尼尔，你才刚刚起步……
YouTube. You're getting you're getting
YouTube。你正在得到你正在得到
your your feet wet in YouTube.
你刚刚涉足YouTube。
&gt;&gt; But, but Cody and Alex have been making
但是，科迪和亚历克斯一直在努力
so much incredible actionable content. I
海量极具价值的实用内容。我
love one of your new your new formats
喜欢你的新格式之一
where you sit with someone and you sort
你和某人坐在一起，然后你们开始……
of redesign their business with them.
与他们重新设计他们的业务。
and Cody's been making some of the most
科迪一直在创作一些最……
entertaining and informative content on
娱乐性和信息性的内容
on how to get going with with simple um
关于如何开始使用简单的嗯
companies and businesses for the longest
公司和企业长期以来
time. So, please go check out their
时间。所以，请去看看他们的
their work and go follow them on social
他们的作品值得关注，请在社交媒体上关注他们。
media. These are the people that I
媒体。这些人是我
admire the most in this space. And if
在这个空间里，最令人欣赏的是什么？如果
you like what we do here on the
你喜欢我们在这里做的事情吗？
Darvisio, you're going to love what they
达维西奥，你会喜欢他们的东西
do. So, thank you so much everybody for
做。所以，非常感谢大家！
being here, for being so generous with
感谢您的慷慨相助，也感谢您能来到这里。
your time and hopefully we'll do this
占用您一些时间，希望我们能做到。
again sometime soon.
不久后还会再来一次。
&gt;&gt; This has always blown my mind a little
这件事一直让我有点难以置信。
bit. 53% of you that listen to this show
少量。 53% 的听众收听了这个节目
regularly haven't yet subscribed to the
经常还没有订阅
show. So, could I ask you for a favor
展示。所以，我能请你帮个忙吗？
before we start? If you like the show
开始之前？如果你喜欢这个节目
and you like what we do here and you
你喜欢我们在这里做的事情，你
want to support us, the free simple way
想支持我们吗？免费又简单的方式！
that you can do just that is by hitting
你可以通过点击来做到这一点。
the subscribe button. And my commitment
订阅按钮。我的承诺
to you is if you do that, then I'll do
对你来说，如果你那样做，那么我也会那样做。
everything in my power, me and my team,
我和我的团队将竭尽全力
to make sure that this show is better
为了确保这个节目更好
for you every single week. We'll listen
每周都为您准备。我们会听的。
to your feedback. We'll find the guests
感谢您的反馈。我们会找到客人。
that you want me to speak to and we'll
你想让我跟谁谈谈，我们……
continue to do what we do. Thank you so
继续做我们正在做的事情。非常感谢
much.
很多。
[Music]
[音乐]